{"theory":"The Merasardu River is a river in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is a river in Efanangole. The Mbalam is a river in Bolurofi. The Kolufori River is a river in Efanangole. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 432 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 218 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 587 kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which is the longest river in Efanangole?","answer":"Kolufori River","answer_templates":["The {0} is a river in Efanangole","The length of the {0} is 587 kilometers."]}},"flags":["superlative"]}
{"theory":"The Merasardu River is a river in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is a river in Efanangole. The Mbalam is a river in Bolurofi. The Kolufori River is a river in Efanangole. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 61 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 12 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 92 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 58 kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which is the longest river in Efanangole?","answer":"Merasardu River","answer_templates":["The {0} is a river in Efanangole","The length of the {0} is 587 kilometers."]}},"flags":["superlative"]}
{"theory":"The Merasardu River is a river in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is a river in Efanangole. The Mbalam is a river in Bolurofi. The Kolufori River is a river in Efanangole. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 3049 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 6128 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 9587 kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which is the longest river in Efanangole?","answer":"Kolufori River","answer_templates":["The {0} is a river in Efanangole","The length of the {0} is 587 kilometers."]}},"flags":["superlative"]}
{"theory":"The Merasardu River is a river in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is a river in Bolurofi. The Mbalam is a river in Bolurofi. The Kolufori River is a river in Efanangole. There are 2 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 3049 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 6128 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 913 kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which is the longest river in Efanangole?","answer":"Merasardu River","answer_templates":["The {0} is a river in Efanangole","The length of the {0} is 587 kilometers."]}},"flags":["superlative"]}
{"theory":"The Merasardu River is a river in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is a river in Bolurofi. The Mbalam is a river in Bolurofi. The Kolufori River is a river in Efanangole. There are 2 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 13 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 21 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 7 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 91 kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which is the longest river in Efanangole?","answer":"Kolufori River","answer_templates":["The {0} is a river in Efanangole","The length of the {0} is 587 kilometers."]}},"flags":["superlative"]}
{"theory":"If X is in Y and Y is in Z, then X is in Z. The Merasardu River is a river in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is a river in the state of Merafagole. Merafagole is a state in Efanangole. The Mbalam is a river in Bolurofi. The Kolufori River is a river in Efanangole. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 432 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 218 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 587 kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which is the longest river in Efanangole?","answer":"Kolufori River","answer_templates":["The {0} is a river in Efanangole","The length of the {0} is 587 kilometers."]}},"flags":["superlative"]}
{"theory":"If X is in Y and Y is in Z, then X is in Z. The Merasardu River is a river in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is a river in the state of Merafagole. Merafagole is a state in Efanangole. The Mbalam is a river in Bolurofi. The Kolufori River is a river in Efanangole. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 61 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 12 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 92 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 58 kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which is the longest river in Efanangole?","answer":"Merasardu River","answer_templates":["The {0} is a river in Efanangole","The length of the {0} is 587 kilometers."]}},"flags":["superlative"]}
{"theory":"If X is in Y and Y is in Z, then X is in Z. The Merasardu River is a river in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is a river in the state of Merafagole. Merafagole is a state in Efanangole. The Mbalam is a river in Bolurofi. The Kolufori River is a river in Efanangole. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 3049 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 6128 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 9587 kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which is the longest river in Efanangole?","answer":"Kolufori River","answer_templates":["The {0} is a river in Efanangole","The length of the {0} is 587 kilometers."]}},"flags":["superlative"]}
{"theory":"If X is in Y and Y is in Z, then X is in Z. The Merasardu River is a river in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is a river in the state of Merafagole. Merafagole is a state in Bolurofi. The Mbalam is a river in Bolurofi. The Kolufori River is a river in Efanangole. There are 2 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 3049 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 6128 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 913 kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which is the longest river in Efanangole?","answer":"Merasardu River","answer_templates":["The {0} is a river in Efanangole","The length of the {0} is 587 kilometers."]}},"flags":["superlative"]}
{"theory":"If X is in Y and Y is in Z, then X is in Z. The Merasardu River is a river in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is a river in the state of Merafagole. Merafagole is a state in Bolurofi. The Mbalam is a river in Bolurofi. The Kolufori River is a river in Efanangole. There are 2 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 13 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 21 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 7 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 91 kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which is the longest river in Efanangole?","answer":"Kolufori River","answer_templates":["The {0} is a river in Efanangole","The length of the {0} is 587 kilometers."]}},"flags":["superlative"]}
{"theory":"River Giffeleney is a river in Wulstershire. River Wulstershire is a river in the state of Wulstershire. River Elsuir is a river in Wulstershire. The length of River Giffeleney is 413 kilometers. The length of River Wulstershire is 830 kilometers. The length of River Elsuir is 207 kilometers. Every river that is longer than 400 kilometers is major.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the major rivers in Wulstershire?","answer":"River Giffeleney, River Wulstershire"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"River Giffeleney is a river in Wulstershire. River Wulstershire is a river in the state of Wulstershire. River Elsuir is a river in Wulstershire. The length of River Giffeleney is 413 kilometers. The length of River Wulstershire is 830 kilometers. The length of River Elsuir is 207 kilometers. Every river that is longer than 1000 kilometers is major.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the major rivers in Wulstershire?","answer":""}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"River Giffeleney is a river in Wulstershire. River Wulstershire is a river in the state of Wulstershire. River Elsuir is a river in Wulstershire. The length of River Giffeleney is 413 kilometers. The length of River Wulstershire is 830 kilometers. The length of River Elsuir is 207 kilometers. Every river that is longer than 650 kilometers is major.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the major rivers in Wulstershire?","answer":"River Wulstershire"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"River Giffeleney is a river in Wulstershire. River Wulstershire is a river in the state of Wulstershire. River Elsuir is a river in Wulstershire. The length of River Giffeleney is 413 kilometers. The length of River Wulstershire is 830 kilometers. The length of River Elsuir is 207 kilometers. Every river that is longer than 798.2 kilometers is major.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the major rivers in Wulstershire?","answer":"River Wulstershire"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"River Giffeleney is a river in Wulstershire. River Wulstershire is a river in the state of Wulstershire. River Elsuir is a river in Wulstershire. The length of River Giffeleney is 413 kilometers. The length of River Wulstershire is 830 kilometers. The length of River Elsuir is 207 kilometers. Every river that is longer than 100 kilometers is major.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the major rivers in Wulstershire?","answer":"River Elsuir, River Giffeleney, River Wulstershire"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"River Giffeleney is a river in Wulstershire. River Wulstershire is a river in the state of Wulstershire. River Elsuir is a river in Wulstershire. The length of River Giffeleney is 413 kilometers. The length of River Wulstershire is 830 kilometers. The length of River Elsuir is 207 kilometers. Every river that is shorter than 400 kilometers is not major.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What rivers in Wulstershire are not major?","answer":"River Elsuir"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition","negation"]}
{"theory":"River Giffeleney is a river in Wulstershire. River Wulstershire is a river in the state of Wulstershire. River Elsuir is a river in Wulstershire. The length of River Giffeleney is 413 kilometers. The length of River Wulstershire is 830 kilometers. The length of River Elsuir is 207 kilometers. Every river that is shorter than 1000 kilometers is not major.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What rivers in Wulstershire are not major?","answer":"River Elsuir, River Giffeleney, River Wulstershire"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition","negation"]}
{"theory":"River Giffeleney is a river in Wulstershire. River Wulstershire is a river in the state of Wulstershire. River Elsuir is a river in Wulstershire. The length of River Giffeleney is 413 kilometers. The length of River Wulstershire is 830 kilometers. The length of River Elsuir is 207 kilometers. Every river that is shorter than 650 kilometers is not major.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What rivers in Wulstershire are not major?","answer":"River Elsuir, River Giffeleney"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition","negation"]}
{"theory":"River Giffeleney is a river in Wulstershire. River Wulstershire is a river in the state of Wulstershire. River Elsuir is a river in Wulstershire. The length of River Giffeleney is 413 kilometers. The length of River Wulstershire is 830 kilometers. The length of River Elsuir is 207 kilometers. Every river that is shorter than 798.2 kilometers is not major.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What rivers in Wulstershire are not major?","answer":"River Elsuir, River Giffeleney"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition","negation"]}
{"theory":"River Giffeleney is a river in Wulstershire. River Wulstershire is a river in the state of Wulstershire. River Elsuir is a river in Wulstershire. The length of River Giffeleney is 413 kilometers. The length of River Wulstershire is 830 kilometers. The length of River Elsuir is 207 kilometers. Every river that is shorter than 100 kilometers is not major.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What rivers in Wulstershire are not major?","answer":""}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition","negation"]}
{"theory":"If the number of people living in X is Y then the population of X is Y. Every city is in one state. Wilgalway is a city in the state of Wulstershire. 189202 people live in Wilgalway. The elevation of Wilgalway is 32 meters. Elfincaster is a city in Wulstershire. The population of Elfincaster is 87142.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the population of Wilgalway, Wulstershire?","answer":"189202"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"If the number of people living in X is Y then the population of X is Y. Every city is in one state. Wilgalway is a city in the state of Wulstershire. 1322 people live in Wilgalway. The elevation of Wilgalway is 1322 meters. Elfincaster is a city in Wulstershire. The population of Elfincaster is 2210.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the population of Wilgalway, Wulstershire?","answer":"1322"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"If the number of people living in X is Y then the population of X is Y. Every city is in one state. Wilgalway is a city in the state of Wulstershire. 189202 people live in Wilgalway, Wulstershire. The elevation of Wilgalway is 32 meters. Elfincaster is a city in Wulstershire. The population of Elfincaster is 87142. Wilgalway is a city in Eldmunster. The population of Wilgalway, Eldmunster is 89210.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the population of Wilgalway, Wulstershire?","answer":"189202"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"If the number of people living in X is Y then the population of X is Y. Every city is in one state. Wilgalway is a city in the state of Wulstershire. 1322 people live in Wilgalway, Wulstershire. The elevation of Wilgalway is 1322 meters. Elfincaster is a city in Wulstershire. The population of Elfincaster is 87142. Wilgalway is a city in Eldmunster. The population of Wilgalway, Eldmunster is 89210.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the population of Wilgalway, Wulstershire?","answer":"1322"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"If the number of people living in X is Y then the population of X is Y. Every city is in one state. Wilgalway is a city in the state of Wulstershire. 60211 people live in Wilgalway, Wulstershire. The elevation of Wilgalway is 1322 meters. Elfincaster is a city in Wulstershire. The population of Elfincaster is 87142. Wilgalway is a city in Eldmunster. The population of Wilgalway, Eldmunster is 89210.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the population of Wilgalway, Wulstershire?","answer":"60211"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"Every city is in one state. Wilgalway is a city in the state of Wulstershire. The population of Wilgalway is 189202. The elevation of Wilgalway is 32 meters. Elfincaster is a city in Wulstershire. The population of Elfincaster is 87142.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the population of Wilgalway, Wulstershire?","answer":"189202"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"Every city is in one state. Wilgalway is a city in the state of Wulstershire. The population of Wilgalway is 1322. The elevation of Wilgalway is 1322 meters. Elfincaster is a city in Wulstershire. The population of Elfincaster is 2210.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the population of Wilgalway, Wulstershire?","answer":"1322"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"Every city is in one state. Wilgalway is a city in the state of Wulstershire. The population of Wilgalway, Wulstershire is 189202. The elevation of Wilgalway is 32 meters. Elfincaster is a city in Wulstershire. The population of Elfincaster is 87142. Wilgalway is a city in Eldmunster. The population of Wilgalway, Eldmunster is 89210.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the population of Wilgalway, Wulstershire?","answer":"189202"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"Every city is in one state. Wilgalway is a city in the state of Wulstershire. The population of Wilgalway, Wulstershire is 1322. The elevation of Wilgalway is 1322 meters. Elfincaster is a city in Wulstershire. The population of Elfincaster is 87142. Wilgalway is a city in Eldmunster. The population of Wilgalway, Eldmunster is 89210.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the population of Wilgalway, Wulstershire?","answer":"1322"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"Every city is in one state. Wilgalway is a city in the state of Wulstershire. The population of Wilgalway, Wulstershire is 60211. The elevation of Wilgalway is 1322 meters. Elfincaster is a city in Wulstershire. The population of Elfincaster is 87142. Wilgalway is a city in Eldmunster. The population of Wilgalway, Eldmunster is 89210.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the population of Wilgalway, Wulstershire?","answer":"60211"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"Kangoyaken is a state in Gyoshoru. Gunmaishyu is one of the 4 states in Gyoshoru. Ibarakishyo is a state in Gyoshoru. Toyusuma is a state in Dogoreoku. Senkuoka is a state in Gyoshoru. The area of Kangoyaken is 3507 square kilometers. The area of Senkuoka is 4216 square kilometers. The area of Toyusuma is 4198 square kilometers. The area of Ibarakishyo is 9108 square kilometers. The area of Gunmaishyu is 82987 square kilometers. The population of Gunmaishyu is 5218607. The population of Senkuoka is 1027862. The population of Ibarakishyo is 419272. The population of Kangoyaken is 89703. The population of Toyusuma is 19272. The population density of X is the population of X divided by the area of X.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What state in Gyoshoru has the lowest population density?","answer":"Kangoyaken"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","arithmetic","superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Kangoyaken is a state in Gyoshoru. Gunmaishyu is one of the 4 states in Gyoshoru. Ibarakishyo is a state in Gyoshoru. Toyusuma is a state in Dogoreoku. Senkuoka is a state in Gyoshoru. The area of Kangoyaken is 1507 square kilometers. The area of Senkuoka is 4216 square kilometers. The area of Toyusuma is 4198 square kilometers. The area of Ibarakishyo is 9108 square kilometers. The area of Gunmaishyu is 82987 square kilometers. The population of Gunmaishyu is 5218607. The population of Senkuoka is 1027862. The population of Ibarakishyo is 419272. The population of Kangoyaken is 89703. The population of Toyusuma is 19272. The population density of X is the population of X divided by the area of X.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What state in Gyoshoru has the lowest population density?","answer":"Ibarakishyo"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","arithmetic","superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Kangoyaken is a state in Gyoshoru. Gunmaishyu is one of the 4 states in Gyoshoru. Ibarakishyo is a state in Gyoshoru. Toyusuma is a state in Dogoreoku. Senkuoka is a state in Gyoshoru. The area of Kangoyaken is 3507 square kilometers. The area of Senkuoka is 40216 square kilometers. The area of Toyusuma is 4198 square kilometers. The area of Ibarakishyo is 9108 square kilometers. The area of Gunmaishyu is 82987 square kilometers. The population of Gunmaishyu is 5218607. The population of Senkuoka is 1027862. The population of Ibarakishyo is 419272. The population of Kangoyaken is 89703. The population of Toyusuma is 19272. The population density of X is the population of X divided by the area of X.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What state in Gyoshoru has the lowest population density?","answer":"Senkuoka"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","arithmetic","superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Kangoyaken is a state in Gyoshoru. Gunmaishyu is one of the 4 states in Gyoshoru. Ibarakishyo is a state in Gyoshoru. Toyusuma is a state in Dogoreoku. Senkuoka is a state in Gyoshoru. The area of Kangoyaken is 3517 square kilometers. The area of Senkuoka is 40216 square kilometers. The area of Toyusuma is 4198 square kilometers. The area of Ibarakishyo is 9108 square kilometers. The area of Gunmaishyu is 82987 square kilometers. The population of Gunmaishyu is 5218607. The population of Senkuoka is 1027862. The population of Ibarakishyo is 419272. The population of Kangoyaken is 89703. The population of Toyusuma is 19272. The population density of X is the population of X divided by the area of X.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What state in Gyoshoru has the lowest population density?","answer":"Kangoyaken"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","arithmetic","superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Kangoyaken is a state in Dogoreoku. Gunmaishyu is one of the 3 states in Gyoshoru. Ibarakishyo is a state in Gyoshoru. Toyusuma is a state in Dogoreoku. Senkuoka is a state in Gyoshoru. The area of Kangoyaken is 3507 square kilometers. The area of Senkuoka is 4216 square kilometers. The area of Toyusuma is 4198 square kilometers. The area of Ibarakishyo is 9108 square kilometers. The area of Gunmaishyu is 82987 square kilometers. The population of Gunmaishyu is 5218607. The population of Senkuoka is 1027862. The population of Ibarakishyo is 419272. The population of Kangoyaken is 89703. The population of Toyusuma is 19272. The population density of X is the population of X divided by the area of X.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What state in Gyoshoru has the lowest population density?","answer":"Ibarakishyo"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","arithmetic","superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Kangoyaken is a state in Gyoshoru. Gunmaishyu is one of the 4 states in Gyoshoru. Ibarakishyo is a state in Gyoshoru. Toyusuma is a state in Dogoreoku. Senkuoka is a state in Gyoshoru. The area of Kangoyaken is 3507 square kilometers. The area of Senkuoka is 4216 square kilometers. The area of Toyusuma is 4198 square kilometers. The area of Ibarakishyo is 9108 square kilometers. The area of Gunmaishyu is 82987 square kilometers. The population of Gunmaishyu is 5218607. The population of Senkuoka is 1027862. The population of Ibarakishyo is 419272. The population of Kangoyaken is 89703. The population of Toyusuma is 19272. The population density of X is the population of X divided by the area of X.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which state in Gyoshoru has the smallest population density?","answer":"Kangoyaken"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","arithmetic","superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Kangoyaken is a state in Gyoshoru. Gunmaishyu is one of the 4 states in Gyoshoru. Ibarakishyo is a state in Gyoshoru. Toyusuma is a state in Dogoreoku. Senkuoka is a state in Gyoshoru. The area of Kangoyaken is 1507 square kilometers. The area of Senkuoka is 4216 square kilometers. The area of Toyusuma is 4198 square kilometers. The area of Ibarakishyo is 9108 square kilometers. The area of Gunmaishyu is 82987 square kilometers. The population of Gunmaishyu is 5218607. The population of Senkuoka is 1027862. The population of Ibarakishyo is 419272. The population of Kangoyaken is 89703. The population of Toyusuma is 19272. The population density of X is the population of X divided by the area of X.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which state in Gyoshoru has the smallest population density?","answer":"Ibarakishyo"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","arithmetic","superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Kangoyaken is a state in Gyoshoru. Gunmaishyu is one of the 4 states in Gyoshoru. Ibarakishyo is a state in Gyoshoru. Toyusuma is a state in Dogoreoku. Senkuoka is a state in Gyoshoru. The area of Kangoyaken is 3507 square kilometers. The area of Senkuoka is 40216 square kilometers. The area of Toyusuma is 4198 square kilometers. The area of Ibarakishyo is 9108 square kilometers. The area of Gunmaishyu is 82987 square kilometers. The population of Gunmaishyu is 5218607. The population of Senkuoka is 1027862. The population of Ibarakishyo is 419272. The population of Kangoyaken is 89703. The population of Toyusuma is 19272. The population density of X is the population of X divided by the area of X.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which state in Gyoshoru has the smallest population density?","answer":"Senkuoka"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","arithmetic","superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Kangoyaken is a state in Gyoshoru. Gunmaishyu is one of the 4 states in Gyoshoru. Ibarakishyo is a state in Gyoshoru. Toyusuma is a state in Dogoreoku. Senkuoka is a state in Gyoshoru. The area of Kangoyaken is 3517 square kilometers. The area of Senkuoka is 40216 square kilometers. The area of Toyusuma is 4198 square kilometers. The area of Ibarakishyo is 9108 square kilometers. The area of Gunmaishyu is 82987 square kilometers. The population of Gunmaishyu is 5218607. The population of Senkuoka is 1027862. The population of Ibarakishyo is 419272. The population of Kangoyaken is 89703. The population of Toyusuma is 19272. The population density of X is the population of X divided by the area of X.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which state in Gyoshoru has the smallest population density?","answer":"Kangoyaken"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","arithmetic","superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Kangoyaken is a state in Dogoreoku. Gunmaishyu is one of the 3 states in Gyoshoru. Ibarakishyo is a state in Gyoshoru. Toyusuma is a state in Dogoreoku. Senkuoka is a state in Gyoshoru. The area of Kangoyaken is 3507 square kilometers. The area of Senkuoka is 4216 square kilometers. The area of Toyusuma is 4198 square kilometers. The area of Ibarakishyo is 9108 square kilometers. The area of Gunmaishyu is 82987 square kilometers. The population of Gunmaishyu is 5218607. The population of Senkuoka is 1027862. The population of Ibarakishyo is 419272. The population of Kangoyaken is 89703. The population of Toyusuma is 19272. The population density of X is the population of X divided by the area of X.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which state in Gyoshoru has the smallest population density?","answer":"Ibarakishyo"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","arithmetic","superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Ballaterma is a city in the state of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Emprizia is a city in Cartabitan. Cartabitan is a state in Catardinia. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Baritolloti is a city in Grappulia. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. There are 5 cities in Catardinia. The population of Ballaterma is 7014892. The population of Emprizia is 162932. The population of Veronizzia is 8201310. The population of Baritolloti is 90128. The population of Brescitabia is 278109. Elfincaster is a city in Wulstershire. Dorbincester is a city in Wulstershire. The population of Dorbincester is 17142. If X is in Y and Y is in Z, then X is in Z.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the smallest city in Catardinia?","answer":"Baritolloti"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Ballaterma is a city in the state of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Emprizia is a city in Cartabitan. Cartabitan is a state in Catardinia. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Baritolloti is a city in Grappulia. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. There are 5 cities in Catardinia. The population of Ballaterma is 7014892. The population of Emprizia is 162932. The population of Veronizzia is 8201310. The population of Baritolloti is 190128. The population of Brescitabia is 278109. Elfincaster is a city in Wulstershire. Dorbincester is a city in Wulstershire. The population of Dorbincester is 17142. If X is in Y and Y is in Z, then X is in Z.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the smallest city in Catardinia?","answer":"Emprizia"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Ballaterma is a city in the state of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Emprizia is a city in Cartabitan. Cartabitan is a state in Catardinia. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Baritolloti is a city in Grappulia. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. There are 5 cities in Catardinia. The population of Ballaterma is 4892. The population of Emprizia is 162932. The population of Veronizzia is 8201310. The population of Baritolloti is 190128. The population of Brescitabia is 278109. Elfincaster is a city in Wulstershire. Dorbincester is a city in Wulstershire. The population of Dorbincester is 17142. If X is in Y and Y is in Z, then X is in Z.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the smallest city in Catardinia?","answer":"Ballaterma"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Ballaterma is a city in the state of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Emprizia is a city in Cartabitan. Cartabitan is a state in Catardinia. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Baritolloti is a city in Grappulia. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. There are 5 cities in Catardinia. The population of Ballaterma is 70. The population of Emprizia is 162. The population of Veronizzia is 8201. The population of Baritolloti is 90. The population of Brescitabia is 86. Elfincaster is a city in Wulstershire. Dorbincester is a city in Wulstershire. The population of Dorbincester is 142. If X is in Y and Y is in Z, then X is in Z.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the smallest city in Catardinia?","answer":"Ballaterma"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Ballaterma is a city in the state of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Emprizia is a city in Cartabitan. Cartabitan is a state in Catardinia. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Baritolloti is a city in Grappulia. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. There are 5 cities in Catardinia. The population of Ballaterma is 70. The population of Emprizia is 162. The population of Veronizzia is 8201. The population of Baritolloti is 90. The population of Brescitabia is 86. Elfincaster is a city in Wulstershire. Dorbincester is a city in Wulstershire. The population of Dorbincester is 11. If X is in Y and Y is in Z, then X is in Z.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the smallest city in Catardinia?","answer":"Ballaterma"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Ballaterma is a city in the state of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Emprizia is a city in Cartabitan. Cartabitan is a state in Catardinia. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Baritolloti is a city in Grappulia. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. There are 5 cities in Catardinia. The population of Ballaterma is 7014892. The population of Emprizia is 162932. The population of Veronizzia is 8201310. The population of Baritolloti is 90128. The population of Brescitabia is 278109. Elfincaster is a city in Wulstershire. The population of Elfincaster is 21027. Dorbincester is a city in Wulstershire. The population of Dorbincester is 11714201. If X is in Y and Y is in Z, then X is in Z.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the largest city in Catardinia?","answer":"Veronizzia"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Ballaterma is a city in the state of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Emprizia is a city in Cartabitan. Cartabitan is a state in Catardinia. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Baritolloti is a city in Grappulia. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. There are 5 cities in Catardinia. The population of Ballaterma is 7014892. The population of Emprizia is 162932. The population of Veronizzia is 6201310. The population of Baritolloti is 190128. The population of Brescitabia is 278109. Elfincaster is a city in Wulstershire. The population of Elfincaster is 21027. Dorbincester is a city in Wulstershire. The population of Dorbincester is 17142. If X is in Y and Y is in Z, then X is in Z.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the largest city in Catardinia?","answer":"Ballaterma"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Ballaterma is a city in the state of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Emprizia is a city in Cartabitan. Cartabitan is a state in Catardinia. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Baritolloti is a city in Grappulia. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. There are 5 cities in Catardinia. The population of Ballaterma is 4892. The population of Emprizia is 162932. The population of Veronizzia is 8201310. The population of Baritolloti is 190128. The population of Brescitabia is 278109. Elfincaster is a city in Wulstershire. The population of Elfincaster is 21027. Dorbincester is a city in Wulstershire. The population of Dorbincester is 17142. If X is in Y and Y is in Z, then X is in Z.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the largest city in Catardinia?","answer":"Veronizzia"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Ballaterma is a city in the state of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Emprizia is a city in Cartabitan. Cartabitan is a state in Catardinia. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Baritolloti is a city in Grappulia. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. There are 5 cities in Catardinia. The population of Ballaterma is 70. The population of Emprizia is 162. The population of Veronizzia is 8201. The population of Baritolloti is 90. The population of Brescitabia is 86. Elfincaster is a city in Wulstershire. The population of Elfincaster is 21027. Dorbincester is a city in Wulstershire. The population of Dorbincester is 142. If X is in Y and Y is in Z, then X is in Z.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the largest city in Catardinia?","answer":"Veronizzia"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Ballaterma is a city in the state of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Emprizia is a city in Cartabitan. Cartabitan is a state in Catardinia. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Baritolloti is a city in Grappulia. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. There are 5 cities in Catardinia. The population of Ballaterma is 70. The population of Emprizia is 162. The population of Veronizzia is 8201. The population of Baritolloti is 90. The population of Brescitabia is 86. Elfincaster is a city in Wulstershire. The population of Elfincaster is 210. Dorbincester is a city in Wulstershire. The population of Dorbincester is 11. If X is in Y and Y is in Z, then X is in Z.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the largest city in Catardinia?","answer":"Veronizzia"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Grappulia borders Cartabitan. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa borders Grappulia. Bascilitina borders Regnobenoa. Bascilitina borders Grappulia. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Baritolloti is a city in Grappulia. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. Cartabitan is a state in Catardinia. The Begliomento is a river in Catardinia. The Begliomento runs through Grappulia. The Begliomento runs through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco is a river in Catardinia. The Terravipacco runs through Grappulia. The Terravipacco runs through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco runs through Bascilitina. The Pernatisone is a river in Catardinia. The Pernatisone runs through Grappulia. If X borders Y, then Y borders X.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which rivers run through states that border the state with the capital Baritolloti?","answer":"Begliomento, Terravipacco"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Grappulia borders Cartabitan. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa borders Grappulia. Bascilitina borders Regnobenoa. Bascilitina borders Grappulia. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Baritolloti is a city in Grappulia. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. Cartabitan is a state in Catardinia. The Begliomento is a river in Catardinia. The Begliomento runs through Grappulia. The Begliomento runs through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco is a river in Catardinia. The Terravipacco runs through Grappulia. The Terravipacco runs through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco runs through Bascilitina. The Pernatisone is a river in Catardinia. The Pernatisone runs through Grappulia. If X borders Y, then Y borders X.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which rivers run through states that border the state with the capital Baritolloti?","answer":"Begliomento, Terravipacco"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Grappulia borders Cartabitan. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Bascilitina borders Regnobenoa. Bascilitina borders Grappulia. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Baritolloti is a city in Grappulia. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. Cartabitan is a state in Catardinia. The Begliomento is a river in Catardinia. The Begliomento runs through Grappulia. The Begliomento runs through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco is a river in Catardinia. The Terravipacco runs through Grappulia. The Terravipacco runs through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco runs through Bascilitina. The Pernatisone is a river in Catardinia. The Pernatisone runs through Grappulia. If X borders Y, then Y borders X.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which rivers run through states that border the state with the capital Baritolloti?","answer":"Terravipacco"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Grappulia borders Cartabitan. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Bascilitina borders Regnobenoa. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Baritolloti is a city in Grappulia. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. Cartabitan is a state in Catardinia. The Begliomento is a river in Catardinia. The Begliomento runs through Grappulia. The Begliomento runs through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco is a river in Catardinia. The Terravipacco runs through Grappulia. The Terravipacco runs through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco runs through Bascilitina. The Pernatisone is a river in Catardinia. The Pernatisone runs through Grappulia. No river runs through Cartabitan. If X borders Y, then Y borders X.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which rivers run through states that border the state with the capital Baritolloti?","answer":""}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa borders Grappulia. Bascilitina borders Regnobenoa. Bascilitina borders Grappulia. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Baritolloti is a city in Grappulia. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. Cartabitan is a state in Catardinia. The Begliomento is a river in Catardinia. The Begliomento runs through Grappulia. The Begliomento runs through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco is a river in Catardinia. The Terravipacco runs through Grappulia. The Terravipacco runs through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco runs through Bascilitina. The Pernatisone is a river in Catardinia. The Pernatisone runs through Grappulia. If X borders Y, then Y borders X.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which rivers run through states that border the state with the capital Baritolloti?","answer":"Begliomento, Terravipacco"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Grappulia borders Cartabitan. Cartabitan borders Grappulia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa borders Grappulia. Grappulia borders Regnobenoa. Bascilitina borders Regnobenoa. Regnobenoa borders Bascilitina. Bascilitina borders Grappulia. Grappulia borders Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Baritolloti is a city in Grappulia. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. Cartabitan is a state in Catardinia. The Begliomento is a river in Catardinia. The Begliomento runs through Grappulia. The Begliomento runs through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco is a river in Catardinia. The Terravipacco runs through Grappulia. The Terravipacco runs through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco runs through Bascilitina. The Pernatisone is a river in Catardinia. The Pernatisone runs through Grappulia.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which rivers run through states that border the state with the capital Baritolloti?","answer":"Begliomento, Terravipacco"}}}
{"theory":"Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Grappulia borders Cartabitan. Cartabitan borders Grappulia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa borders Grappulia. Grappulia borders Regnobenoa. Bascilitina borders Regnobenoa. Regnobenoa borders Bascilitina. Bascilitina borders Grappulia. Grappulia borders Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Baritolloti is a city in Grappulia. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. Cartabitan is a state in Catardinia. The Begliomento is a river in Catardinia. The Begliomento runs through Grappulia. The Begliomento runs through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco is a river in Catardinia. The Terravipacco runs through Grappulia. The Terravipacco runs through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco runs through Bascilitina. The Pernatisone is a river in Catardinia. The Pernatisone runs through Grappulia.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which rivers run through states that border the state with the capital Baritolloti?","answer":"Begliomento, Terravipacco"}}}
{"theory":"Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Grappulia borders Cartabitan. Cartabitan borders Grappulia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Bascilitina borders Regnobenoa. Regnobenoa borders Bascilitina. Bascilitina borders Grappulia. Grappulia borders Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Baritolloti is a city in Grappulia. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. Cartabitan is a state in Catardinia. The Begliomento is a river in Catardinia. The Begliomento runs through Grappulia. The Begliomento runs through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco is a river in Catardinia. The Terravipacco runs through Grappulia. The Terravipacco runs through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco runs through Bascilitina. The Pernatisone is a river in Catardinia. The Pernatisone runs through Grappulia.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which rivers run through states that border the state with the capital Baritolloti?","answer":"Terravipacco"}}}
{"theory":"Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Grappulia borders Cartabitan. Cartabitan borders Grappulia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Bascilitina borders Regnobenoa. Regnobenoa borders Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Baritolloti is a city in Grappulia. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. Cartabitan is a state in Catardinia. The Begliomento is a river in Catardinia. The Begliomento runs through Grappulia. The Begliomento runs through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco is a river in Catardinia. The Terravipacco runs through Grappulia. The Terravipacco runs through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco runs through Bascilitina. The Pernatisone is a river in Catardinia. The Pernatisone runs through Grappulia. No river runs through Cartabitan.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which rivers run through states that border the state with the capital Baritolloti?","answer":""}}}
{"theory":"Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa borders Grappulia. Grappulia borders Regnobenoa. Bascilitina borders Regnobenoa. Regnobenoa borders Bascilitina. Bascilitina borders Grappulia. Grappulia borders Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Baritolloti is a city in Grappulia. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. Cartabitan is a state in Catardinia. The Begliomento is a river in Catardinia. The Begliomento runs through Grappulia. The Begliomento runs through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco is a river in Catardinia. The Terravipacco runs through Grappulia. The Terravipacco runs through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco runs through Bascilitina. The Pernatisone is a river in Catardinia. The Pernatisone runs through Grappulia.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which rivers run through states that border the state with the capital Baritolloti?","answer":"Begliomento, Terravipacco"}}}
{"theory":"Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Cartabitan is one of the 4 states in Catardinia. The Begliomento is a river in Catardinia. The Begliomento runs through Grappulia. The Begliomento runs through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco is a river in Catardinia. The Terravipacco runs through Grappulia. The Terravipacco runs through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco runs through Bascilitina. The Pernatisone is a river in Catardinia. The Pernatisone runs through Grappulia.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"The Begliomento runs through what states?","answer":"Grappulia, Regnobenoa"}}}
{"theory":"Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Cartabitan is one of the 4 states in Catardinia. The Begliomento is a river in Catardinia. The Begliomento runs through Grappulia. The Begliomento runs through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco is a river in Catardinia. The Terravipacco runs through Grappulia. The Terravipacco runs through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco runs through Bascilitina. The Pernatisone is a river in Catardinia. The Pernatisone runs through Grappulia.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"The Terravipacco runs through what states?","answer":"Bascilitina, Grappulia, Regnobenoa"}}}
{"theory":"Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Cartabitan is one of the 4 states in Catardinia. The Begliomento is a river in Catardinia. The Begliomento runs through Grappulia. The Begliomento runs through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco is a river in Catardinia. The Terravipacco runs through Grappulia. The Terravipacco runs through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco runs through Bascilitina. The Pernatisone is a river in Catardinia. The Pernatisone runs through Grappulia.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"The Pernatisone runs through what states?","answer":"Grappulia"}}}
{"theory":"Grappulia is one of the 4 states in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Cartabitan is a state in Catardinia. The Begliomento is a river in Catardinia. The Begliomento runs through Grappulia. The Begliomento runs through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco is a river in Catardinia. The Terravipacco runs through Grappulia. The Terravipacco runs through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco runs through Bascilitina. The Pernatisone is a river in Catardinia. The Pernatisone runs through Grappulia.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"The Begliomento runs through what states?","answer":"Grappulia, Regnobenoa"}}}
{"theory":"Grappulia is one of the 4 states in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Cartabitan is a state in Catardinia. The Begliomento is a river in Catardinia. The Begliomento runs through Grappulia. The Begliomento runs through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco is a river in Catardinia. The Terravipacco runs through Grappulia. The Terravipacco runs through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco runs through Bascilitina. The Pernatisone is a river in Catardinia. The Pernatisone runs through Grappulia.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"The Terravipacco runs through what states?","answer":"Bascilitina, Grappulia, Regnobenoa"}}}
{"theory":"Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Cartabitan is one of the 7 states in Catardinia. Umbriazzo is a state in Catardinia. Lordanidia is a state in Catardinia. Estmolise is a state in Catardinia. The Begliomento is a river in Catardinia. The Begliomento runs through Grappulia. The Begliomento runs through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco is a river in Catardinia. The Terravipacco runs through Grappulia. The Terravipacco runs through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco runs through Bascilitina. The Pernatisone is a river in Catardinia. The Pernatisone runs through Grappulia. The Terravipacco runs through Umbriazzo. Terravipacco runs through Lordanidia. Terravipacco runs through Estmolise.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"The Begliomento runs through what states?","answer":"Grappulia, Regnobenoa"}}}
{"theory":"Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Cartabitan is one of the 7 states in Catardinia. Umbriazzo is a state in Catardinia. Lordanidia is a state in Catardinia. Estmolise is a state in Catardinia. The Begliomento is a river in Catardinia. The Begliomento runs through Grappulia. The Begliomento runs through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco is a river in Catardinia. The Terravipacco runs through Grappulia. The Terravipacco runs through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco runs through Bascilitina. The Pernatisone is a river in Catardinia. The Pernatisone runs through Grappulia. Terravipacco runs through Umbriazzo. Terravipacco runs through Lordanidia. Terravipacco runs through Estmolise.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"The Terravipacco runs through what states?","answer":"Bascilitina, Grappulia, Regnobenoa, Umbriazzo, Lordanidia, Estmolise"}}}
{"theory":"Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Cartabitan is one of the 7 states in Catardinia. Umbriazzo is a state in Catardinia. Lordanidia is a state in Catardinia. Estmolise is a state in Catardinia. The Begliomento is a river in Catardinia. The Begliomento runs through Grappulia. The Begliomento runs through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco is a river in Catardinia. The Terravipacco runs through Grappulia. The Terravipacco runs through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco runs through Bascilitina. The Pernatisone is a river in Catardinia. The Pernatisone runs through Grappulia. Terravipacco runs through Umbriazzo. Terravipacco runs through Lordanidia. Terravipacco runs through Estmolise.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"The Pernatisone runs through what states?","answer":"Grappulia"}}}
{"theory":"Grappulia is one of the 7 states in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Cartabitan is a state in Catardinia. Umbriazzo is a state in Catardinia. Lordanidia is a state in Catardinia. Estmolise is a state in Catardinia. The Begliomento is a river in Catardinia. The Begliomento runs through Grappulia. The Begliomento runs through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco is a river in Catardinia. The Terravipacco runs through Grappulia. The Terravipacco runs through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco runs through Bascilitina. The Pernatisone is a river in Catardinia. The Pernatisone runs through Grappulia. Terravipacco runs through Umbriazzo. Terravipacco runs through Lordanidia. Terravipacco runs through Estmolise.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"The Begliomento runs through what states?","answer":"Grappulia, Regnobenoa"}}}
{"theory":"Grappulia is one of the 7 states in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Cartabitan is a state in Catardinia. Umbriazzo is a state in Catardinia. Lordanidia is a state in Catardinia. Estmolise is a state in Catardinia. The Begliomento is a river in Catardinia. The Begliomento runs through Grappulia. The Begliomento runs through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco is a river in Catardinia. The Terravipacco runs through Grappulia. The Terravipacco runs through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco runs through Bascilitina. The Pernatisone is a river in Catardinia. The Pernatisone runs through Grappulia. Terravipacco runs through Umbriazzo. Terravipacco runs through Lordanidia. Terravipacco runs through Estmolise.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"The Terravipacco runs through what states?","answer":"Bascilitina, Grappulia, Regnobenoa, Umbriazzo, Lordanidia, Estmolise"}}}
{"theory":"Wilgalway is a city in the state of Wulstershire. Elfincaster is a city in Wulstershire. Dorbincester is a city in Wulstershire. River Giffeleney is a river in Wulstershire. Wulstershire is a state in Gaelgiland. River Wulstershire runs through Wulstershire. River Elsuir is a river in Wulstershire. Eldmunster is a state in Gaelgiland. River Wulstershire runs through Eldmunster. Baermerick is a state in Gaelgiland. River Elsuir runs through Wulstershire. River Elsuir runs through Baermerick. Gilkarney is a city in Eldmunster. Wilgalway is a city in Eldmunster. Waterghal is a city in Baermerick. River Giffeleney runs through Baermerick.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the cities in states through which the River Wulstershire runs?","answer":"Dorbincester, Elfincaster, Gilkarney, Wilgalway"}}}
{"theory":"Wilgalway is a city in the state of Wulstershire. Elfincaster is a city in Baermerick. Dorbincester is a city in Wulstershire. River Giffeleney is a river in Wulstershire. Wulstershire is a state in Gaelgiland. River Wulstershire runs through Wulstershire. River Elsuir is a river in Wulstershire. Eldmunster is a state in Gaelgiland. River Wulstershire runs through Eldmunster. Baermerick is a state in Gaelgiland. River Elsuir runs through Wulstershire. River Elsuir runs through Baermerick. Gilkarney is a city in Eldmunster. Wilgalway is a city in Eldmunster. Waterghal is a city in Baermerick. River Giffeleney runs through Baermerick.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the cities in states through which the River Wulstershire runs?","answer":"Dorbincester, Gilkarney, Wilgalway"}}}
{"theory":"Wilgalway is a city in the state of Wulstershire. Elfincaster is a city in Baermerick. Dorbincester is a city in Wulstershire. River Giffeleney is a river in Wulstershire. Wulstershire is a state in Gaelgiland. River Wulstershire runs through Wulstershire. River Elsuir is a river in Wulstershire. Eldmunster is a state in Gaelgiland. River Wulstershire runs through Eldmunster. Baermerick is a state in Gaelgiland. River Elsuir runs through Wulstershire. River Elsuir runs through Baermerick. Gilkarney is a city in Wulstershire. Wilgalway is a city in Eldmunster. Waterghal is a city in Baermerick. River Giffeleney runs through Baermerick.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the cities in states through which the River Wulstershire runs?","answer":"Dorbincester, Gilkarney, Wilgalway"}}}
{"theory":"Wilgalway is a city in the state of Wulstershire. Elfincaster is a city in Baermerick. Dorbincester is a city in Wulstershire. River Giffeleney is a river in Wulstershire. Wulstershire is a state in Gaelgiland. River Wulstershire runs through Wulstershire. River Elsuir is a river in Wulstershire. Eldmunster is a state in Gaelgiland. River Wulstershire runs through Eldmunster. Baermerick is a state in Gaelgiland. River Elsuir runs through Wulstershire. River Elsuir runs through Baermerick. Gilkarney is a city in Baermerick. Wilgalway is a city in Eldmunster. Waterghal is a city in Baermerick. River Giffeleney runs through Baermerick.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the cities in states through which the River Wulstershire runs?","answer":"Dorbincester, Wilgalway"}}}
{"theory":"Wilgalway is a city in the state of Wulstershire. Elfincaster is a city in Baermerick. Dorbincester is a city in Wulstershire. River Giffeleney is a river in Wulstershire. Wulstershire is a state in Gaelgiland. River Wulstershire runs through Wulstershire. River Elsuir is a river in Wulstershire. Eldmunster is a state in Gaelgiland. River Wulstershire runs through Eldmunster. Baermerick is a state in Gaelgiland. River Elsuir runs through Wulstershire. River Elsuir runs through Baermerick. Gilkarney is a city in Baermerick. Wilgalway is a city in Baermerick. Waterghal is a city in Baermerick. River Giffeleney runs through Baermerick.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the cities in states through which the River Wulstershire runs?","answer":"Dorbincester, Wilgalway"}}}
{"theory":"Wilgalway is a city in the state of Wulstershire. Elfincaster is a city in Wulstershire. Dorbincester is a city in Wulstershire. River Giffeleney is a river in Wulstershire. Wulstershire is a state in Gaelgiland. River Wulstershire runs through Wulstershire. River Elsuir is a river in Wulstershire. Eldmunster is a state in Gaelgiland. River Wulstershire runs through Eldmunster. Baermerick is a state in Gaelgiland. River Elsuir runs through Wulstershire. River Elsuir runs through Baermerick. Gilkarney is a city in Eldmunster. Wilgalway is a city in Eldmunster. Waterghal is a city in Baermerick. River Giffeleney runs through Baermerick.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the cities in states through which the River Elsuir runs?","answer":"Dorbincester, Elfincaster, Waterghal, Wilgalway"}}}
{"theory":"Wilgalway is a city in the state of Wulstershire. Elfincaster is a city in Baermerick. Dorbincester is a city in Wulstershire. River Giffeleney is a river in Wulstershire. Wulstershire is a state in Gaelgiland. River Wulstershire runs through Wulstershire. River Elsuir is a river in Wulstershire. Eldmunster is a state in Gaelgiland. River Wulstershire runs through Eldmunster. Baermerick is a state in Gaelgiland. River Elsuir runs through Wulstershire. River Elsuir runs through Baermerick. Gilkarney is a city in Eldmunster. Wilgalway is a city in Eldmunster. Waterghal is a city in Baermerick. River Giffeleney runs through Baermerick.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the cities in states through which the River Elsuir runs?","answer":"Dorbincester, Elfincaster, Waterghal, Wilgalway"}}}
{"theory":"Wilgalway is a city in the state of Wulstershire. Elfincaster is a city in Baermerick. Dorbincester is a city in Wulstershire. River Giffeleney is a river in Wulstershire. Wulstershire is a state in Gaelgiland. River Wulstershire runs through Wulstershire. River Elsuir is a river in Wulstershire. Eldmunster is a state in Gaelgiland. River Wulstershire runs through Eldmunster. Baermerick is a state in Gaelgiland. River Elsuir runs through Wulstershire. River Elsuir runs through Baermerick. Gilkarney is a city in Wulstershire. Wilgalway is a city in Eldmunster. Waterghal is a city in Baermerick. River Giffeleney runs through Baermerick.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the cities in states through which the River Elsuir runs?","answer":"Dorbincester, Elfincaster, Gilkarney, Waterghal, Wilgalway"}}}
{"theory":"Wilgalway is a city in the state of Wulstershire. Elfincaster is a city in Baermerick. Dorbincester is a city in Wulstershire. River Giffeleney is a river in Wulstershire. Wulstershire is a state in Gaelgiland. River Wulstershire runs through Wulstershire. River Elsuir is a river in Wulstershire. Eldmunster is a state in Gaelgiland. River Wulstershire runs through Eldmunster. Baermerick is a state in Gaelgiland. River Elsuir runs through Wulstershire. River Elsuir runs through Baermerick. Gilkarney is a city in Baermerick. Wilgalway is a city in Eldmunster. Waterghal is a city in Baermerick. River Giffeleney runs through Baermerick.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the cities in states through which the River Elsuir runs?","answer":"Dorbincester, Elfincaster, Gilkarney, Waterghal, Wilgalway"}}}
{"theory":"Wilgalway is a city in the state of Wulstershire. Elfincaster is a city in Baermerick. Dorbincester is a city in Wulstershire. River Giffeleney is a river in Wulstershire. Wulstershire is a state in Gaelgiland. River Wulstershire runs through Wulstershire. River Elsuir is a river in Wulstershire. Eldmunster is a state in Gaelgiland. River Wulstershire runs through Eldmunster. Baermerick is a state in Gaelgiland. River Elsuir runs through Wulstershire. River Elsuir runs through Baermerick. Gilkarney is a city in Baermerick. Wilgalway is a city in Baermerick. Waterghal is a city in Baermerick. River Giffeleney runs through Baermerick.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the cities in states through which the River Elsuir runs?","answer":"Dorbincester, Elfincaster, Gilkarney, Waterghal, Wilgalway"}}}
{"theory":"If the population of X is Y then the number of people living in X is Y. Every city is in one state. Wilgalway is a city in the state of Wulstershire. 189202 people live in Wilgalway. The elevation of Wilgalway is 32 meters. Elfincaster is a city in Wulstershire. The population of Elfincaster is 87142.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"How many people live in Wilgalway, Wulstershire?","answer":"189202"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"If the population of X is Y then the number of people living in X is Y. Every city is in one state. Wilgalway is a city in the state of Wulstershire. 1322 people live in Wilgalway. The elevation of Wilgalway is 1322 meters. Elfincaster is a city in Wulstershire. The population of Elfincaster is 2210.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"How many people live in Wilgalway, Wulstershire?","answer":"1322"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"If the population of X is Y then the number of people living in X is Y. Every city is in one state. Wilgalway is a city in the state of Wulstershire. 189202 people live in Wilgalway, Wulstershire. The elevation of Wilgalway is 32 meters. Elfincaster is a city in Wulstershire. The population of Elfincaster is 87142. Wilgalway is a city in Eldmunster. The population of Wilgalway, Eldmunster is 89210.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"How many people live in Wilgalway, Wulstershire?","answer":"189202"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"If the population of X is Y then the number of people living in X is Y. Every city is in one state. Wilgalway is a city in the state of Wulstershire. 1322 people live in Wilgalway, Wulstershire. The elevation of Wilgalway is 1322 meters. Elfincaster is a city in Wulstershire. The population of Elfincaster is 87142. Wilgalway is a city in Eldmunster. The population of Wilgalway, Eldmunster is 89210.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"How many people live in Wilgalway, Wulstershire?","answer":"1322"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"If the population of X is Y then the number of people living in X is Y. Every city is in one state. Wilgalway is a city in the state of Wulstershire. 60211 people live in Wilgalway, Wulstershire. The elevation of Wilgalway is 1322 meters. Elfincaster is a city in Wulstershire. The population of Elfincaster is 87142. Wilgalway is a city in Eldmunster. The population of Wilgalway, Eldmunster is 89210.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"How many people live in Wilgalway, Wulstershire?","answer":"60211"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"If the population of X is Y then the number of people living in X is Y. Every city is in one state. Wilgalway is a city in the state of Wulstershire. The population of Wilgalway is 189202. The elevation of Wilgalway is 32 meters. Elfincaster is a city in Wulstershire. The population of Elfincaster is 87142.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"How many people live in Wilgalway, Wulstershire?","answer":"189202"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"If the population of X is Y then the number of people living in X is Y. Every city is in one state. Wilgalway is a city in the state of Wulstershire. The population of Wilgalway is 1322. The elevation of Wilgalway is 1322 meters. Elfincaster is a city in Wulstershire. The population of Elfincaster is 2210.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"How many people live in Wilgalway, Wulstershire?","answer":"1322"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"If the population of X is Y then the number of people living in X is Y. Every city is in one state. Wilgalway is a city in the state of Wulstershire. The population of Wilgalway, Wulstershire is 189202. The elevation of Wilgalway is 32 meters. Elfincaster is a city in Wulstershire. The population of Elfincaster is 87142. Wilgalway is a city in Eldmunster. The population of Wilgalway, Eldmunster is 89210.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"How many people live in Wilgalway, Wulstershire?","answer":"189202"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"If the population of X is Y then the number of people living in X is Y. Every city is in one state. Wilgalway is a city in the state of Wulstershire. The population of Wilgalway, Wulstershire is 1322. The elevation of Wilgalway is 1322 meters. Elfincaster is a city in Wulstershire. The population of Elfincaster is 87142. Wilgalway is a city in Eldmunster. The population of Wilgalway, Eldmunster is 89210.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"How many people live in Wilgalway, Wulstershire?","answer":"1322"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"If the population of X is Y then the number of people living in X is Y. Every city is in one state. Wilgalway is a city in the state of Wulstershire. The population of Wilgalway, Wulstershire is 60211. The elevation of Wilgalway is 1322 meters. Elfincaster is a city in Wulstershire. The population of Elfincaster is 87142. Wilgalway is a city in Eldmunster. The population of Wilgalway, Eldmunster is 89210.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"How many people live in Wilgalway, Wulstershire?","answer":"60211"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam runs through Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River runs through Kolufori. The Merasardu River runs through Efanangole. The Kolufori River runs through Efanangole. The Kolufori River runs through Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the populations of states through which the Kolufori River runs?","answer":"812390, 1420892, 9021832"}}}
{"theory":"The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam runs through Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River runs through Kolufori. The Merasardu River runs through Efanangole. The Kolufori River runs through Efanangole. The Kolufori River runs through Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the populations of states through which the Merasardu River runs?","answer":"1420892"}}}
{"theory":"The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam runs through Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River runs through Kolufori. The Merasardu River runs through Efanangole. The Kolufori River runs through Efanangole. The Kolufori River runs through Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the populations of states through which the Mbalam runs?","answer":"9021832"}}}
{"theory":"The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam runs through Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River runs through Kolufori. The Merasardu River runs through Efanangole. The Kolufori River runs through Efanangole. The Kolufori River runs through Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 14. The population of Bolurofi is 90. The population of Kolufori is 8.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the populations of states through which the Merasardu River runs?","answer":"14"}}}
{"theory":"The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam runs through Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River runs through Kolufori. The Merasardu River runs through Efanangole. The Kolufori River runs through Efanangole. The Kolufori River runs through Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 14. The population of Bolurofi is 90. The population of Kolufori is 8.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the populations of states through which the Mbalam runs?","answer":"90"}}}
{"theory":"The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam runs through Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River runs through Kolufori. The Merasardu River runs through Efanangole. The Kolufori River runs through Efanangole. The Kolufori River runs through Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. The Mbalam does not run through Kolufori. The Merasardu River does not run through Kolufori. The Merasardu River does not run through Bolurofi.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the populations of states through which the Kolufori River runs?","answer":"812390, 1420892, 9021832"}}}
{"theory":"The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam runs through Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River runs through Kolufori. The Merasardu River runs through Efanangole. The Kolufori River runs through Efanangole. The Kolufori River runs through Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. The Mbalam does not run through Kolufori. The Merasardu River does not run through Kolufori. The Merasardu River does not run through Bolurofi.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the populations of states through which the Merasardu River runs?","answer":"1420892"}}}
{"theory":"The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam runs through Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River runs through Kolufori. The Merasardu River runs through Efanangole. The Kolufori River runs through Efanangole. The Kolufori River runs through Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. The Mbalam does not run through Kolufori. The Merasardu River does not run through Kolufori. The Merasardu River does not run through Bolurofi.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the populations of states through which the Mbalam runs?","answer":"9021832"}}}
{"theory":"The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam runs through Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River runs through Kolufori. The Merasardu River runs through Efanangole. The Kolufori River runs through Efanangole. The Kolufori River runs through Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 14. The population of Bolurofi is 90. The population of Kolufori is 8. The Mbalam does not run through Kolufori. The Merasardu River does not run through Kolufori. The Merasardu River does not run through Bolurofi.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the populations of states through which the Merasardu River runs?","answer":"14"}}}
{"theory":"The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam runs through Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River runs through Kolufori. The Merasardu River runs through Efanangole. The Kolufori River runs through Efanangole. The Kolufori River runs through Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 14. The population of Bolurofi is 90. The population of Kolufori is 8. The Mbalam does not run through Kolufori. The Merasardu River does not run through Kolufori. The Merasardu River does not run through Bolurofi.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the populations of states through which the Mbalam runs?","answer":"90"}}}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"The Voronolga runs through what provinces?","answer":"Bripetrsk, Galininograd, Puotorsk, Voronolga"}}}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"The Kolonolga runs through what provinces?","answer":"Bripetrsk, Getarovo, Puotorsk"}}}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"The Karbankaya runs through what provinces?","answer":"Abdorostan, Voronolga"}}}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"The Chetershka runs through what provinces?","answer":"Fordgorod"}}}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"The Brasyugan runs through what provinces?","answer":"Puotorsk"}}}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"The Voronolga runs through what provinces?","answer":"Bripetrsk, Galininograd, Puotorsk, Voronolga"}}}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"The Kolonolga runs through what provinces?","answer":"Bripetrsk, Getarovo, Puotorsk"}}}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"The Karbankaya runs through what provinces?","answer":"Abdorostan, Voronolga"}}}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"The Chetershka runs through what provinces?","answer":"Fordgorod"}}}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"The Brasyugan runs through what provinces?","answer":"Puotorsk"}}}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is a province in Bievorsk. There are 7 provinces. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The population of Abdorostan is 6712302. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What province has the most population?","answer":"Getarovo"}},"flags":["superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is a province in Bievorsk. There are 7 provinces. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The population of Abdorostan is 6712302. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The population of Getarovo is 2912062. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What province has the most population?","answer":"Voronolga"}},"flags":["superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is a province in Bievorsk. There are 7 provinces. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. The population of Voronolga is 101. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The population of Abdorostan is 67. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The population of Fordgorod is 72. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The population of Galininograd is 23. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The population of Puotorsk is 41. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The population of Getarovo is 229. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The population of Bripetrsk is 4. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What province has the most population?","answer":"Getarovo"}},"flags":["superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is a province in Bievorsk. There are 7 provinces. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. The population of Voronolga is 101. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The population of Abdorostan is 67. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The population of Fordgorod is 72. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The population of Galininograd is 23. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The population of Puotorsk is 41. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The population of Getarovo is 22. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The population of Bripetrsk is 4. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What province has the most population?","answer":"Voronolga"}},"flags":["superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is a province in Bievorsk. There are 7 provinces. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. The population of Voronolga is 10. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The population of Abdorostan is 67. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The population of Fordgorod is 72. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The population of Galininograd is 23. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The population of Puotorsk is 41. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The population of Getarovo is 22. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The population of Bripetrsk is 4. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What province has the most population?","answer":"Fordgorod"}},"flags":["superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is a province in Bievorsk. There are 7 provinces. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The population of Abdorostan is 6712302. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What province has the least population?","answer":"Puotorsk"}},"flags":["superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is a province in Bievorsk. There are 7 provinces. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The population of Abdorostan is 6712302. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The population of Getarovo is 2912062. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What province has the least population?","answer":"Puotorsk"}},"flags":["superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is a province in Bievorsk. There are 7 provinces. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. The population of Voronolga is 101. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The population of Abdorostan is 67. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The population of Fordgorod is 72. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The population of Galininograd is 23. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The population of Puotorsk is 41. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The population of Getarovo is 229. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The population of Bripetrsk is 4. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What province has the least population?","answer":"Bripetrsk"}},"flags":["superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is a province in Bievorsk. There are 7 provinces. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. The population of Voronolga is 101. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The population of Abdorostan is 67. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The population of Fordgorod is 72. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The population of Galininograd is 23. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The population of Puotorsk is 41. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The population of Getarovo is 22. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The population of Bripetrsk is 4. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What province has the least population?","answer":"Bripetrsk"}},"flags":["superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is a province in Bievorsk. There are 7 provinces. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. The population of Voronolga is 10. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The population of Abdorostan is 67. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The population of Fordgorod is 72. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The population of Galininograd is 23. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The population of Puotorsk is 41. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The population of Getarovo is 22. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The population of Bripetrsk is 4. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What province has the least population?","answer":"Bripetrsk"}},"flags":["superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"If X is in Y and Y is in Z then X is in Z. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. The population of Lomberona is 10230192. The population of Messinitina is 816291. The population of Baritolloti is 913022. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. The population of Lomtrieste is 18201392. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. The population of Albucapua is 728102. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. The population of Geoturin is 41290. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. The population of Veronizzia is 219326. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. The population of Brescitabia is 91049. Cartabitan is one of the 4 states in Catardinia.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the largest capital city in Catardinia?","answer":"Baritolloti"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"If X is in Y and Y is in Z then X is in Z. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. The population of Lomberona is 10230192. The population of Messinitina is 816291. The population of Baritolloti is 913022. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. The population of Lomtrieste is 18201392. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. The population of Albucapua is 2728102. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. The population of Geoturin is 41290. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. The population of Veronizzia is 219326. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. The population of Brescitabia is 91049. Cartabitan is one of the 4 states in Catardinia.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the largest capital city in Catardinia?","answer":"Albucapua"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"If X is in Y and Y is in Z then X is in Z. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. The population of Lomberona is 10230192. The population of Messinitina is 816291. The population of Baritolloti is 91302. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. The population of Lomtrieste is 18201392. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. The population of Albucapua is 728102. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. The population of Geoturin is 41290. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. The population of Veronizzia is 219326. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. The population of Brescitabia is 91049. Cartabitan is one of the 4 states in Catardinia.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the largest capital city in Catardinia?","answer":"Messinitina"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"If X is in Y and Y is in Z then X is in Z. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. The population of Lomberona is 1023. The population of Messinitina is 81. The population of Baritolloti is 91. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. The population of Lomtrieste is 1820. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. The population of Albucapua is 72. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. The population of Geoturin is 4. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. The population of Veronizzia is 21. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. The population of Brescitabia is 9. Cartabitan is one of the 4 states in Catardinia.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the largest capital city in Catardinia?","answer":"Baritolloti"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"If X is in Y and Y is in Z then X is in Z. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. The population of Lomberona is 1023. The population of Messinitina is 81. The population of Baritolloti is 91. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. The population of Lomtrieste is 1820. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. The population of Albucapua is 272. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. The population of Geoturin is 4. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. The population of Veronizzia is 21. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. The population of Brescitabia is 9. Cartabitan is one of the 4 states in Catardinia.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the largest capital city in Catardinia?","answer":"Albucapua"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. The population of Lomberona is 10230192. The population of Messinitina is 816291. The population of Baritolloti is 913022. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. The population of Lomtrieste is 18201392. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. The population of Albucapua is 728102. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. The population of Geoturin is 41290. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. The population of Veronizzia is 219326. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. The population of Brescitabia is 91049. Cartabitan is one of the 4 states in Catardinia. Baritolloti is in Catardinia. Messinitina is in Catardinia. Lomberona is in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is in Catardinia. Albucapua is in Catardinia. Geoturin is in Catardinia. Veronizzia is in Catardinia. Brescitabia is in Catardinia.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the largest capital city in Catardinia?","answer":"Baritolloti"}},"flags":["superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. The population of Lomberona is 10230192. The population of Messinitina is 816291. The population of Baritolloti is 913022. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. The population of Lomtrieste is 18201392. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. The population of Albucapua is 2728102. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. The population of Geoturin is 41290. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. The population of Veronizzia is 219326. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. The population of Brescitabia is 91049. Cartabitan is one of the 4 states in Catardinia. Baritolloti is in Catardinia. Messinitina is in Catardinia. Lomberona is in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is in Catardinia. Albucapua is in Catardinia. Geoturin is in Catardinia. Veronizzia is in Catardinia. Brescitabia is in Catardinia.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the largest capital city in Catardinia?","answer":"Albucapua"}},"flags":["superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. The population of Lomberona is 10230192. The population of Messinitina is 816291. The population of Baritolloti is 91302. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. The population of Lomtrieste is 18201392. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. The population of Albucapua is 728102. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. The population of Geoturin is 41290. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. The population of Veronizzia is 219326. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. The population of Brescitabia is 91049. Cartabitan is one of the 4 states in Catardinia. Baritolloti is in Catardinia. Messinitina is in Catardinia. Lomberona is in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is in Catardinia. Albucapua is in Catardinia. Geoturin is in Catardinia. Veronizzia is in Catardinia. Brescitabia is in Catardinia.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the largest capital city in Catardinia?","answer":"Messinitina"}},"flags":["superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. The population of Lomberona is 1023. The population of Messinitina is 81. The population of Baritolloti is 91. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. The population of Lomtrieste is 1820. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. The population of Albucapua is 72. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. The population of Geoturin is 4. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. The population of Veronizzia is 21. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. The population of Brescitabia is 9. Cartabitan is one of the 4 states in Catardinia. Baritolloti is in Catardinia. Messinitina is in Catardinia. Lomberona is in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is in Catardinia. Albucapua is in Catardinia. Geoturin is in Catardinia. Veronizzia is in Catardinia. Brescitabia is in Catardinia.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the largest capital city in Catardinia?","answer":"Baritolloti"}},"flags":["superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. The population of Lomberona is 1023. The population of Messinitina is 81. The population of Baritolloti is 91. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. The population of Lomtrieste is 1820. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. The population of Albucapua is 272. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. The population of Geoturin is 4. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. The population of Veronizzia is 21. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. The population of Brescitabia is 9. Cartabitan is one of the 4 states in Catardinia. Baritolloti is in Catardinia. Messinitina is in Catardinia. Lomberona is in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is in Catardinia. Albucapua is in Catardinia. Geoturin is in Catardinia. Veronizzia is in Catardinia. Brescitabia is in Catardinia.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the largest capital city in Catardinia?","answer":"Albucapua"}},"flags":["superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 6712302. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 2912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the populations of provinces which border Abdorostan?","answer":"410293, 7290132, 10178291"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 6712302. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 2912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the populations of provinces which border Getarovo?","answer":"410293, 412908, 2392010, 10178291"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 6712302. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 2912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the populations of provinces which border Bripetrsk?","answer":"2392010, 2912062, 7290132"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 6712302. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 2912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the populations of provinces which border Voronolga?","answer":"410293, 2392010, 2912062, 6712302, 7290132"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 6712302. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 2912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the populations of provinces which border Puotorsk?","answer":"2912062, 6712302, 10178291"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 6712302. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 2912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. Puotorsk borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Fordgorod. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Abdorostan. Voronolga borders Abdorostan. Getarovo borders Voronolga. Puotorsk borders Getarovo. Galininograd borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Galininograd. Getarovo borders Bripetrsk. Fordgorod borders Bripetrsk.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the populations of provinces which border Abdorostan?","answer":"410293, 7290132, 10178291"}}}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 6712302. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 2912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. Puotorsk borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Fordgorod. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Abdorostan. Voronolga borders Abdorostan. Getarovo borders Voronolga. Puotorsk borders Getarovo. Galininograd borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Galininograd. Getarovo borders Bripetrsk. Fordgorod borders Bripetrsk.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the populations of provinces which border Getarovo?","answer":"410293, 412908, 2392010, 10178291"}}}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 6712302. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 2912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. Puotorsk borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Fordgorod. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Abdorostan. Voronolga borders Abdorostan. Getarovo borders Voronolga. Puotorsk borders Getarovo. Galininograd borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Galininograd. Getarovo borders Bripetrsk. Fordgorod borders Bripetrsk.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the populations of provinces which border Bripetrsk?","answer":"2392010, 2912062, 7290132"}}}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 6712302. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 2912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. Puotorsk borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Fordgorod. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Abdorostan. Voronolga borders Abdorostan. Getarovo borders Voronolga. Puotorsk borders Getarovo. Galininograd borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Galininograd. Getarovo borders Bripetrsk. Fordgorod borders Bripetrsk.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the populations of provinces which border Voronolga?","answer":"410293, 2392010, 2912062, 6712302, 7290132"}}}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 6712302. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 2912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. Puotorsk borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Fordgorod. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Abdorostan. Voronolga borders Abdorostan. Getarovo borders Voronolga. Puotorsk borders Getarovo. Galininograd borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Galininograd. Getarovo borders Bripetrsk. Fordgorod borders Bripetrsk.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the populations of provinces which border Puotorsk?","answer":"2912062, 6712302, 10178291"}}}
{"theory":"Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the capital of states that have cities named Baritolloti?","answer":"Baritolloti","answer_templates":["{0} is the capital city of the state of Grappulia.", "{0} is the capital of the state of Grappulia."]}},"flags":["lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the capital of states that have cities named Lomberona?","answer":"Messinitina","answer_templates":["{0} is a city in Regnobenoa.", "The capital city of Regnobenoa is {0}.", "The capital of Regnobenoa is {0}."]}},"flags":["lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the capital of states that have cities named Lomtrieste?","answer":"Albucapua","answer_templates":["{0} is the capital city of the state of Bascilitina.", "{0} is the capital of the state of Bascilitina."]}},"flags":["lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the capital of states that have cities named Albucapua?","answer":"Albucapua","answer_templates":["{0} is the capital city of the state of Bascilitina.", "{0} is the capital of the state of Bascilitina."]}},"flags":["lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the capital of states that have cities named Brescitabia?","answer":"Geoturin","answer_templates":["{0} is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan.", "{0} is the capital of the state of Cartabitan."]}},"flags":["lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. Lomberona is a city in Cartabitan.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the capital of states that have cities named Lomberona?","answer":"Geoturin, Messinitina"}},"flags":["lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. Lomberona is a city in Cartabitan.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the capital of states that have cities named Veronizzia?","answer":"Geoturin","answer_templates":["{0} is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan.", "{0} is the capital of the state of Cartabitan."]}},"flags":["lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. Lomberona is a city in Cartabitan.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the capital of states that have cities named Baritolloti?","answer":"Baritolloti","answer_templates":["{0} is the capital city of the state of Grappulia.", "{0} is the capital of the state of Grappulia."]}},"flags":["lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. Lomberona is a city in Cartabitan.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the capital of states that have cities named Lomtrieste?","answer":"Albucapua","answer_templates":["{0} is the capital city of the state of Bascilitina.", "{0} is the capital of the state of Bascilitina."]}},"flags":["lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. Lomberona is a city in Cartabitan.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the capital of states that have cities named Geoturin?","answer":"Geoturin","answer_templates":["{0} is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan.", "{0} is the capital of the state of Cartabitan."]}},"flags":["lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. There are 2 cities in Senkuoka.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the biggest city in Kangoyaken?","answer":"Dogayashi"}},"flags":["superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 192301. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. There are 2 cities in Senkuoka.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the biggest city in Kangoyaken?","answer":"Kagenegawa"}},"flags":["superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 1329020. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 192301. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. There are 2 cities in Senkuoka.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the biggest city in Kangoyaken?","answer":"Koruhashi"}},"flags":["superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 13. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 192. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino is 21. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 4. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 81. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 2139. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 2. There are 2 cities in Senkuoka.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the biggest city in Kangoyaken?","answer":"Dogayashi"}},"flags":["superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 13. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 19. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino is 21. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 4. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 81. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 2139. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 2. There are 2 cities in Senkuoka.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the biggest city in Kangoyaken?","answer":"Kagenegawa"}},"flags":["superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. There are 2 cities in Senkuoka.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the smallest city in Kangoyaken?","answer":"Agarikoshi"}},"flags":["superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 192301. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. There are 2 cities in Senkuoka.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the smallest city in Kangoyaken?","answer":"Agarikoshi"}},"flags":["superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 1329020. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 192301. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. There are 2 cities in Senkuoka.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the smallest city in Kangoyaken?","answer":"Agarikoshi"}},"flags":["superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 13. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 192. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino is 21. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 4. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 81. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 2139. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 2. There are 2 cities in Senkuoka.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the smallest city in Kangoyaken?","answer":"Agarikoshi"}},"flags":["superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 13. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 19. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino is 21. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 4. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 81. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 2139. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 2. There are 2 cities in Senkuoka.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the smallest city in Kangoyaken?","answer":"Agarikoshi"}},"flags":["superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"River Giffeleney is a river in Wulstershire. River Wulstershire is a river in the state of Wulstershire. River Elsuir is a river in Wulstershire. The length of River Giffeleney is 413 kilometers. The length of River Wulstershire is 830 kilometers. The length of River Elsuir is 207 kilometers. Every river that is longer than 400 kilometers is long.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the long rivers in Wulstershire?","answer":"River Giffeleney, River Wulstershire"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"River Giffeleney is a river in Wulstershire. River Wulstershire is a river in the state of Wulstershire. River Elsuir is a river in Wulstershire. The length of River Giffeleney is 413 kilometers. The length of River Wulstershire is 830 kilometers. The length of River Elsuir is 207 kilometers. Every river that is longer than 1000 kilometers is long.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the long rivers in Wulstershire?","answer":""}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"River Giffeleney is a river in Wulstershire. River Wulstershire is a river in the state of Wulstershire. River Elsuir is a river in Wulstershire. The length of River Giffeleney is 413 kilometers. The length of River Wulstershire is 830 kilometers. The length of River Elsuir is 207 kilometers. Every river that is longer than 650 kilometers is long.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the long rivers in Wulstershire?","answer":"River Wulstershire"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"River Giffeleney is a river in Wulstershire. River Wulstershire is a river in the state of Wulstershire. River Elsuir is a river in Wulstershire. The length of River Giffeleney is 413 kilometers. The length of River Wulstershire is 830 kilometers. The length of River Elsuir is 207 kilometers. Every river that is longer than 798.2 kilometers is long.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the long rivers in Wulstershire?","answer":"River Wulstershire"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"River Giffeleney is a river in Wulstershire. River Wulstershire is a river in the state of Wulstershire. River Elsuir is a river in Wulstershire. The length of River Giffeleney is 413 kilometers. The length of River Wulstershire is 830 kilometers. The length of River Elsuir is 207 kilometers. Every river that is longer than 100 kilometers is long.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the long rivers in Wulstershire?","answer":"River Elsuir, River Giffeleney, River Wulstershire"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"River Giffeleney is a river in Wulstershire. River Wulstershire is a river in the state of Wulstershire. River Elsuir is a river in Wulstershire. The length of River Giffeleney is 413 kilometers. The length of River Wulstershire is 830 kilometers. The length of River Elsuir is 207 kilometers. Every river that is shorter than 400 kilometers is not long.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What rivers in Wulstershire are not long?","answer":"River Elsuir"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition","negation"]}
{"theory":"River Giffeleney is a river in Wulstershire. River Wulstershire is a river in the state of Wulstershire. River Elsuir is a river in Wulstershire. The length of River Giffeleney is 413 kilometers. The length of River Wulstershire is 830 kilometers. The length of River Elsuir is 207 kilometers. Every river that is shorter than 1000 kilometers is not long.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What rivers in Wulstershire are not long?","answer":"River Elsuir, River Giffeleney, River Wulstershire"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition","negation"]}
{"theory":"River Giffeleney is a river in Wulstershire. River Wulstershire is a river in the state of Wulstershire. River Elsuir is a river in Wulstershire. The length of River Giffeleney is 413 kilometers. The length of River Wulstershire is 830 kilometers. The length of River Elsuir is 207 kilometers. Every river that is shorter than 650 kilometers is not long.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What rivers in Wulstershire are not long?","answer":"River Elsuir, River Giffeleney"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition","negation"]}
{"theory":"River Giffeleney is a river in Wulstershire. River Wulstershire is a river in the state of Wulstershire. River Elsuir is a river in Wulstershire. The length of River Giffeleney is 413 kilometers. The length of River Wulstershire is 830 kilometers. The length of River Elsuir is 207 kilometers. Every river that is shorter than 798.2 kilometers is not long.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What rivers in Wulstershire are not long?","answer":"River Elsuir, River Giffeleney"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition","negation"]}
{"theory":"River Giffeleney is a river in Wulstershire. River Wulstershire is a river in the state of Wulstershire. River Elsuir is a river in Wulstershire. The length of River Giffeleney is 413 kilometers. The length of River Wulstershire is 830 kilometers. The length of River Elsuir is 207 kilometers. Every river that is shorter than 100 kilometers is not long.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What rivers in Wulstershire are not long?","answer":""}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition","negation"]}
{"theory":"Every city is in one state. Kangoyaken is a state in Gyoshoru. Senkuoka is a state in Gyoshoru. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken?","answer":"210392"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"Every city is in one state. Kangoyaken is a state in Gyoshoru. Senkuoka is a state in Gyoshoru. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka?","answer":"210390"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"Every city is in one state. Kangoyaken is a state in Gyoshoru. Senkuoka is a state in Gyoshoru. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 210392. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 210392. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 210392. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 210392. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 210392. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken?","answer":"210392"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"Every city is in one state. Kangoyaken is a state in Gyoshoru. Senkuoka is a state in Gyoshoru. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 13. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 192. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 21. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 4. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 81. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 2139. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 2. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 20. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken?","answer":"21"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"Every city is in one state. Kangoyaken is a state in Gyoshoru. Senkuoka is a state in Gyoshoru. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 13. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 192. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 21. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 4. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 81. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 2139. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 2. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 20. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka?","answer":"20"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"If the number of people living in X is Y then the population of X is Y. Every city is in one state. Kangoyaken is a state in Gyoshoru. Senkuoka is a state in Gyoshoru. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The number of people living in Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken?","answer":"210392"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"If the number of people living in X is Y then the population of X is Y. Every city is in one state. Kangoyaken is a state in Gyoshoru. Senkuoka is a state in Gyoshoru. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The number of people living in Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka?","answer":"210390"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"If the number of people living in X is Y then the population of X is Y. Every city is in one state. Kangoyaken is a state in Gyoshoru. Senkuoka is a state in Gyoshoru. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 210392. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 210392. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The number of people living in Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 210392. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 210392. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 210392. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken?","answer":"210392"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"If the number of people living in X is Y then the population of X is Y. Every city is in one state. Kangoyaken is a state in Gyoshoru. Senkuoka is a state in Gyoshoru. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 13. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 192. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The number of people living in Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 21. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 4. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 81. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 2139. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 2. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 20. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken?","answer":"21"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"If the number of people living in X is Y then the population of X is Y. Every city is in one state. Kangoyaken is a state in Gyoshoru. Senkuoka is a state in Gyoshoru. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 13. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 192. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The number of people living in Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 21. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 4. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 81. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 2139. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 2. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 20. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka?","answer":"20"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. Timbuqt is a state in Mofubali. There are 4 states in Mofubali. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Timbuqt is 29103276. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. The population of Mofubali is 571390214.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which state has the greatest population?","answer":"Timbuqt"}},"flags":["superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. Timbuqt is a state in Mofubali. There are 4 states in Mofubali. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Timbuqt is 2910327. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. The population of Mofubali is 571390214.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which state has the greatest population?","answer":"Bolurofi"}},"flags":["superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. Timbuqt is a state in Mofubali. There are 4 states in Mofubali. The population of Efanangole is 14208920. The population of Timbuqt is 2910327. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. The population of Mofubali is 571390214.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which state has the greatest population?","answer":"Efanangole"}},"flags":["superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. Timbuqt is a state in Mofubali. There are 4 states in Mofubali. The population of Efanangole is 142. The population of Timbuqt is 2910. The population of Bolurofi is 902. The population of Kolufori is 81. The population of Mofubali is 57139.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which state has the greatest population?","answer":"Timbuqt"}},"flags":["superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. Timbuqt is a state in Mofubali. There are 4 states in Mofubali. The population of Efanangole is 142. The population of Timbuqt is 291. The population of Bolurofi is 902. The population of Kolufori is 81. The population of Mofubali is 57139.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which state has the greatest population?","answer":"Bolurofi"}},"flags":["superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. Timbuqt is a state in Mofubali. There are 4 states in Mofubali. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Timbuqt is 29103276. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. The population of Mofubali is 571390214.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which state has the least population?","answer":"Kolufori"}},"flags":["superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. Timbuqt is a state in Mofubali. There are 4 states in Mofubali. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Timbuqt is 2910327. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. The population of Mofubali is 571390214.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which state has the least population?","answer":"Kolufori"}},"flags":["superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. Timbuqt is a state in Mofubali. There are 4 states in Mofubali. The population of Efanangole is 14208920. The population of Timbuqt is 2910327. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. The population of Mofubali is 571390214.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which state has the least population?","answer":"Kolufori"}},"flags":["superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. Timbuqt is a state in Mofubali. There are 4 states in Mofubali. The population of Efanangole is 142. The population of Timbuqt is 2910. The population of Bolurofi is 902. The population of Kolufori is 81. The population of Mofubali is 57139.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which state has the least population?","answer":"Kolufori"}},"flags":["superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. Timbuqt is a state in Mofubali. There are 4 states in Mofubali. The population of Efanangole is 142. The population of Timbuqt is 291. The population of Bolurofi is 902. The population of Kolufori is 81. The population of Mofubali is 57139.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which state has the least population?","answer":"Kolufori"}},"flags":["superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka. If the population of X is greater than 150000, X is major.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the major cities in Kangoyaken?","answer":"Dogayashi, Kagenegawa, Kyoukashino"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka. If the population of X is greater than 250000, X is major.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the major cities in Kangoyaken?","answer":"Dogayashi, Kagenegawa"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka. If the population of X is greater than 1000000, X is major.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the major cities in Kangoyaken?","answer":"Dogayashi"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka. If the population of X is greater than 100000, X is major.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the major cities in Kangoyaken?","answer":"Dogayashi, Kagenegawa, Koruhashi, Kyoukashino"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka. If the population of X is greater than 20000, X is major.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the major cities in Kangoyaken?","answer":"Agarikoshi, Dogayashi, Kagenegawa, Koruhashi, Kyoukashino"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka. If the population of X is less than 150000, X is not major.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What cities in Kangoyaken are not major?","answer":"Agarikoshi, Koruhashi"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition","negation"]}
{"theory":"Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka. If the population of X is less than 250000, X is not major.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What cities in Kangoyaken are not major?","answer":"Agarikoshi, Koruhashi, Kyoukashino"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition","negation"]}
{"theory":"Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka. If the population of X is less than 1000000, X is not major.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What cities in Kangoyaken are not major?","answer":"Agarikoshi, Kagenegawa, Koruhashi, Kyoukashino"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition","negation"]}
{"theory":"Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka. If the population of X is less than 100000, X is not major.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What cities in Kangoyaken are not major?","answer":"Agarikoshi"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition","negation"]}
{"theory":"Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka. If the population of X is less than 20000, X is not major.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What cities in Kangoyaken are not major?","answer":""}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition","negation"]}
{"theory":"Kangoyaken is a state in Gyoshoru. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Senkuoka is a state in Gyoshoru. There are 2 states. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. If the population of X is greater than 150000, X is major.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which state has the most major cities?","answer":"Kangoyaken"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition","counting","superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Kangoyaken is a state in Gyoshoru. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Senkuoka is a state in Gyoshoru. There are 2 states. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. If the population of X is greater than 200000, X is major.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which state has the most major cities?","answer":"Kangoyaken"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition","counting","superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Kangoyaken is a state in Gyoshoru. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Senkuoka is a state in Gyoshoru. There are 2 states. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. If the population of X is greater than 10000000, X is major.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which state has the most major cities?","answer":"Senkuoka"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition","counting","superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Kangoyaken is a state in Gyoshoru. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Senkuoka is a state in Gyoshoru. There are 2 states. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. If the population of X is greater than 15000000, X is major.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which state has the most major cities?","answer":"Senkuoka"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition","counting","superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Kangoyaken is a state in Gyoshoru. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Senkuoka is a state in Gyoshoru. There are 2 states. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. If the population of X is greater than 20000000, X is major.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which state has the most major cities?","answer":"Senkuoka"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition","counting","superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Kangoyaken is a state in Gyoshoru. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Senkuoka is a state in Gyoshoru. There are 2 states. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. If the population of X is greater than 150000, X is major.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which state has the fewest major cities?","answer":"Senkuoka"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition","counting","superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Kangoyaken is a state in Gyoshoru. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Senkuoka is a state in Gyoshoru. There are 2 states. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. If the population of X is greater than 200000, X is major.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which state has the fewest major cities?","answer":"Senkuoka"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition","counting","superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Kangoyaken is a state in Gyoshoru. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Senkuoka is a state in Gyoshoru. There are 2 states. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. If the population of X is greater than 10000000, X is major.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which state has the fewest major cities?","answer":"Kangoyaken"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition","counting","superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Kangoyaken is a state in Gyoshoru. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Senkuoka is a state in Gyoshoru. There are 2 states. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. If the population of X is greater than 15000000, X is major.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which state has the fewest major cities?","answer":"Kangoyaken"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition","counting","superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Kangoyaken is a state in Gyoshoru. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Senkuoka is a state in Gyoshoru. There are 2 states. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. If the population of X is greater than 20000000, X is major.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which state has the fewest major cities?","answer":"Kangoyaken"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition","counting","superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. There are 7 provinces.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What provinces border the province with the smallest area?","answer":"Bripetrsk, Fordgorod, Getarovo, Voronolga"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","superlative"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 3149000 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. There are 7 provinces.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What provinces border the province with the smallest area?","answer":"Fordgorod, Galininograd, Getarovo"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","superlative"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 102390 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. There are 7 provinces.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What provinces border the province with the smallest area?","answer":"Getarovo, Voronolga"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","superlative"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 67130 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. There are 7 provinces.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What provinces border the province with the smallest area?","answer":"Abdorostan, Bripetrsk, Galininograd"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","superlative"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 91230 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. There are 7 provinces.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What provinces border the province with the smallest area?","answer":"Fordgorod, Voronolga"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","superlative"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. There are 7 provinces. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 6712302. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What provinces border the province with the smallest area?","answer":"Bripetrsk, Fordgorod, Getarovo, Voronolga"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","superlative"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 3149000 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. There are 7 provinces. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 6712302. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What provinces border the province with the smallest area?","answer":"Fordgorod, Galininograd, Getarovo"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","superlative"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 102390 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. There are 7 provinces. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 6712302. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What provinces border the province with the smallest area?","answer":"Getarovo, Voronolga"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","superlative"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 67130 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. There are 7 provinces. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 6712302. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What provinces border the province with the smallest area?","answer":"Abdorostan, Bripetrsk, Galininograd"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","superlative"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 91230 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. There are 7 provinces. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 6712302. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What provinces border the province with the smallest area?","answer":"Fordgorod, Voronolga"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","superlative"]}
{"theory":"River Giffeleney is a river in Wulstershire. River Wulstershire is a river in the state of Wulstershire. River Elsuir is a river in Wulstershire. The length of River Giffeleney is 413 kilometers. The length of River Wulstershire is 830 kilometers. The length of River Elsuir is 207 kilometers. Every river that is longer than 400 kilometers is not short.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What rivers in Wulstershire are not short?","answer":"River Giffeleney, River Wulstershire"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition","negation"]}
{"theory":"River Giffeleney is a river in Wulstershire. River Wulstershire is a river in the state of Wulstershire. River Elsuir is a river in Wulstershire. The length of River Giffeleney is 413 kilometers. The length of River Wulstershire is 830 kilometers. The length of River Elsuir is 207 kilometers. Every river that is longer than 1000 kilometers is not short.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What rivers in Wulstershire are not short?","answer":""}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition","negation"]}
{"theory":"River Giffeleney is a river in Wulstershire. River Wulstershire is a river in the state of Wulstershire. River Elsuir is a river in Wulstershire. The length of River Giffeleney is 413 kilometers. The length of River Wulstershire is 830 kilometers. The length of River Elsuir is 207 kilometers. Every river that is longer than 650 kilometers is not short.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What rivers in Wulstershire are not short?","answer":"River Wulstershire"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition","negation"]}
{"theory":"River Giffeleney is a river in Wulstershire. River Wulstershire is a river in the state of Wulstershire. River Elsuir is a river in Wulstershire. The length of River Giffeleney is 413 kilometers. The length of River Wulstershire is 830 kilometers. The length of River Elsuir is 207 kilometers. Every river that is longer than 798.2 kilometers is not short.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What rivers in Wulstershire are not short?","answer":"River Wulstershire"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition","negation"]}
{"theory":"River Giffeleney is a river in Wulstershire. River Wulstershire is a river in the state of Wulstershire. River Elsuir is a river in Wulstershire. The length of River Giffeleney is 413 kilometers. The length of River Wulstershire is 830 kilometers. The length of River Elsuir is 207 kilometers. Every river that is longer than 100 kilometers is not short.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What rivers in Wulstershire are not short?","answer":"River Elsuir, River Giffeleney, River Wulstershire"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition","negation"]}
{"theory":"River Giffeleney is a river in Wulstershire. River Wulstershire is a river in the state of Wulstershire. River Elsuir is a river in Wulstershire. The length of River Giffeleney is 413 kilometers. The length of River Wulstershire is 830 kilometers. The length of River Elsuir is 207 kilometers. Every river that is shorter than 400 kilometers is short.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the short rivers in Wulstershire?","answer":"River Elsuir"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"River Giffeleney is a river in Wulstershire. River Wulstershire is a river in the state of Wulstershire. River Elsuir is a river in Wulstershire. The length of River Giffeleney is 413 kilometers. The length of River Wulstershire is 830 kilometers. The length of River Elsuir is 207 kilometers. Every river that is shorter than 1000 kilometers is short.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the short rivers in Wulstershire?","answer":"River Elsuir, River Giffeleney, River Wulstershire"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"River Giffeleney is a river in Wulstershire. River Wulstershire is a river in the state of Wulstershire. River Elsuir is a river in Wulstershire. The length of River Giffeleney is 413 kilometers. The length of River Wulstershire is 830 kilometers. The length of River Elsuir is 207 kilometers. Every river that is shorter than 650 kilometers is short.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the short rivers in Wulstershire?","answer":"River Elsuir, River Giffeleney"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"River Giffeleney is a river in Wulstershire. River Wulstershire is a river in the state of Wulstershire. River Elsuir is a river in Wulstershire. The length of River Giffeleney is 413 kilometers. The length of River Wulstershire is 830 kilometers. The length of River Elsuir is 207 kilometers. Every river that is shorter than 798.2 kilometers is short.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the short rivers in Wulstershire?","answer":"River Elsuir, River Giffeleney"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"River Giffeleney is a river in Wulstershire. River Wulstershire is a river in the state of Wulstershire. River Elsuir is a river in Wulstershire. The length of River Giffeleney is 413 kilometers. The length of River Wulstershire is 830 kilometers. The length of River Elsuir is 207 kilometers. Every river that is shorter than 100 kilometers is short.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the short rivers in Wulstershire?","answer":""}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 6712302. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What provinces border the most populous province?","answer":"Bripetrsk, Galininograd, Puotorsk, Voronolga"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","superlative"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 6712302. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 2291206. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What provinces border the most populous province?","answer":"Abdorostan, Galininograd, Getarovo, Fordgorod, Puotorsk"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","superlative"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 1017829. The population of Abdorostan is 6712302. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 2291206. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What provinces border the most populous province?","answer":"Abdorostan, Bripetrsk, Galininograd"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","superlative"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 6712302. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 41290800. There are 7 provinces.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What provinces border the most populous province?","answer":"Fordgorod, Galininograd, Getarovo"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","superlative"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What provinces border the most populous province?","answer":"Fordgorod, Voronolga"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","superlative"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 6712302. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What provinces border the most populous province?","answer":"Bripetrsk, Galininograd, Puotorsk, Voronolga"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","superlative"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 6712302. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 2291206. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What provinces border the most populous province?","answer":"Abdorostan, Galininograd, Getarovo, Fordgorod, Puotorsk"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","superlative"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 1017829. The population of Abdorostan is 6712302. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 2291206. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What provinces border the most populous province?","answer":"Abdorostan, Bripetrsk, Galininograd"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","superlative"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 6712302. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 41290800. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What provinces border the most populous province?","answer":"Fordgorod, Galininograd, Getarovo"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","superlative"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What provinces border the most populous province?","answer":"Fordgorod, Voronolga"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","superlative"]}
{"theory":"Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. Mbalam is a city in Bolurofi. Marba Adama is the capital city of Efanangole. Alharwassa is the capital city of Bolurofi. Sharhamane is a city in Efanangole. Saare Daewa is a city in Bolurofi. The population of Marba Adama is 7182032. The population of Alharwassa is 173201. The population of Sharhamane is 4192302. The population of Saare Daewa is 86110. Gondarbawa is a city in Efanangole. The population of Gondarbawa is 398184. There are 3 cities in Efanangole. The population of Mbalam is 6132027. There are 3 cities in Bolurofi.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the largest city in Efanangole?","answer":"Marba Adama"}},"flags":["superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. Mbalam is a city in Bolurofi. Marba Adama is the capital city of Efanangole. Alharwassa is the capital city of Bolurofi. Sharhamane is a city in Efanangole. Saare Daewa is a city in Bolurofi. The population of Marba Adama is 71820. The population of Alharwassa is 173201. The population of Sharhamane is 4192302. The population of Saare Daewa is 86110. Gondarbawa is a city in Efanangole. The population of Gondarbawa is 398184. There are 3 cities in Efanangole. The population of Mbalam is 6132027. There are 3 cities in Bolurofi.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the largest city in Efanangole?","answer":"Sharhamane"}},"flags":["superlative", "lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. Mbalam is a city in Bolurofi. Marba Adama is the capital city of Efanangole. Alharwassa is the capital city of Bolurofi. Sharhamane is a city in Efanangole. Saare Daewa is a city in Bolurofi. The population of Marba Adama is 7182032. The population of Alharwassa is 173201. The population of Sharhamane is 4192302. The population of Saare Daewa is 86110219. Gondarbawa is a city in Efanangole. The population of Gondarbawa is 3981840. There are 3 cities in Efanangole. The population of Mbalam is 6132027. There are 3 cities in Bolurofi.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the largest city in Efanangole?","answer":"Marba Adama"}},"flags":["superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. Mbalam is a city in Bolurofi. Marba Adama is the capital city of Efanangole. Alharwassa is the capital city of Bolurofi. Sharhamane is a city in Efanangole. Saare Daewa is a city in Bolurofi. The population of Marba Adama is 7. The population of Alharwassa is 17. The population of Sharhamane is 419. The population of Saare Daewa is 8. Gondarbawa is a city in Efanangole. The population of Gondarbawa is 39. There are 3 cities in Efanangole. The population of Mbalam is 613. There are 3 cities in Bolurofi.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the largest city in Efanangole?","answer":"Sharhamane"}},"flags":["superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. Mbalam is a city in Bolurofi. Marba Adama is the capital city of Efanangole. Alharwassa is the capital city of Bolurofi. Sharhamane is a city in Efanangole. Saare Daewa is a city in Bolurofi. The population of Marba Adama is 718. The population of Alharwassa is 17. The population of Sharhamane is 419. The population of Saare Daewa is 8611. Gondarbawa is a city in Efanangole. The population of Gondarbawa is 398. There are 3 cities in Efanangole. The population of Mbalam is 613. There are 3 cities in Bolurofi.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the largest city in Efanangole?","answer":"Marba Adama"}},"flags":["superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. Mbalam is a city in Bolurofi. Marba Adama is the capital city of Efanangole. Alharwassa is the capital city of Bolurofi. Sharhamane is a city in Efanangole. Saare Daewa is a city in Bolurofi. The population of Marba Adama is 7182032. The population of Alharwassa is 173201. The population of Sharhamane is 4192302. The population of Saare Daewa is 86110. Gondarbawa is a city in Efanangole. The population of Gondarbawa is 398184. There are 3 cities in Efanangole. The population of Mbalam is 6132027. There are 3 cities in Bolurofi.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the smallest city in Efanangole?","answer":"Gondarbawa"}},"flags":["superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. Mbalam is a city in Bolurofi. Marba Adama is the capital city of Efanangole. Alharwassa is the capital city of Bolurofi. Sharhamane is a city in Efanangole. Saare Daewa is a city in Bolurofi. The population of Marba Adama is 71820. The population of Alharwassa is 173201. The population of Sharhamane is 4192302. The population of Saare Daewa is 86110. Gondarbawa is a city in Efanangole. The population of Gondarbawa is 398184. There are 3 cities in Efanangole. The population of Mbalam is 6132027. There are 3 cities in Bolurofi.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the smallest city in Efanangole?","answer":"Marba Adama"}},"flags":["superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. Mbalam is a city in Bolurofi. Marba Adama is the capital city of Efanangole. Alharwassa is the capital city of Bolurofi. Sharhamane is a city in Efanangole. Saare Daewa is a city in Bolurofi. The population of Marba Adama is 7182032. The population of Alharwassa is 173201. The population of Sharhamane is 4192302. The population of Saare Daewa is 86110219. Gondarbawa is a city in Efanangole. The population of Gondarbawa is 3981840. There are 3 cities in Efanangole. The population of Mbalam is 6132027. There are 3 cities in Bolurofi.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the smallest city in Efanangole?","answer":"Gondarbawa"}},"flags":["superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. Mbalam is a city in Bolurofi. Marba Adama is the capital city of Efanangole. Alharwassa is the capital city of Bolurofi. Sharhamane is a city in Efanangole. Saare Daewa is a city in Bolurofi. The population of Marba Adama is 7. The population of Alharwassa is 17. The population of Sharhamane is 419. The population of Saare Daewa is 8. Gondarbawa is a city in Efanangole. The population of Gondarbawa is 39. There are 3 cities in Efanangole. The population of Mbalam is 613. There are 3 cities in Bolurofi.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the smallest city in Efanangole?","answer":"Marba Adama"}},"flags":["superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. Mbalam is a city in Bolurofi. Marba Adama is the capital city of Efanangole. Alharwassa is the capital city of Bolurofi. Sharhamane is a city in Efanangole. Saare Daewa is a city in Bolurofi. The population of Marba Adama is 718. The population of Alharwassa is 17. The population of Sharhamane is 419. The population of Saare Daewa is 8611. Gondarbawa is a city in Efanangole. The population of Gondarbawa is 398. There are 3 cities in Efanangole. The population of Mbalam is 613. There are 3 cities in Bolurofi.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the smallest city in Efanangole?","answer":"Gondarbawa"}},"flags":["superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"If the population of X is Y, then the number of people living in X is Y. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. Mbalam is a city in Bolurofi. Marba Adama is the capital city of Efanangole. Alharwassa is the capital city of Bolurofi. Sharhamane is a city in Efanangole. Saare Daewa is a city in Bolurofi. The population of Marba Adama is 7182032. The population of Alharwassa is 173201. The population of Sharhamane is 4192302. The population of Saare Daewa is 86110. Gondarbawa is a city in Efanangole. The population of Gondarbawa is 398184. There are 3 cities in Efanangole. The population of Mbalam is 6132027. There are 3 cities in Bolurofi.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"How many people live in the biggest city in Efanangole?","answer":"7182032"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"If the population of X is Y, then the number of people living in X is Y. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. Mbalam is a city in Bolurofi. Marba Adama is the capital city of Efanangole. Alharwassa is the capital city of Bolurofi. Sharhamane is a city in Efanangole. Saare Daewa is a city in Bolurofi. The population of Marba Adama is 71820. The population of Alharwassa is 173201. The population of Sharhamane is 4192302. The population of Saare Daewa is 86110. Gondarbawa is a city in Efanangole. The population of Gondarbawa is 398184. There are 3 cities in Efanangole. The population of Mbalam is 6132027. There are 3 cities in Bolurofi.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"How many people live in the biggest city in Efanangole?","answer":"4192302"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"If the population of X is Y, then the number of people living in X is Y. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. Mbalam is a city in Bolurofi. Marba Adama is the capital city of Efanangole. Alharwassa is the capital city of Bolurofi. Sharhamane is a city in Efanangole. Saare Daewa is a city in Bolurofi. The population of Marba Adama is 7182032. The population of Alharwassa is 173201. The population of Sharhamane is 4192302. The population of Saare Daewa is 86110219. Gondarbawa is a city in Efanangole. The population of Gondarbawa is 3981840. There are 3 cities in Efanangole. The population of Mbalam is 6132027. There are 3 cities in Bolurofi.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"How many people live in the biggest city in Efanangole?","answer":"7182032"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"If the population of X is Y, then the number of people living in X is Y. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. Mbalam is a city in Bolurofi. Marba Adama is the capital city of Efanangole. Alharwassa is the capital city of Bolurofi. Sharhamane is a city in Efanangole. Saare Daewa is a city in Bolurofi. The population of Marba Adama is 7. The population of Alharwassa is 17. The population of Sharhamane is 419. The population of Saare Daewa is 8. Gondarbawa is a city in Efanangole. The population of Gondarbawa is 39. There are 3 cities in Efanangole. The population of Mbalam is 613. There are 3 cities in Bolurofi.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"How many people live in the biggest city in Efanangole?","answer":"419"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"If the population of X is Y, then the number of people living in X is Y. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. Mbalam is a city in Bolurofi. Marba Adama is the capital city of Efanangole. Alharwassa is the capital city of Bolurofi. Sharhamane is a city in Efanangole. Saare Daewa is a city in Bolurofi. The population of Marba Adama is 718. The population of Alharwassa is 17. The population of Sharhamane is 419. The population of Saare Daewa is 8611. Gondarbawa is a city in Efanangole. The population of Gondarbawa is 398. There are 3 cities in Efanangole. The population of Mbalam is 613. There are 3 cities in Bolurofi.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"How many people live in the biggest city in Efanangole?","answer":"718"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"If the population of X is Y, then the number of people living in X is Y. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. Mbalam is a city in Bolurofi. Marba Adama is the capital city of Efanangole. Alharwassa is the capital city of Bolurofi. Sharhamane is a city in Efanangole. Saare Daewa is a city in Bolurofi. The population of Marba Adama is 7182032. The population of Alharwassa is 173201. The population of Sharhamane is 4192302. The population of Saare Daewa is 86110. Gondarbawa is a city in Efanangole. The population of Gondarbawa is 398184. There are 3 cities in Efanangole. The population of Mbalam is 6132027. There are 3 cities in Bolurofi.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"How many people live in the smallest city in Efanangole?","answer":"398184"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"If the population of X is Y, then the number of people living in X is Y. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. Mbalam is a city in Bolurofi. Marba Adama is the capital city of Efanangole. Alharwassa is the capital city of Bolurofi. Sharhamane is a city in Efanangole. Saare Daewa is a city in Bolurofi. The population of Marba Adama is 71820. The population of Alharwassa is 173201. The population of Sharhamane is 4192302. The population of Saare Daewa is 86110. Gondarbawa is a city in Efanangole. The population of Gondarbawa is 398184. There are 3 cities in Efanangole. The population of Mbalam is 6132027. There are 3 cities in Bolurofi.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"How many people live in the smallest city in Efanangole?","answer":"71820"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"If the population of X is Y, then the number of people living in X is Y. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. Mbalam is a city in Bolurofi. Marba Adama is the capital city of Efanangole. Alharwassa is the capital city of Bolurofi. Sharhamane is a city in Efanangole. Saare Daewa is a city in Bolurofi. The population of Marba Adama is 7182032. The population of Alharwassa is 173201. The population of Sharhamane is 4192302. The population of Saare Daewa is 86110219. Gondarbawa is a city in Efanangole. The population of Gondarbawa is 3981840. There are 3 cities in Efanangole. The population of Mbalam is 6132027. There are 3 cities in Bolurofi.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"How many people live in the smallest city in Efanangole?","answer":"3981840"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"If the population of X is Y, then the number of people living in X is Y. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. Mbalam is a city in Bolurofi. Marba Adama is the capital city of Efanangole. Alharwassa is the capital city of Bolurofi. Sharhamane is a city in Efanangole. Saare Daewa is a city in Bolurofi. The population of Marba Adama is 7. The population of Alharwassa is 17. The population of Sharhamane is 419. The population of Saare Daewa is 8. Gondarbawa is a city in Efanangole. The population of Gondarbawa is 39. There are 3 cities in Efanangole. The population of Mbalam is 613. There are 3 cities in Bolurofi.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"How many people live in the smallest city in Efanangole?","answer":"7"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"If the population of X is Y, then the number of people living in X is Y. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. Mbalam is a city in Bolurofi. Marba Adama is the capital city of Efanangole. Alharwassa is the capital city of Bolurofi. Sharhamane is a city in Efanangole. Saare Daewa is a city in Bolurofi. The population of Marba Adama is 718. The population of Alharwassa is 17. The population of Sharhamane is 419. The population of Saare Daewa is 8611. Gondarbawa is a city in Efanangole. The population of Gondarbawa is 398. There are 3 cities in Efanangole. The population of Mbalam is 613. There are 3 cities in Bolurofi.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"How many people live in the smallest city in Efanangole?","answer":"398"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"River Giffeleney is a river in Wulstershire. River Wulstershire is a river in the state of Wulstershire. River Elsuir is a river in Wulstershire. The length of River Giffeleney is 413 kilometers. The length of River Wulstershire is 830 kilometers. The length of River Elsuir is 207 kilometers. Every river that is longer than 400 kilometers is not a tributary.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What rivers in Wulstershire are not tributaries?","answer":"River Giffeleney, River Wulstershire"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition","negation"]}
{"theory":"River Giffeleney is a river in Wulstershire. River Wulstershire is a river in the state of Wulstershire. River Elsuir is a river in Wulstershire. The length of River Giffeleney is 413 kilometers. The length of River Wulstershire is 830 kilometers. The length of River Elsuir is 207 kilometers. Every river that is longer than 1000 kilometers is not a tributary.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What rivers in Wulstershire are not tributaries?","answer":""}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition","negation"]}
{"theory":"River Giffeleney is a river in Wulstershire. River Wulstershire is a river in the state of Wulstershire. River Elsuir is a river in Wulstershire. The length of River Giffeleney is 413 kilometers. The length of River Wulstershire is 830 kilometers. The length of River Elsuir is 207 kilometers. Every river that is longer than 650 kilometers is not a tributary.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What rivers in Wulstershire are not tributaries?","answer":"River Wulstershire"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition","negation"]}
{"theory":"River Giffeleney is a river in Wulstershire. River Wulstershire is a river in the state of Wulstershire. River Elsuir is a river in Wulstershire. The length of River Giffeleney is 413 kilometers. The length of River Wulstershire is 830 kilometers. The length of River Elsuir is 207 kilometers. Every river that is longer than 798.2 kilometers is not a tributary.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What rivers in Wulstershire are not tributaries?","answer":"River Wulstershire"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition","negation"]}
{"theory":"River Giffeleney is a river in Wulstershire. River Wulstershire is a river in the state of Wulstershire. River Elsuir is a river in Wulstershire. The length of River Giffeleney is 413 kilometers. The length of River Wulstershire is 830 kilometers. The length of River Elsuir is 207 kilometers. Every river that is longer than 100 kilometers is not a tributary.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What rivers in Wulstershire are not tributaries?","answer":"River Elsuir, River Giffeleney, River Wulstershire"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition","negation"]}
{"theory":"River Giffeleney is a river in Wulstershire. River Wulstershire is a river in the state of Wulstershire. River Elsuir is a river in Wulstershire. The length of River Giffeleney is 413 kilometers. The length of River Wulstershire is 830 kilometers. The length of River Elsuir is 207 kilometers. Every river that is shorter than 400 kilometers is a tributary.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the tributaries in Wulstershire?","answer":"River Elsuir"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"River Giffeleney is a river in Wulstershire. River Wulstershire is a river in the state of Wulstershire. River Elsuir is a river in Wulstershire. The length of River Giffeleney is 413 kilometers. The length of River Wulstershire is 830 kilometers. The length of River Elsuir is 207 kilometers. Every river that is shorter than 1000 kilometers is a tributary.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the tributaries in Wulstershire?","answer":"River Elsuir, River Giffeleney, River Wulstershire"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"River Giffeleney is a river in Wulstershire. River Wulstershire is a river in the state of Wulstershire. River Elsuir is a river in Wulstershire. The length of River Giffeleney is 413 kilometers. The length of River Wulstershire is 830 kilometers. The length of River Elsuir is 207 kilometers. Every river that is shorter than 650 kilometers is a tributary.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the tributaries in Wulstershire?","answer":"River Elsuir, River Giffeleney"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"River Giffeleney is a river in Wulstershire. River Wulstershire is a river in the state of Wulstershire. River Elsuir is a river in Wulstershire. The length of River Giffeleney is 413 kilometers. The length of River Wulstershire is 830 kilometers. The length of River Elsuir is 207 kilometers. Every river that is shorter than 798.2 kilometers is a tributary.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the tributaries in Wulstershire?","answer":"River Elsuir, River Giffeleney"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"River Giffeleney is a river in Wulstershire. River Wulstershire is a river in the state of Wulstershire. River Elsuir is a river in Wulstershire. The length of River Giffeleney is 413 kilometers. The length of River Wulstershire is 830 kilometers. The length of River Elsuir is 207 kilometers. Every river that is shorter than 100 kilometers is a tributary.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the tributaries in Wulstershire?","answer":""}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka. If the population of X is greater than 150000, X is a metropolis.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the metropolises in Kangoyaken?","answer":"Dogayashi, Kagenegawa, Kyoukashino"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka. If the population of X is greater than 250000, X is a metropolis.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the metropolises in Kangoyaken?","answer":"Dogayashi, Kagenegawa"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka. If the population of X is greater than 1000000, X is a metropolis.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the metropolises in Kangoyaken?","answer":"Dogayashi"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka. If the population of X is greater than 100000, X is a metropolis.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the metropolises in Kangoyaken?","answer":"Dogayashi, Kagenegawa, Koruhashi, Kyoukashino"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka. If the population of X is greater than 20000, X is a metropolis.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the metropolises in Kangoyaken?","answer":"Agarikoshi, Dogayashi, Kagenegawa, Koruhashi, Kyoukashino"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka. If the population of X is less than 150000, X is not a metropolis.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What cities in Kangoyaken are not metropolises?","answer":"Agarikoshi, Koruhashi"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition","negation"]}
{"theory":"Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka. If the population of X is less than 250000, X is not a metropolis.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What cities in Kangoyaken are not metropolises?","answer":"Agarikoshi, Koruhashi, Kyoukashino"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition","negation"]}
{"theory":"Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka. If the population of X is less than 1000000, X is not a metropolis.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What cities in Kangoyaken are not metropolises?","answer":"Agarikoshi, Kagenegawa, Koruhashi, Kyoukashino"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition","negation"]}
{"theory":"Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka. If the population of X is less than 100000, X is not a metropolis.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What cities in Kangoyaken are not metropolises?","answer":"Agarikoshi"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition","negation"]}
{"theory":"Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka. If the population of X is less than 20000, X is not a metropolis.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What cities in Kangoyaken are not metropolises?","answer":""}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition","negation"]}
{"theory":"Kangoyaken is a state in Gyoshoru. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Senkuoka is a state in Gyoshoru. There are 2 states. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. If the population of X is greater than 150000, X is a metropolis.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which state has the most metropolises?","answer":"Kangoyaken"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition","counting","superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Kangoyaken is a state in Gyoshoru. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Senkuoka is a state in Gyoshoru. There are 2 states. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. If the population of X is greater than 200000, X is a metropolis.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which state has the most metropolises?","answer":"Kangoyaken"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition","counting","superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Kangoyaken is a state in Gyoshoru. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Senkuoka is a state in Gyoshoru. There are 2 states. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. If the population of X is greater than 10000000, X is a metropolis.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which state has the most metropolises?","answer":"Senkuoka"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition","counting","superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Kangoyaken is a state in Gyoshoru. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Senkuoka is a state in Gyoshoru. There are 2 states. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. If the population of X is greater than 15000000, X is a metropolis.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which state has the most metropolises?","answer":"Senkuoka"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition","counting","superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Kangoyaken is a state in Gyoshoru. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Senkuoka is a state in Gyoshoru. There are 2 states. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. If the population of X is greater than 20000000, X is a metropolis.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which state has the most metropolises?","answer":"Senkuoka"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition","counting","superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Kangoyaken is a state in Gyoshoru. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Senkuoka is a state in Gyoshoru. There are 2 states. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. If the population of X is greater than 150000, X is a metropolis.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which state has the fewest metropolises?","answer":"Senkuoka"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition","counting","superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Kangoyaken is a state in Gyoshoru. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Senkuoka is a state in Gyoshoru. There are 2 states. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. If the population of X is greater than 200000, X is a metropolis.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which state has the fewest metropolises?","answer":"Senkuoka"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition","counting","superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Kangoyaken is a state in Gyoshoru. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Senkuoka is a state in Gyoshoru. There are 2 states. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. If the population of X is greater than 10000000, X is a metropolis.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which state has the fewest metropolises?","answer":"Kangoyaken"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition","counting","superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Kangoyaken is a state in Gyoshoru. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Senkuoka is a state in Gyoshoru. There are 2 states. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. If the population of X is greater than 15000000, X is a metropolis.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which state has the fewest metropolises?","answer":"Kangoyaken"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition","counting","superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Kangoyaken is a state in Gyoshoru. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Senkuoka is a state in Gyoshoru. There are 2 states. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. If the population of X is greater than 20000000, X is a metropolis.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which state has the fewest metropolises?","answer":"Kangoyaken"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition","counting","superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. Mbalam is a city in Bolurofi. Marba Adama is the capital city of Efanangole. Alharwassa is the capital city of Bolurofi. Sharhamane is a city in Efanangole. Saare Daewa is a city in Bolurofi. The population of Marba Adama is 7182032. The population of Alharwassa is 173201. The population of Sharhamane is 4192302. The population of Saare Daewa is 86110. Gondarbawa is a city in Efanangole. The population of Gondarbawa is 398184. There are 3 cities not in Bolurofi. The population of Mbalam is 6132027. There are 3 cities in Bolurofi.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the largest city not in Bolurofi?","answer":"Marba Adama"}},"flags":["negation","superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. Mbalam is a city in Bolurofi. Marba Adama is the capital city of Efanangole. Alharwassa is the capital city of Bolurofi. Sharhamane is a city in Efanangole. Saare Daewa is a city in Bolurofi. The population of Marba Adama is 71820. The population of Alharwassa is 173201. The population of Sharhamane is 4192302. The population of Saare Daewa is 86110. Gondarbawa is a city in Efanangole. The population of Gondarbawa is 398184. There are 3 cities not in Bolurofi. The population of Mbalam is 6132027. There are 3 cities in Bolurofi.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the largest city not in Bolurofi?","answer":"Sharhamane"}},"flags":["negation","superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. Mbalam is a city in Bolurofi. Marba Adama is the capital city of Efanangole. Alharwassa is the capital city of Bolurofi. Sharhamane is a city in Efanangole. Saare Daewa is a city in Bolurofi. The population of Marba Adama is 7182032. The population of Alharwassa is 173201. The population of Sharhamane is 4192302. The population of Saare Daewa is 86110219. Gondarbawa is a city in Efanangole. The population of Gondarbawa is 3981840. There are 3 cities not in Bolurofi. The population of Mbalam is 6132027. There are 3 cities in Bolurofi.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the largest city not in Bolurofi?","answer":"Marba Adama"}},"flags":["negation","superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. Mbalam is a city in Bolurofi. Marba Adama is the capital city of Efanangole. Alharwassa is the capital city of Bolurofi. Sharhamane is a city in Efanangole. Saare Daewa is a city in Bolurofi. The population of Marba Adama is 7. The population of Alharwassa is 17. The population of Sharhamane is 419. The population of Saare Daewa is 8. Gondarbawa is a city in Efanangole. The population of Gondarbawa is 39. There are 3 cities not in Bolurofi. The population of Mbalam is 613. There are 3 cities in Bolurofi.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the largest city not in Bolurofi?","answer":"Sharhamane"}},"flags":["negation","superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. Mbalam is a city in Bolurofi. Marba Adama is the capital city of Efanangole. Alharwassa is the capital city of Bolurofi. Sharhamane is a city in Efanangole. Saare Daewa is a city in Bolurofi. The population of Marba Adama is 718. The population of Alharwassa is 17. The population of Sharhamane is 419. The population of Saare Daewa is 8611. Gondarbawa is a city in Efanangole. The population of Gondarbawa is 398. There are 3 cities not in Bolurofi. The population of Mbalam is 613. There are 3 cities in Bolurofi.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the largest city not in Bolurofi?","answer":"Marba Adama"}},"flags":["negation","superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. Mbalam is a city in Bolurofi. Marba Adama is the capital city of Efanangole. Alharwassa is the capital city of Bolurofi. Sharhamane is a city in Efanangole. Saare Daewa is a city in Bolurofi. The population of Marba Adama is 7182032. The population of Alharwassa is 173201. The population of Sharhamane is 4192302. The population of Saare Daewa is 86110. Gondarbawa is a city in Efanangole. The population of Gondarbawa is 398184. There are 3 cities not in Bolurofi. The population of Mbalam is 6132027. There are 3 cities in Bolurofi.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the smallest city not in Bolurofi?","answer":"Gondarbawa"}},"flags":["negation","superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. Mbalam is a city in Bolurofi. Marba Adama is the capital city of Efanangole. Alharwassa is the capital city of Bolurofi. Sharhamane is a city in Efanangole. Saare Daewa is a city in Bolurofi. The population of Marba Adama is 71820. The population of Alharwassa is 173201. The population of Sharhamane is 4192302. The population of Saare Daewa is 86110. Gondarbawa is a city in Efanangole. The population of Gondarbawa is 398184. There are 3 cities not in Bolurofi. The population of Mbalam is 6132027. There are 3 cities in Bolurofi.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the smallest city not in Bolurofi?","answer":"Marba Adama"}},"flags":["negation","superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. Mbalam is a city in Bolurofi. Marba Adama is the capital city of Efanangole. Alharwassa is the capital city of Bolurofi. Sharhamane is a city in Efanangole. Saare Daewa is a city in Bolurofi. The population of Marba Adama is 7182032. The population of Alharwassa is 173201. The population of Sharhamane is 4192302. The population of Saare Daewa is 86110219. Gondarbawa is a city in Efanangole. The population of Gondarbawa is 3981840. There are 3 cities not in Bolurofi. The population of Mbalam is 6132027. There are 3 cities in Bolurofi.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the smallest city not in Bolurofi?","answer":"Gondarbawa"}},"flags":["negation","superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. Mbalam is a city in Bolurofi. Marba Adama is the capital city of Efanangole. Alharwassa is the capital city of Bolurofi. Sharhamane is a city in Efanangole. Saare Daewa is a city in Bolurofi. The population of Marba Adama is 7. The population of Alharwassa is 17. The population of Sharhamane is 419. The population of Saare Daewa is 8. Gondarbawa is a city in Efanangole. The population of Gondarbawa is 39. There are 3 cities not in Bolurofi. The population of Mbalam is 613. There are 3 cities in Bolurofi.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the smallest city not in Bolurofi?","answer":"Marba Adama"}},"flags":["negation","superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. Mbalam is a city in Bolurofi. Marba Adama is the capital city of Efanangole. Alharwassa is the capital city of Bolurofi. Sharhamane is a city in Efanangole. Saare Daewa is a city in Bolurofi. The population of Marba Adama is 718. The population of Alharwassa is 17. The population of Sharhamane is 419. The population of Saare Daewa is 8611. Gondarbawa is a city in Efanangole. The population of Gondarbawa is 398. There are 3 cities not in Bolurofi. The population of Mbalam is 613. There are 3 cities in Bolurofi.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the smallest city not in Bolurofi?","answer":"Gondarbawa"}},"flags":["negation","superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Baritolloti is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What states have cities named Baritolloti?","answer":"Grappulia, Regnobenoa"}},"flags":["lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Baritolloti is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What states have cities named Lomberona?","answer":"Regnobenoa"}},"flags":["lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Baritolloti is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What states have cities named Lomtrieste?","answer":"Bascilitina, Catardinia"}},"flags":["lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Baritolloti is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What states have cities named Albucapua?","answer":"Bascilitina"}},"flags":["lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Baritolloti is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What states have cities named Brescitabia?","answer":"Cartabitan"}},"flags":["lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Baritolloti is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. Lomberona is a city in Cartabitan.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What states have cities named Lomberona?","answer":"Cartabitan, Regnobenoa"}},"flags":["lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Baritolloti is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. Lomberona is a city in Cartabitan.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What states have cities named Veronizzia?","answer":"Cartabitan"}},"flags":["lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Baritolloti is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. Lomberona is a city in Cartabitan.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What states have cities named Baritolloti?","answer":"Grappulia, Regnobenoa"}},"flags":["lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Baritolloti is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. Lomberona is a city in Cartabitan.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What states have cities named Lomtrieste?","answer":"Bascilitina, Catardinia"}},"flags":["lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Baritolloti is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. Lomberona is a city in Cartabitan.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What states have cities named Geoturin?","answer":"Cartabitan"}},"flags":["lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Every city has one name. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Baritolloti is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What states have a city not named Baritolloti?","answer":"Bascilitina, Cartabitan"}},"flags":["negation","objective_concept_definition","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Every city has one name. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Baritolloti is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What states have a city not named Lomberona?","answer":"Bascilitina, Cartabitan, Grappulia"}},"flags":["negation","objective_concept_definition","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Every city has one name. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Baritolloti is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What states have a city not named Lomtrieste?","answer":"Grappulia, Regnobenoa"}},"flags":["negation","objective_concept_definition","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Every city has one name. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Baritolloti is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What states have a city not named Albucapua?","answer":"Cartabitan, Grappulia, Regnobenoa"}},"flags":["negation","objective_concept_definition","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Every city has one name. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Baritolloti is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What states have a city not named Brescitabia?","answer":"Bascilitina, Grappulia, Regnobenoa"}},"flags":["negation","objective_concept_definition","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Every city has one name. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Baritolloti is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. Lomberona is a city in Cartabitan.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What states have a city not named Lomberona?","answer":"Bascilitina, Grappulia"}},"flags":["negation","objective_concept_definition","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Every city has one name. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Baritolloti is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. Lomberona is a city in Cartabitan.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What states have a city not named Veronizzia?","answer":"Bascilitina, Grappulia, Regnobenoa"}},"flags":["negation","objective_concept_definition","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Every city has one name. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Baritolloti is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. Lomberona is a city in Cartabitan.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What states have a city not named Baritolloti?","answer":"Bascilitina, Cartabitan"}},"flags":["negation","objective_concept_definition","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Every city has one name. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Baritolloti is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. Lomberona is a city in Cartabitan.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What states have a city not named Lomtrieste?","answer":"Grappulia, Regnobenoa"}},"flags":["negation","objective_concept_definition","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Every city has one name. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Baritolloti is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. Lomberona is a city in Cartabitan.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What states have a city not named Geoturin?","answer":"Bascilitina, Grappulia, Regnobenoa"}},"flags":["negation","objective_concept_definition","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Grappulia borders Cartabitan. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa borders Grappulia. Bascilitina borders Regnobenoa. Bascilitina borders Grappulia. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Baritolloti is a city in Grappulia. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. Cartabitan is a state in Catardinia. If X borders Y, then Y borders X.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which states border Grappulia?","answer":"Bascilitina, Cartabitan, Regnobenoa"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Grappulia borders Cartabitan. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa borders Grappulia. Bascilitina borders Regnobenoa. Bascilitina borders Grappulia. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Baritolloti is a city in Grappulia. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. Cartabitan is a state in Catardinia. Cartabitan does not border Regnobenoa. Regnobenoa does not border Cartabitan. If X borders Y, then Y borders X.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which states border Grappulia?","answer":"Bascilitina, Cartabitan, Regnobenoa"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Grappulia borders Cartabitan. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Bascilitina borders Regnobenoa. Bascilitina borders Grappulia. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Baritolloti is a city in Grappulia. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. Cartabitan is a state in Catardinia. If X borders Y, then Y borders X.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which states border Grappulia?","answer":"Bascilitina, Cartabitan"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Grappulia borders Cartabitan. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Bascilitina borders Regnobenoa. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Baritolloti is a city in Grappulia. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. Cartabitan is a state in Catardinia. If X borders Y, then Y borders X.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which states border Grappulia?","answer":"Cartabitan"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa borders Grappulia. Bascilitina borders Regnobenoa. Bascilitina borders Grappulia. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Baritolloti is a city in Grappulia. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. Cartabitan is a state in Catardinia. If X borders Y, then Y borders X.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which states border Grappulia?","answer":"Bascilitina, Regnobenoa"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Grappulia borders Cartabitan. Cartabitan borders Grappulia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa borders Grappulia. Grappulia borders Regnobenoa. Bascilitina borders Regnobenoa. Regnobenoa borders Bascilitina. Bascilitina borders Grappulia. Grappulia borders Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Baritolloti is a city in Grappulia. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. Cartabitan is a state in Catardinia.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which states border Grappulia?","answer":"Bascilitina, Cartabitan, Regnobenoa"}}}
{"theory":"Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Grappulia borders Cartabitan. Cartabitan borders Grappulia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa borders Grappulia. Grappulia borders Regnobenoa. Bascilitina borders Regnobenoa. Regnobenoa borders Bascilitina. Bascilitina borders Grappulia. Grappulia borders Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Baritolloti is a city in Grappulia. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. Cartabitan is a state in Catardinia. Cartabitan does not border Regnobenoa. Regnobenoa does not border Cartabitan.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which states border Grappulia?","answer":"Bascilitina, Cartabitan, Regnobenoa"}}}
{"theory":"Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Grappulia borders Cartabitan. Cartabitan borders Grappulia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Bascilitina borders Regnobenoa. Regnobenoa borders Bascilitina. Bascilitina borders Grappulia. Grappulia borders Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Baritolloti is a city in Grappulia. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. Cartabitan is a state in Catardinia.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which states border Grappulia?","answer":"Bascilitina, Cartabitan"}}}
{"theory":"Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Grappulia borders Cartabitan. Cartabitan borders Grappulia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Bascilitina borders Regnobenoa. Regnobenoa borders Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Baritolloti is a city in Grappulia. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. Cartabitan is a state in Catardinia.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which states border Grappulia?","answer":"Cartabitan"}}}
{"theory":"Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa borders Grappulia. Grappulia borders Regnobenoa. Bascilitina borders Regnobenoa. Regnobenoa borders Bascilitina. Bascilitina borders Grappulia. Grappulia borders Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Baritolloti is a city in Grappulia. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. Cartabitan is a state in Catardinia.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which states border Grappulia?","answer":"Bascilitina, Regnobenoa"}}}
{"theory":"Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Grappulia borders Cartabitan. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa borders Grappulia. Bascilitina borders Regnobenoa. Bascilitina borders Grappulia. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Baritolloti is a city in Grappulia. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. Cartabitan is a state in Catardinia. If X borders Y, then Y borders X.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which are the states that border Grappulia?","answer":"Bascilitina, Cartabitan, Regnobenoa"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Grappulia borders Cartabitan. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa borders Grappulia. Bascilitina borders Regnobenoa. Bascilitina borders Grappulia. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Baritolloti is a city in Grappulia. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. Cartabitan is a state in Catardinia. Cartabitan does not border Regnobenoa. Regnobenoa does not border Cartabitan. If X borders Y, then Y borders X.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which are the states that border Grappulia?","answer":"Bascilitina, Cartabitan, Regnobenoa"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Grappulia borders Cartabitan. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Bascilitina borders Regnobenoa. Bascilitina borders Grappulia. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Baritolloti is a city in Grappulia. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. Cartabitan is a state in Catardinia. If X borders Y, then Y borders X.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which are the states that border Grappulia?","answer":"Bascilitina, Cartabitan"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Grappulia borders Cartabitan. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Bascilitina borders Regnobenoa. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Baritolloti is a city in Grappulia. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. Cartabitan is a state in Catardinia. If X borders Y, then Y borders X.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which are the states that border Grappulia?","answer":"Cartabitan"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa borders Grappulia. Bascilitina borders Regnobenoa. Bascilitina borders Grappulia. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Baritolloti is a city in Grappulia. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. Cartabitan is a state in Catardinia. If X borders Y, then Y borders X.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which are the states that border Grappulia?","answer":"Bascilitina, Regnobenoa"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Grappulia borders Cartabitan. Cartabitan borders Grappulia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa borders Grappulia. Grappulia borders Regnobenoa. Bascilitina borders Regnobenoa. Regnobenoa borders Bascilitina. Bascilitina borders Grappulia. Grappulia borders Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Baritolloti is a city in Grappulia. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. Cartabitan is a state in Catardinia.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which are the states that border Grappulia?","answer":"Bascilitina, Cartabitan, Regnobenoa"}}}
{"theory":"Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Grappulia borders Cartabitan. Cartabitan borders Grappulia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa borders Grappulia. Grappulia borders Regnobenoa. Bascilitina borders Regnobenoa. Regnobenoa borders Bascilitina. Bascilitina borders Grappulia. Grappulia borders Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Baritolloti is a city in Grappulia. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. Cartabitan is a state in Catardinia. Cartabitan does not border Regnobenoa. Regnobenoa does not border Cartabitan.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which are the states that border Grappulia?","answer":"Bascilitina, Cartabitan, Regnobenoa"}}}
{"theory":"Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Grappulia borders Cartabitan. Cartabitan borders Grappulia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Bascilitina borders Regnobenoa. Regnobenoa borders Bascilitina. Bascilitina borders Grappulia. Grappulia borders Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Baritolloti is a city in Grappulia. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. Cartabitan is a state in Catardinia.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which are the states that border Grappulia?","answer":"Bascilitina, Cartabitan"}}}
{"theory":"Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Grappulia borders Cartabitan. Cartabitan borders Grappulia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Bascilitina borders Regnobenoa. Regnobenoa borders Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Baritolloti is a city in Grappulia. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. Cartabitan is a state in Catardinia.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which are the states that border Grappulia?","answer":"Cartabitan"}}}
{"theory":"Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa borders Grappulia. Grappulia borders Regnobenoa. Bascilitina borders Regnobenoa. Regnobenoa borders Bascilitina. Bascilitina borders Grappulia. Grappulia borders Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Baritolloti is a city in Grappulia. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. Cartabitan is a state in Catardinia.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which are the states that border Grappulia?","answer":"Bascilitina, Regnobenoa"}}}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. There are 7 provinces.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Puotorsk is how large?","answer":"1023900","answer_templates":["{0} square kilometers", "{0} square km", "{0} square km.", "{0} sq kilometers", "{0} sq. kilometers", "{0} sq km", "{0} sq. km."]}},"flags":["lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 3149000 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. There are 7 provinces.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Fordgorod is how large?","answer":"671300","answer_templates":["{0} square kilometers", "{0} square km", "{0} square km.", "{0} sq kilometers", "{0} sq. kilometers", "{0} sq km", "{0} sq. km."]}},"flags":["lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 102390 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. There are 7 provinces.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Abdorostan is how large?","answer":"912300","answer_templates":["{0} square kilometers", "{0} square km", "{0} square km.", "{0} sq kilometers", "{0} sq. kilometers", "{0} sq km", "{0} sq. km."]}},"flags":["lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 67130 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. There are 7 provinces.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Bripetrsk is how large?","answer":"428100","answer_templates":["{0} square kilometers", "{0} square km", "{0} square km.", "{0} sq kilometers", "{0} sq. kilometers", "{0} sq km", "{0} sq. km."]}},"flags":["lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 91230 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. There are 7 provinces.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Galininograd is how large?","answer":"314900","answer_templates":["{0} square kilometers", "{0} square km", "{0} square km.", "{0} sq kilometers", "{0} sq. kilometers", "{0} sq km", "{0} sq. km."]}},"flags":["lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. There are 7 provinces.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Puotorsk is how large?","answer":"1023900","answer_templates":["{0} square kilometers", "{0} square km", "{0} square km.", "{0} sq kilometers", "{0} sq. kilometers", "{0} sq km", "{0} sq. km."]}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 3149000 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. There are 7 provinces.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Fordgorod is how large?","answer":"671300","answer_templates":["{0} square kilometers", "{0} square km", "{0} square km.", "{0} sq kilometers", "{0} sq. kilometers", "{0} sq km", "{0} sq. km."]}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 102390 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. There are 7 provinces.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Abdorostan is how large?","answer":"912300","answer_templates":["{0} square kilometers", "{0} square km", "{0} square km.", "{0} sq kilometers", "{0} sq. kilometers", "{0} sq km", "{0} sq. km."]}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 67130 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. There are 7 provinces.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Bripetrsk is how large?","answer":"428100","answer_templates":["{0} square kilometers", "{0} square km", "{0} square km.", "{0} sq kilometers", "{0} sq. kilometers", "{0} sq km", "{0} sq. km."]}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 91230 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. There are 7 provinces.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Galininograd is how large?","answer":"314900","answer_templates":["{0} square kilometers", "{0} square km", "{0} square km.", "{0} sq kilometers", "{0} sq. kilometers", "{0} sq km", "{0} sq. km."]}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"The Merasardu River is a river in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is a river in Efanangole. The Mbalam is a river in Bolurofi. The Kolufori River is a river in Efanangole. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 432 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 218 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 587 kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"How long is the Kolufori River?","answer":"587","answer_templates":["{0} kilometers", "{0} km", "{0} km."]}}}
{"theory":"The Merasardu River is a river in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is a river in Efanangole. The Mbalam is a river in Bolurofi. The Kolufori River is a river in Efanangole. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 61 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 12 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 92 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 58 kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"How long is the Kolufori River?","answer":"58","answer_templates":["{0} kilometers", "{0} km", "{0} km."]}}}
{"theory":"The Merasardu River is a river in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is a river in Efanangole. The Mbalam is a river in Bolurofi. The Kolufori River is a river in Efanangole. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 3049 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 6128 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 9587 kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"How long is the Kolufori River?","answer":"9587","answer_templates":["{0} kilometers", "{0} km", "{0} km."]}}}
{"theory":"The Merasardu River is a river in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is a river in Bolurofi. The Mbalam is a river in Bolurofi. The Kolufori River is a river in Efanangole. There are 2 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 3049 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 6128 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 913 kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"How long is the Kolufori River?","answer":"913","answer_templates":["{0} kilometers", "{0} km", "{0} km."]}}}
{"theory":"The Merasardu River is a river in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is a river in Bolurofi. The Mbalam is a river in Bolurofi. The Kolufori River is a river in Efanangole. There are 2 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 13 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 21 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 7 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 91 kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"How long is the Kolufori River?","answer":"91","answer_templates":["{0} kilometers", "{0} km", "{0} km."]}}}
{"theory":"The Merasardu River is a river in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is a river in Efanangole. The Mbalam is a river in Bolurofi. The Kolufori River is a river in Efanangole. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 432 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 218 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 587 kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"How long is the Merasardu River?","answer":"432","answer_templates":["{0} kilometers", "{0} km", "{0} km."]}}}
{"theory":"The Merasardu River is a river in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is a river in Efanangole. The Mbalam is a river in Bolurofi. The Kolufori River is a river in Efanangole. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 61 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 12 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 92 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 58 kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"How long is the Merasardu River?","answer":"61","answer_templates":["{0} kilometers", "{0} km", "{0} km."]}}}
{"theory":"The Merasardu River is a river in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is a river in Efanangole. The Mbalam is a river in Bolurofi. The Kolufori River is a river in Efanangole. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 3049 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 6128 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 9587 kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"How long is the Merasardu River?","answer":"3049","answer_templates":["{0} kilometers", "{0} km", "{0} km."]}}}
{"theory":"The Merasardu River is a river in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is a river in Bolurofi. The Mbalam is a river in Bolurofi. The Kolufori River is a river in Efanangole. There are 2 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 3049 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 6128 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 913 kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"How long is the Merasardu River?","answer":"3049","answer_templates":["{0} kilometers", "{0} km", "{0} km."]}}}
{"theory":"The Merasardu River is a river in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is a river in Bolurofi. The Mbalam is a river in Bolurofi. The Kolufori River is a river in Efanangole. There are 2 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 13 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 21 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 7 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 91 kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"How long is the Merasardu River?","answer":"13","answer_templates":["{0} kilometers", "{0} km", "{0} km."]}}}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is a province in Bievorsk. There are 7 provinces. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The population of Abdorostan is 6712302. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. If the area of X is smaller than 100000 square kilometers then X is minor.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the minor provinces?","answer":""}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is a province in Bievorsk. There are 7 provinces. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The population of Abdorostan is 6712302. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The population of Getarovo is 2912062. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. If the area of X is smaller than 500000 square kilometers then X is minor.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the minor provinces?","answer":"Bripetrsk, Galininograd"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is a province in Bievorsk. There are 7 provinces. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. The population of Voronolga is 101. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The population of Abdorostan is 67. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The population of Fordgorod is 72. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The population of Galininograd is 23. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The population of Puotorsk is 41. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The population of Getarovo is 229. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The population of Bripetrsk is 4. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. If the area of X is smaller than 600000 square kilometers then X is minor.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the minor provinces?","answer":"Bripetrsk, Galininograd, Getarovo"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is a province in Bievorsk. There are 7 provinces. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. The population of Voronolga is 101. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The population of Abdorostan is 67. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The population of Fordgorod is 72. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The population of Galininograd is 23. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The population of Puotorsk is 41. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The population of Getarovo is 22. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The population of Bripetrsk is 4. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. If the area of X is smaller than 1000000 square kilometers then X is minor.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the minor provinces?","answer":"Abdorostan, Bripetrsk, Fordgorod, Galininograd, Getarovo, Voronolga"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is a province in Bievorsk. There are 7 provinces. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. The population of Voronolga is 10. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The population of Abdorostan is 67. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The population of Fordgorod is 72. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The population of Galininograd is 23. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The population of Puotorsk is 41. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The population of Getarovo is 22. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The population of Bripetrsk is 4. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. If the area of X is smaller than 500000 square kilometers then X is minor.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the minor provinces?","answer":"Bripetrsk, Galininograd"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is a province in Bievorsk. There are 7 provinces. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The population of Abdorostan is 6712302. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. If the area of X is smaller than 100000 square kilometers then X is not big.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the provinces that are not big?","answer":""}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition","negation"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is a province in Bievorsk. There are 7 provinces. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The population of Abdorostan is 6712302. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The population of Getarovo is 2912062. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. If the area of X is smaller than 500000 square kilometers then X is not big.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the provinces that are not big?","answer":"Bripetrsk, Galininograd"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition","negation"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is a province in Bievorsk. There are 7 provinces. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. The population of Voronolga is 101. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The population of Abdorostan is 67. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The population of Fordgorod is 72. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The population of Galininograd is 23. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The population of Puotorsk is 41. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The population of Getarovo is 229. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The population of Bripetrsk is 4. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. If the area of X is smaller than 600000 square kilometers then X is not big.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the provinces that are not big?","answer":"Bripetrsk, Galininograd, Getarovo"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition","negation"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is a province in Bievorsk. There are 7 provinces. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. The population of Voronolga is 101. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The population of Abdorostan is 67. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The population of Fordgorod is 72. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The population of Galininograd is 23. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The population of Puotorsk is 41. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The population of Getarovo is 22. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The population of Bripetrsk is 4. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. If the area of X is smaller than 1000000 square kilometers then X is not big.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the provinces that are not big?","answer":"Abdorostan, Bripetrsk, Fordgorod, Galininograd, Getarovo, Voronolga"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition","negation"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is a province in Bievorsk. There are 7 provinces. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. The population of Voronolga is 10. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The population of Abdorostan is 67. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The population of Fordgorod is 72. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The population of Galininograd is 23. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The population of Puotorsk is 41. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The population of Getarovo is 22. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The population of Bripetrsk is 4. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. If the area of X is smaller than 500000 square kilometers then X is not big.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the provinces that are not big?","answer":"Bripetrsk, Galininograd"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition","negation"]}
{"theory":"If X runs through Y, then X is in Y. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Cartabitan is one of the 4 states in Catardinia. The Begliomento is a river in Catardinia. The Begliomento runs through Grappulia. The Begliomento runs through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco is a river in Catardinia. The Terravipacco runs through Grappulia. The Terravipacco runs through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco runs through Bascilitina. The Pernatisone is a river in Catardinia. The Pernatisone runs through Grappulia.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the rivers in Grappulia?","answer":"Begliomento, Pernatisone, Terravipacco"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"If X runs through Y, then X is in Y. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Cartabitan is one of the 4 states in Catardinia. The Begliomento is a river in Catardinia. The Begliomento runs through Grappulia. The Begliomento runs through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco is a river in Catardinia. The Terravipacco runs through Grappulia. The Terravipacco runs through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco runs through Bascilitina. The Pernatisone is a river in Catardinia. The Pernatisone runs through Grappulia.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the rivers in Regnobenoa?","answer":"Begliomento, Terravipacco"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"If X runs through Y, then X is in Y. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Cartabitan is one of the 4 states in Catardinia. The Begliomento is a river in Catardinia. The Begliomento runs through Grappulia. The Begliomento runs through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco is a river in Catardinia. The Terravipacco runs through Grappulia. The Terravipacco runs through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco runs through Bascilitina. The Pernatisone is a river in Catardinia. The Pernatisone runs through Grappulia.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the rivers in Cartabitan?","answer":""}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"If X runs through Y, then X is in Y. Grappulia is one of the 4 states in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Cartabitan is a state in Catardinia. The Begliomento is a river in Catardinia. The Begliomento runs through Grappulia. The Begliomento runs through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco is a river in Catardinia. The Terravipacco runs through Grappulia. The Terravipacco runs through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco runs through Bascilitina. The Pernatisone is a river in Catardinia. The Pernatisone runs through Grappulia.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the rivers in Grappulia?","answer":"Begliomento, Pernatisone, Terravipacco"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"If X runs through Y, then X is in Y. Grappulia is one of the 4 states in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Cartabitan is a state in Catardinia. The Begliomento is a river in Catardinia. The Begliomento runs through Grappulia. The Begliomento runs through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco is a river in Catardinia. The Terravipacco runs through Grappulia. The Terravipacco runs through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco runs through Bascilitina. The Pernatisone is a river in Catardinia. The Pernatisone runs through Grappulia.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the rivers in Regnobenoa?","answer":"Begliomento, Terravipacco"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"If X runs through Y, then X is in Y. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Cartabitan is one of the 7 states in Catardinia. Umbriazzo is a state in Catardinia. Lordanidia is a state in Catardinia. Estmolise is a state in Catardinia. The Begliomento is a river in Catardinia. The Begliomento runs through Grappulia. The Begliomento runs through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco is a river in Catardinia. The Terravipacco runs through Grappulia. The Terravipacco runs through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco runs through Bascilitina. The Pernatisone is a river in Catardinia. The Pernatisone runs through Grappulia. The Terravipacco runs through Umbriazzo. Terravipacco runs through Lordanidia. Terravipacco runs through Estmolise.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the rivers in Grappulia?","answer":"Begliomento, Pernatisone, Terravipacco"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"If X runs through Y, then X is in Y. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Cartabitan is one of the 7 states in Catardinia. Umbriazzo is a state in Catardinia. Lordanidia is a state in Catardinia. Estmolise is a state in Catardinia. The Begliomento is a river in Catardinia. The Begliomento runs through Grappulia. The Begliomento runs through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco is a river in Catardinia. The Terravipacco runs through Grappulia. The Terravipacco runs through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco runs through Bascilitina. The Pernatisone is a river in Catardinia. The Pernatisone runs through Grappulia. Terravipacco runs through Umbriazzo. Terravipacco runs through Lordanidia. Terravipacco runs through Estmolise.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the rivers in Regnobenoa?","answer":"Begliomento, Terravipacco"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"If X runs through Y, then X is in Y. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Cartabitan is one of the 7 states in Catardinia. Umbriazzo is a state in Catardinia. Lordanidia is a state in Catardinia. Estmolise is a state in Catardinia. The Begliomento is a river in Catardinia. The Begliomento runs through Grappulia. The Begliomento runs through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco is a river in Catardinia. The Terravipacco runs through Grappulia. The Terravipacco runs through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco runs through Bascilitina. The Pernatisone is a river in Catardinia. The Pernatisone runs through Grappulia. Terravipacco runs through Umbriazzo. Terravipacco runs through Lordanidia. Terravipacco runs through Estmolise.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the rivers in Cartabitan?","answer":""}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"If X runs through Y, then X is in Y. Grappulia is one of the 7 states in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Cartabitan is a state in Catardinia. Umbriazzo is a state in Catardinia. Lordanidia is a state in Catardinia. Estmolise is a state in Catardinia. The Begliomento is a river in Catardinia. The Begliomento runs through Grappulia. The Begliomento runs through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco is a river in Catardinia. The Terravipacco runs through Grappulia. The Terravipacco runs through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco runs through Bascilitina. The Pernatisone is a river in Catardinia. The Pernatisone runs through Grappulia. Terravipacco runs through Umbriazzo. Terravipacco runs through Lordanidia. Terravipacco runs through Estmolise.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the rivers in Grappulia?","answer":"Begliomento, Pernatisone, Terravipacco"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"If X runs through Y, then X is in Y. Grappulia is one of the 7 states in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Cartabitan is a state in Catardinia. Umbriazzo is a state in Catardinia. Lordanidia is a state in Catardinia. Estmolise is a state in Catardinia. The Begliomento is a river in Catardinia. The Begliomento runs through Grappulia. The Begliomento runs through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco is a river in Catardinia. The Terravipacco runs through Grappulia. The Terravipacco runs through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco runs through Bascilitina. The Pernatisone is a river in Catardinia. The Pernatisone runs through Grappulia. Terravipacco runs through Umbriazzo. Terravipacco runs through Lordanidia. Terravipacco runs through Estmolise.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the rivers in Regnobenoa?","answer":"Begliomento, Terravipacco"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in East Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in East Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in East Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, East Senkuoka is 210390.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Where is Koruhashi?","answer":"Kangoyaken"}}}
{"theory":"Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in East Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in East Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in East Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, East Senkuoka is 210390.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Where is Dogayashi?","answer":"Kangoyaken"}}}
{"theory":"Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in East Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in East Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in East Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, East Senkuoka is 210390.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Where is Kyoukashino?","answer":"East Senkuoka, Kangoyaken"}}}
{"theory":"Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in East Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in East Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in East Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, East Senkuoka is 210390.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Where is Sennouhama?","answer":"East Senkuoka"}}}
{"theory":"Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in East Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in East Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in East Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, East Senkuoka is 210390.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Where is Yotsuyamashi?","answer":"East Senkuoka"}}}
{"theory":"Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in East Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in East Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in East Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, East Senkuoka is 210390. Koruhashi is a city in North Senkuoka. The population of Koruhashi, North Senkuoka is 489012. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Kangoyaken. 1 million people live in Yotsuyamashi, Kangoyaken.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Where is Koruhashi?","answer":"Kangoyaken, North Senkuoka"}}}
{"theory":"Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in East Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in East Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in East Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, East Senkuoka is 210390. Koruhashi is a city in North Senkuoka. The population of Koruhashi, North Senkuoka is 489012. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Kangoyaken. 1 million people live in Yotsuyamashi, Kangoyaken.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Where is Dogayashi?","answer":"Kangoyaken"}}}
{"theory":"Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in East Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in East Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in East Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, East Senkuoka is 210390. Koruhashi is a city in North Senkuoka. The population of Koruhashi, North Senkuoka is 489012. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Kangoyaken. 1 million people live in Yotsuyamashi, Kangoyaken.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Where is Kyoukashino?","answer":"East Senkuoka, Kangoyaken"}}}
{"theory":"Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in East Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in East Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in East Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, East Senkuoka is 210390. Koruhashi is a city in North Senkuoka. The population of Koruhashi, North Senkuoka is 489012. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Kangoyaken. 1 million people live in Yotsuyamashi, Kangoyaken.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Where is Sennouhama?","answer":"East Senkuoka"}}}
{"theory":"Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in East Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in East Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in East Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, East Senkuoka is 210390. Koruhashi is a city in North Senkuoka. The population of Koruhashi, North Senkuoka is 489012. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Kangoyaken. 1 million people live in Yotsuyamashi, Kangoyaken.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Where is Yotsuyamashi?","answer":"East Senkuoka, Kangoyaken"}}}
{"theory":"If the population of X is Y, then the number of people in X is Y. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is a province in Bievorsk. There are 7 provinces. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The population of Abdorostan is 6712302. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What province has the most people?","answer":"Getarovo"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"If the population of X is Y, then the number of people in X is Y. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is a province in Bievorsk. There are 7 provinces. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The population of Abdorostan is 6712302. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The population of Getarovo is 2912062. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What province has the most people?","answer":"Voronolga"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"If the population of X is Y, then the number of people in X is Y. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is a province in Bievorsk. There are 7 provinces. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. The population of Voronolga is 101. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The population of Abdorostan is 67. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The population of Fordgorod is 72. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The population of Galininograd is 23. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The population of Puotorsk is 41. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The population of Getarovo is 229. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The population of Bripetrsk is 4. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What province has the most people?","answer":"Getarovo"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"If the population of X is Y, then the number of people in X is Y. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is a province in Bievorsk. There are 7 provinces. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. The population of Voronolga is 101. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The population of Abdorostan is 67. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The population of Fordgorod is 72. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The population of Galininograd is 23. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The population of Puotorsk is 41. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The population of Getarovo is 22. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The population of Bripetrsk is 4. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What province has the most people?","answer":"Voronolga"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"If the population of X is Y, then the number of people in X is Y. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is a province in Bievorsk. There are 7 provinces. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. The population of Voronolga is 10. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The population of Abdorostan is 67. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The population of Fordgorod is 72. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The population of Galininograd is 23. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The population of Puotorsk is 41. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The population of Getarovo is 22. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The population of Bripetrsk is 4. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What province has the most people?","answer":"Fordgorod"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"If the population of X is Y, then the number of people in X is Y. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is a province in Bievorsk. There are 7 provinces. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The population of Abdorostan is 6712302. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What province has the fewest people?","answer":"Puotorsk"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"If the population of X is Y, then the number of people in X is Y. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is a province in Bievorsk. There are 7 provinces. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The population of Abdorostan is 6712302. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The population of Getarovo is 2912062. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What province has the fewest people?","answer":"Puotorsk"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"If the population of X is Y, then the number of people in X is Y. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is a province in Bievorsk. There are 7 provinces. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. The population of Voronolga is 101. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The population of Abdorostan is 67. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The population of Fordgorod is 72. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The population of Galininograd is 23. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The population of Puotorsk is 41. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The population of Getarovo is 229. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The population of Bripetrsk is 4. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What province has the fewest people?","answer":"Bripetrsk"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"If the population of X is Y, then the number of people in X is Y. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is a province in Bievorsk. There are 7 provinces. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. The population of Voronolga is 101. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The population of Abdorostan is 67. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The population of Fordgorod is 72. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The population of Galininograd is 23. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The population of Puotorsk is 41. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The population of Getarovo is 22. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The population of Bripetrsk is 4. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What province has the fewest people?","answer":"Bripetrsk"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"If the population of X is Y, then the number of people in X is Y. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is a province in Bievorsk. There are 7 provinces. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. The population of Voronolga is 10. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The population of Abdorostan is 67. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The population of Fordgorod is 72. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The population of Galininograd is 23. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The population of Puotorsk is 41. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The population of Getarovo is 22. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The population of Bripetrsk is 4. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What province has the fewest people?","answer":"Bripetrsk"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is a province in Bievorsk. There are 7 provinces. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The population of Abdorostan is 6712302. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is minor.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the minor provinces?","answer":""}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is a province in Bievorsk. There are 7 provinces. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The population of Abdorostan is 6712302. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The population of Getarovo is 2912062. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. If the population of X is smaller than 500000 then X is minor.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the minor provinces?","answer":"Bripetrsk, Puotorsk"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is a province in Bievorsk. There are 7 provinces. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. The population of Voronolga is 101. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The population of Abdorostan is 67. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The population of Fordgorod is 72. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The population of Galininograd is 23. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The population of Puotorsk is 41. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The population of Getarovo is 229. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The population of Bripetrsk is 4. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. If the population of X is smaller than 60 then X is minor.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the minor provinces?","answer":"Bripetrsk, Galininograd, Puotorsk"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is a province in Bievorsk. There are 7 provinces. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. The population of Voronolga is 101. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The population of Abdorostan is 67. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The population of Fordgorod is 72. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The population of Galininograd is 23. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The population of Puotorsk is 41. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The population of Getarovo is 22. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The population of Bripetrsk is 4. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. If the population of X is smaller than 100 then X is minor.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the minor provinces?","answer":"Abdorostan, Bripetrsk, Fordgorod, Galininograd, Getarovo, Puotorsk"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is a province in Bievorsk. There are 7 provinces. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. The population of Voronolga is 10. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The population of Abdorostan is 67. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The population of Fordgorod is 72. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The population of Galininograd is 23. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The population of Puotorsk is 41. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The population of Getarovo is 22. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The population of Bripetrsk is 4. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. If the population of X is smaller than 50 then X is minor.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the minor provinces?","answer":"Bripetrsk, Galininograd, Getarovo, Puotorsk, Voronolga"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is a province in Bievorsk. There are 7 provinces. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The population of Abdorostan is 6712302. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is not big.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the provinces that are not big?","answer":""}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition","negation"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is a province in Bievorsk. There are 7 provinces. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The population of Abdorostan is 6712302. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The population of Getarovo is 2912062. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. If the population of X is smaller than 500000 then X is not big.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the provinces that are not big?","answer":"Bripetrsk, Puotorsk"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition","negation"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is a province in Bievorsk. There are 7 provinces. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. The population of Voronolga is 101. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The population of Abdorostan is 67. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The population of Fordgorod is 72. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The population of Galininograd is 23. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The population of Puotorsk is 41. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The population of Getarovo is 229. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The population of Bripetrsk is 4. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. If the population of X is smaller than 60 then X is not big.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the provinces that are not big?","answer":"Bripetrsk, Galininograd, Puotorsk"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition","negation"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is a province in Bievorsk. There are 7 provinces. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. The population of Voronolga is 101. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The population of Abdorostan is 67. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The population of Fordgorod is 72. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The population of Galininograd is 23. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The population of Puotorsk is 41. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The population of Getarovo is 22. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The population of Bripetrsk is 4. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. If the population of X is smaller than 100 then X is not big.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the provinces that are not big?","answer":"Abdorostan, Bripetrsk, Fordgorod, Galininograd, Getarovo, Puotorsk"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition","negation"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is a province in Bievorsk. There are 7 provinces. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. The population of Voronolga is 10. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The population of Abdorostan is 67. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The population of Fordgorod is 72. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The population of Galininograd is 23. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The population of Puotorsk is 41. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The population of Getarovo is 22. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The population of Bripetrsk is 4. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. If the population of X is smaller than 50 then X is not big.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the provinces that are not big?","answer":"Bripetrsk, Galininograd, Getarovo, Puotorsk, Voronolga"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition","negation"]}
{"theory":"The Merasardu River is a river in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is a river in Efanangole. The Mbalam is a river in Bolurofi. The Kolufori River is a river in Efanangole. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 432 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 218 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 587 kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"How long is the longest river in Efanangole?","answer":"587","answer_templates":["{0} kilometers", "{0} km", "{0} km."]}},"flags":["superlative"]}
{"theory":"The Merasardu River is a river in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is a river in Efanangole. The Mbalam is a river in Bolurofi. The Kolufori River is a river in Efanangole. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 61 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 12 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 92 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 58 kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"How long is the longest river in Efanangole?","answer":"61","answer_templates":["{0} kilometers", "{0} km", "{0} km."]}},"flags":["superlative"]}
{"theory":"The Merasardu River is a river in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is a river in Efanangole. The Mbalam is a river in Bolurofi. The Kolufori River is a river in Efanangole. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 3049 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 6128 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 9587 kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"How long is the longest river in Efanangole?","answer":"9587","answer_templates":["{0} kilometers", "{0} km", "{0} km."]}},"flags":["superlative"]}
{"theory":"The Merasardu River is a river in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is a river in Bolurofi. The Mbalam is a river in Bolurofi. The Kolufori River is a river in Efanangole. There are 2 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 3049 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 6128 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 913 kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"How long is the longest river in Efanangole?","answer":"3049","answer_templates":["{0} kilometers", "{0} km", "{0} km."]}},"flags":["superlative"]}
{"theory":"The Merasardu River is a river in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is a river in Bolurofi. The Mbalam is a river in Bolurofi. The Kolufori River is a river in Efanangole. There are 2 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 13 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 21 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 7 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 91 kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"How long is the longest river in Efanangole?","answer":"91","answer_templates":["{0} kilometers", "{0} km", "{0} km."]}},"flags":["superlative"]}
{"theory":"If X is in Y and Y is in Z, then X is in Z. The Merasardu River is a river in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is a river in the state of Merafagole. Merafagole is a state in Efanangole. The Mbalam is a river in Bolurofi. The Kolufori River is a river in Efanangole. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 432 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 218 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 587 kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"How long is the longest river in Efanangole?","answer":"587","answer_templates":["{0} kilometers", "{0} km", "{0} km."]}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","superlative"]}
{"theory":"If X is in Y and Y is in Z, then X is in Z. The Merasardu River is a river in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is a river in the state of Merafagole. Merafagole is a state in Efanangole. The Mbalam is a river in Bolurofi. The Kolufori River is a river in Efanangole. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 61 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 12 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 92 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 58 kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"How long is the longest river in Efanangole?","answer":"61","answer_templates":["{0} kilometers", "{0} km", "{0} km."]}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","superlative"]}
{"theory":"If X is in Y and Y is in Z, then X is in Z. The Merasardu River is a river in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is a river in the state of Merafagole. Merafagole is a state in Efanangole. The Mbalam is a river in Bolurofi. The Kolufori River is a river in Efanangole. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 3049 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 6128 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 9587 kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"How long is the longest river in Efanangole?","answer":"9587","answer_templates":["{0} kilometers", "{0} km", "{0} km."]}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","superlative"]}
{"theory":"If X is in Y and Y is in Z, then X is in Z. The Merasardu River is a river in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is a river in the state of Merafagole. Merafagole is a state in Bolurofi. The Mbalam is a river in Bolurofi. The Kolufori River is a river in Efanangole. There are 2 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 3049 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 6128 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 913 kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"How long is the longest river in Efanangole?","answer":"3049","answer_templates":["{0} kilometers", "{0} km", "{0} km."]}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","superlative"]}
{"theory":"If X is in Y and Y is in Z, then X is in Z. The Merasardu River is a river in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is a river in the state of Merafagole. Merafagole is a state in Bolurofi. The Mbalam is a river in Bolurofi. The Kolufori River is a river in Efanangole. There are 2 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 13 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 21 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 7 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 91 kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"How long is the longest river in Efanangole?","answer":"91","answer_templates":["{0} kilometers", "{0} km", "{0} km."]}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","superlative"]}
{"theory":"Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. Mbalam is a city in Bolurofi. Marba Adama is the capital city of Efanangole. Alharwassa is the capital city of Bolurofi. Sharhamane is a city in Efanangole. Saare Daewa is a city in Bolurofi. The population of Marba Adama is 7182032. The population of Alharwassa is 173201. The population of Sharhamane is 4192302. The population of Saare Daewa is 86110. Gondarbawa is a city in Efanangole. The population of Gondarbawa is 398184. There are 3 cities in Efanangole. The population of Mbalam is 6132027. There are 3 cities in Bolurofi.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the city in Efanangole with the largest population?","answer":"Marba Adama"}},"flags":["superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. Mbalam is a city in Bolurofi. Marba Adama is the capital city of Efanangole. Alharwassa is the capital city of Bolurofi. Sharhamane is a city in Efanangole. Saare Daewa is a city in Bolurofi. The population of Marba Adama is 71820. The population of Alharwassa is 173201. The population of Sharhamane is 4192302. The population of Saare Daewa is 86110. Gondarbawa is a city in Efanangole. The population of Gondarbawa is 398184. There are 3 cities in Efanangole. The population of Mbalam is 6132027. There are 3 cities in Bolurofi.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the city in Efanangole with the largest population?","answer":"Sharhamane"}},"flags":["superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. Mbalam is a city in Bolurofi. Marba Adama is the capital city of Efanangole. Alharwassa is the capital city of Bolurofi. Sharhamane is a city in Efanangole. Saare Daewa is a city in Bolurofi. The population of Marba Adama is 7182032. The population of Alharwassa is 173201. The population of Sharhamane is 4192302. The population of Saare Daewa is 86110219. Gondarbawa is a city in Efanangole. The population of Gondarbawa is 3981840. There are 3 cities in Efanangole. The population of Mbalam is 6132027. There are 3 cities in Bolurofi.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the city in Efanangole with the largest population?","answer":"Marba Adama"}},"flags":["superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. Mbalam is a city in Bolurofi. Marba Adama is the capital city of Efanangole. Alharwassa is the capital city of Bolurofi. Sharhamane is a city in Efanangole. Saare Daewa is a city in Bolurofi. The population of Marba Adama is 7. The population of Alharwassa is 17. The population of Sharhamane is 419. The population of Saare Daewa is 8. Gondarbawa is a city in Efanangole. The population of Gondarbawa is 39. There are 3 cities in Efanangole. The population of Mbalam is 613. There are 3 cities in Bolurofi.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the city in Efanangole with the largest population?","answer":"Sharhamane"}},"flags":["superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. Mbalam is a city in Bolurofi. Marba Adama is the capital city of Efanangole. Alharwassa is the capital city of Bolurofi. Sharhamane is a city in Efanangole. Saare Daewa is a city in Bolurofi. The population of Marba Adama is 718. The population of Alharwassa is 17. The population of Sharhamane is 419. The population of Saare Daewa is 8611. Gondarbawa is a city in Efanangole. The population of Gondarbawa is 398. There are 3 cities in Efanangole. The population of Mbalam is 613. There are 3 cities in Bolurofi.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the city in Efanangole with the largest population?","answer":"Marba Adama"}},"flags":["superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. Mbalam is a city in Bolurofi. Marba Adama is the capital city of Efanangole. Alharwassa is the capital city of Bolurofi. Sharhamane is a city in Efanangole. Saare Daewa is a city in Bolurofi. The population of Marba Adama is 7182032. The population of Alharwassa is 173201. The population of Sharhamane is 4192302. The population of Saare Daewa is 86110. Gondarbawa is a city in Efanangole. The population of Gondarbawa is 398184. There are 3 cities in Efanangole. The population of Mbalam is 6132027. There are 3 cities in Bolurofi.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the city in Efanangole with the smallest population?","answer":"Gondarbawa"}},"flags":["superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. Mbalam is a city in Bolurofi. Marba Adama is the capital city of Efanangole. Alharwassa is the capital city of Bolurofi. Sharhamane is a city in Efanangole. Saare Daewa is a city in Bolurofi. The population of Marba Adama is 71820. The population of Alharwassa is 173201. The population of Sharhamane is 4192302. The population of Saare Daewa is 86110. Gondarbawa is a city in Efanangole. The population of Gondarbawa is 398184. There are 3 cities in Efanangole. The population of Mbalam is 6132027. There are 3 cities in Bolurofi.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the city in Efanangole with the smallest population?","answer":"Marba Adama"}},"flags":["superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. Mbalam is a city in Bolurofi. Marba Adama is the capital city of Efanangole. Alharwassa is the capital city of Bolurofi. Sharhamane is a city in Efanangole. Saare Daewa is a city in Bolurofi. The population of Marba Adama is 7182032. The population of Alharwassa is 173201. The population of Sharhamane is 4192302. The population of Saare Daewa is 86110219. Gondarbawa is a city in Efanangole. The population of Gondarbawa is 3981840. There are 3 cities in Efanangole. The population of Mbalam is 6132027. There are 3 cities in Bolurofi.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the city in Efanangole with the smallest population?","answer":"Gondarbawa"}},"flags":["superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. Mbalam is a city in Bolurofi. Marba Adama is the capital city of Efanangole. Alharwassa is the capital city of Bolurofi. Sharhamane is a city in Efanangole. Saare Daewa is a city in Bolurofi. The population of Marba Adama is 7. The population of Alharwassa is 17. The population of Sharhamane is 419. The population of Saare Daewa is 8. Gondarbawa is a city in Efanangole. The population of Gondarbawa is 39. There are 3 cities in Efanangole. The population of Mbalam is 613. There are 3 cities in Bolurofi.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the city in Efanangole with the smallest population?","answer":"Marba Adama"}},"flags":["superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. Mbalam is a city in Bolurofi. Marba Adama is the capital city of Efanangole. Alharwassa is the capital city of Bolurofi. Sharhamane is a city in Efanangole. Saare Daewa is a city in Bolurofi. The population of Marba Adama is 718. The population of Alharwassa is 17. The population of Sharhamane is 419. The population of Saare Daewa is 8611. Gondarbawa is a city in Efanangole. The population of Gondarbawa is 398. There are 3 cities in Efanangole. The population of Mbalam is 613. There are 3 cities in Bolurofi.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the city in Efanangole with the smallest population?","answer":"Gondarbawa"}},"flags":["superlative","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Baritolloti is a city in Grappulia. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. Cartabitan is a state in Catardinia. The Begliomento is a river in Catardinia. The Begliomento does not run through Grappulia. The Begliomento does not run through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco is a river in Catardinia. The Terravipacco does not run through Grappulia. The Terravipacco does not run through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco does not run through Bascilitina. The Pernatisone is a river in Catardinia. The Pernatisone does not run through Grappulia.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What rivers do not run through Grappulia?","answer":"Begliomento, Pernatisone, Terravipacco"}},"flags":["negation"]}
{"theory":"Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Baritolloti is a city in Grappulia. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. Cartabitan is a state in Catardinia. The Begliomento is a river in Catardinia. The Begliomento does not run through Grappulia. The Begliomento does not run through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco is a river in Catardinia. The Terravipacco does not run through Grappulia. The Terravipacco does not run through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco does not run through Bascilitina. The Pernatisone is a river in Catardinia. The Pernatisone does not run through Grappulia.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What rivers do not run through Bascilitina?","answer":"Terravipacco"}},"flags":["negation"]}
{"theory":"Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Baritolloti is a city in Grappulia. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. Cartabitan is a state in Catardinia. The Begliomento is a river in Catardinia. The Begliomento does not run through Grappulia. The Begliomento does not run through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco is a river in Catardinia. The Terravipacco does not run through Grappulia. The Terravipacco does not run through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco does not run through Bascilitina. The Pernatisone is a river in Catardinia. The Pernatisone does not run through Grappulia.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What rivers do not run through Cartabitan?","answer":""}},"flags":["negation"]}
{"theory":"Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Baritolloti is a city in Grappulia. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. Cartabitan is a state in Catardinia. The Begliomento is a river in Catardinia. The Begliomento does not run through Grappulia. The Begliomento does not run through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco is a river in Catardinia. The Terravipacco does not run through Grappulia. The Terravipacco does not run through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco does not run through Bascilitina. The Pernatisone is a river in Catardinia. The Pernatisone does not run through Grappulia.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What rivers do not run through Regnobenoa?","answer":"Begliomento, Terravipacco"}},"flags":["negation"]}
{"theory":"Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Baritolloti is a city in Grappulia. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. Cartabitan is a state in Catardinia. The Begliomento is a river in Catardinia. The Begliomento does not run through Grappulia. The Begliomento does not run through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco is a river in Catardinia. The Terravipacco does not run through Grappulia. The Terravipacco does not run through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco does not run through Bascilitina. The Pernatisone is a river in Catardinia. The Pernatisone does not run through Grappulia. The Pernatisone does not run through Regnobenoa.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What rivers do not run through Regnobenoa?","answer":"Begliomento, Pernatisone, Terravipacco"}},"flags":["negation"]}
{"theory":"Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Baritolloti is a city in Grappulia. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. Cartabitan is a state in Catardinia. The Begliomento is a river in Catardinia. The Begliomento does not run through Grappulia. The Begliomento does not run through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco is a river in Catardinia. The Terravipacco does not run through Grappulia. The Terravipacco does not run through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco does not run through Bascilitina. The Pernatisone is a river in Catardinia. The Pernatisone does not run through Grappulia. The Begliomento runs through Bascilitina. The Pernatisone runs through Bascilitina. The Begliomento runs through Cartabitan. The Pernatisone runs through Cartabitan. The Terravipacco runs through Cartabitan. The Pernatisone runs through Regnobenoa.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What rivers do not run through Grappulia?","answer":"Begliomento, Pernatisone, Terravipacco"}},"flags":["negation"]}
{"theory":"Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Baritolloti is a city in Grappulia. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. Cartabitan is a state in Catardinia. The Begliomento is a river in Catardinia. The Begliomento does not run through Grappulia. The Begliomento does not run through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco is a river in Catardinia. The Terravipacco does not run through Grappulia. The Terravipacco does not run through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco does not run through Bascilitina. The Pernatisone is a river in Catardinia. The Pernatisone does not run through Grappulia. The Begliomento runs through Bascilitina. The Pernatisone runs through Bascilitina. The Begliomento runs through Cartabitan. The Pernatisone runs through Cartabitan. The Terravipacco runs through Cartabitan. The Pernatisone runs through Regnobenoa.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What rivers do not run through Bascilitina?","answer":"Terravipacco"}},"flags":["negation"]}
{"theory":"Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Baritolloti is a city in Grappulia. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. Cartabitan is a state in Catardinia. The Begliomento is a river in Catardinia. The Begliomento does not run through Grappulia. The Begliomento does not run through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco is a river in Catardinia. The Terravipacco does not run through Grappulia. The Terravipacco does not run through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco does not run through Bascilitina. The Pernatisone is a river in Catardinia. The Pernatisone does not run through Grappulia. The Begliomento runs through Bascilitina. The Pernatisone runs through Bascilitina. The Begliomento runs through Cartabitan. The Pernatisone runs through Cartabitan. The Terravipacco runs through Cartabitan. The Pernatisone runs through Regnobenoa.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What rivers do not run through Cartabitan?","answer":""}},"flags":["negation"]}
{"theory":"Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Baritolloti is a city in Grappulia. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. Cartabitan is a state in Catardinia. The Begliomento is a river in Catardinia. The Begliomento does not run through Grappulia. The Begliomento does not run through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco is a river in Catardinia. The Terravipacco does not run through Grappulia. The Terravipacco does not run through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco does not run through Bascilitina. The Pernatisone is a river in Catardinia. The Pernatisone does not run through Grappulia. The Begliomento runs through Bascilitina. The Pernatisone runs through Bascilitina. The Begliomento runs through Cartabitan. The Pernatisone runs through Cartabitan. The Terravipacco runs through Cartabitan. The Pernatisone runs through Regnobenoa.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What rivers do not run through Regnobenoa?","answer":"Begliomento, Terravipacco"}},"flags":["negation"]}
{"theory":"Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Baritolloti is a city in Grappulia. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. Cartabitan is a state in Catardinia. The Begliomento is a river in Catardinia. The Begliomento does not run through Grappulia. The Begliomento does not run through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco is a river in Catardinia. The Terravipacco does not run through Grappulia. The Terravipacco does not run through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco does not run through Bascilitina. The Pernatisone is a river in Catardinia. The Pernatisone does not run through Grappulia. The Pernatisone does not run through Regnobenoa. The Begliomento runs through Bascilitina. The Pernatisone runs through Bascilitina. The Begliomento runs through Cartabitan. The Pernatisone runs through Cartabitan. The Terravipacco runs through Cartabitan.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What rivers do not run through Regnobenoa?","answer":"Begliomento, Pernatisone, Terravipacco"}},"flags":["negation"]}
{"theory":"Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Baritolloti is a city in Grappulia. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. Cartabitan is a state in Catardinia. The Begliomento is a river in Catardinia. The Begliomento runs through Grappulia. The Begliomento runs through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco is a river in Catardinia. The Terravipacco runs through Grappulia. The Terravipacco runs through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco runs through Bascilitina. The Pernatisone is a river in Catardinia. The Pernatisone runs through Grappulia. 3 rivers run through Grappulia. 2 rivers run through Regnobenoa. 1 river runs through Bascilitina. 0 rivers run through Cartabitan.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What rivers do not run through Regnobenoa?","answer":"Pernatisone"}},"flags":["negation"]}
{"theory":"Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Baritolloti is a city in Grappulia. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. Cartabitan is a state in Catardinia. The Begliomento is a river in Catardinia. The Begliomento runs through Grappulia. The Begliomento runs through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco is a river in Catardinia. The Terravipacco runs through Grappulia. The Terravipacco runs through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco runs through Bascilitina. The Pernatisone is a river in Catardinia. The Pernatisone runs through Grappulia. 3 rivers run through Grappulia. 2 rivers run through Regnobenoa. 1 river runs through Bascilitina. 0 rivers run through Cartabitan.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What rivers do not run through Grappulia?","answer":""}},"flags":["negation"]}
{"theory":"Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Baritolloti is a city in Grappulia. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. Cartabitan is a state in Catardinia. The Begliomento is a river in Catardinia. The Begliomento runs through Grappulia. The Begliomento runs through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco is a river in Catardinia. The Terravipacco runs through Grappulia. The Terravipacco runs through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco runs through Bascilitina. The Pernatisone is a river in Catardinia. The Pernatisone runs through Grappulia. 3 rivers run through Grappulia. 2 rivers run through Regnobenoa. 1 river runs through Bascilitina. 0 rivers run through Cartabitan.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What rivers do not run through Cartabitan?","answer":"Begliomento, Pernatisone, Terravipacco"}},"flags":["negation"]}
{"theory":"Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Baritolloti is a city in Grappulia. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. Cartabitan is a state in Catardinia. The Begliomento is a river in Catardinia. The Begliomento runs through Grappulia. The Begliomento runs through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco is a river in Catardinia. The Terravipacco runs through Grappulia. The Terravipacco runs through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco runs through Bascilitina. The Pernatisone is a river in Catardinia. The Pernatisone runs through Grappulia. 3 rivers run through Grappulia. 2 rivers run through Regnobenoa. 1 river runs through Bascilitina. 0 rivers run through Cartabitan.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What rivers do not run through Bascilitina?","answer":"Begliomento, Pernatisone"}},"flags":["negation"]}
{"theory":"Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Baritolloti is a city in Grappulia. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. Cartabitan is a state in Catardinia. The Begliomento is a river in Catardinia. The Begliomento runs through Grappulia. The Begliomento runs through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco is a river in Catardinia. The Terravipacco runs through Grappulia. The Terravipacco runs through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco runs through Bascilitina. The Pernatisone is a river in Catardinia. The Pernatisone runs through Grappulia. The Pernatisone runs through Regnobenoa. 3 rivers run through Grappulia. 3 rivers run through Regnobenoa. 1 river runs through Bascilitina. 0 rivers run through Cartabitan.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What rivers do not run through Regnobenoa?","answer":""}},"flags":["negation"]}
{"theory":"Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Baritolloti is a city in Grappulia. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. Cartabitan is a state in Catardinia. The Begliomento is a river in Catardinia. The Begliomento flows through Grappulia. The Begliomento runs through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco is a river in Catardinia. The Terravipacco runs through Grappulia. The Terravipacco flows through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco runs through Bascilitina. The Pernatisone is a river in Catardinia. The Pernatisone runs through Grappulia. 3 rivers run through Grappulia. 2 rivers run through Regnobenoa. 1 river flows through Bascilitina. 0 rivers run through Cartabitan.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What rivers do not flow through Regnobenoa?","answer":"Pernatisone"}},"flags":["negation"]}
{"theory":"Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Baritolloti is a city in Grappulia. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. Cartabitan is a state in Catardinia. The Begliomento is a river in Catardinia. The Begliomento flows through Grappulia. The Begliomento runs through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco is a river in Catardinia. The Terravipacco runs through Grappulia. The Terravipacco flows through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco runs through Bascilitina. The Pernatisone is a river in Catardinia. The Pernatisone runs through Grappulia. 3 rivers run through Grappulia. 2 rivers run through Regnobenoa. 1 river flows through Bascilitina. 0 rivers run through Cartabitan.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What rivers do not flow through Grappulia?","answer":""}},"flags":["negation"]}
{"theory":"Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Baritolloti is a city in Grappulia. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. Cartabitan is a state in Catardinia. The Begliomento is a river in Catardinia. The Begliomento flows through Grappulia. The Begliomento runs through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco is a river in Catardinia. The Terravipacco runs through Grappulia. The Terravipacco flows through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco runs through Bascilitina. The Pernatisone is a river in Catardinia. The Pernatisone runs through Grappulia. 3 rivers run through Grappulia. 2 rivers run through Regnobenoa. 1 river flows through Bascilitina. 0 rivers run through Cartabitan.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What rivers do not flow through Cartabitan?","answer":"Begliomento, Pernatisone, Terravipacco"}},"flags":["negation"]}
{"theory":"Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Baritolloti is a city in Grappulia. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. Cartabitan is a state in Catardinia. The Begliomento is a river in Catardinia. The Begliomento flows through Grappulia. The Begliomento runs through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco is a river in Catardinia. The Terravipacco runs through Grappulia. The Terravipacco flows through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco runs through Bascilitina. The Pernatisone is a river in Catardinia. The Pernatisone runs through Grappulia. 3 rivers run through Grappulia. 2 rivers run through Regnobenoa. 1 river flows through Bascilitina. 0 rivers run through Cartabitan.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What rivers do not flow through Bascilitina?","answer":"Begliomento, Pernatisone"}},"flags":["negation"]}
{"theory":"Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Baritolloti is a city in Grappulia. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. Cartabitan is a state in Catardinia. The Begliomento is a river in Catardinia. The Begliomento flows through Grappulia. The Begliomento runs through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco is a river in Catardinia. The Terravipacco runs through Grappulia. The Terravipacco flows through Regnobenoa. The Terravipacco runs through Bascilitina. The Pernatisone is a river in Catardinia. The Pernatisone runs through Grappulia. The Pernatisone flows through Regnobenoa. 3 rivers run through Grappulia. 3 rivers run through Regnobenoa. 1 river flows through Bascilitina. 0 rivers run through Cartabitan.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What rivers do not flow through Regnobenoa?","answer":""}},"flags":["negation"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is a province in Bievorsk. There are 7 provinces. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The population of Abdorostan is 6712302. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. If the area of X is smaller than 100000 square kilometers then X is minor.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"How many minor provinces are there?","answer":"0"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition","counting"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is a province in Bievorsk. There are 7 provinces. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The population of Abdorostan is 6712302. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The population of Getarovo is 2912062. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. If the area of X is smaller than 500000 square kilometers then X is minor.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"How many minor provinces are there?","answer":"2"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition","counting"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is a province in Bievorsk. There are 7 provinces. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. The population of Voronolga is 101. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The population of Abdorostan is 67. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The population of Fordgorod is 72. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The population of Galininograd is 23. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The population of Puotorsk is 41. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The population of Getarovo is 229. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The population of Bripetrsk is 4. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. If the area of X is smaller than 600000 square kilometers then X is minor.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"How many minor provinces are there?","answer":"3"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition","counting"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is a province in Bievorsk. There are 7 provinces. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. The population of Voronolga is 101. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The population of Abdorostan is 67. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The population of Fordgorod is 72. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The population of Galininograd is 23. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The population of Puotorsk is 41. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The population of Getarovo is 22. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The population of Bripetrsk is 4. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. If the area of X is smaller than 1000000 square kilometers then X is minor.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"How many minor provinces are there?","answer":"6"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition","counting"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is a province in Bievorsk. There are 7 provinces. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. The population of Voronolga is 10. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The population of Abdorostan is 67. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The population of Fordgorod is 72. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The population of Galininograd is 23. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The population of Puotorsk is 41. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The population of Getarovo is 22. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The population of Bripetrsk is 4. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. If the area of X is smaller than 500000 square kilometers then X is minor.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"How many minor provinces are there?","answer":"2"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition","counting"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is a province in Bievorsk. There are 7 provinces. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The population of Abdorostan is 6712302. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. If the area of X is smaller than 100000 square kilometers then X is not big.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the number of provinces that are not big?","answer":"0"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition","negation","counting"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is a province in Bievorsk. There are 7 provinces. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The population of Abdorostan is 6712302. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The population of Getarovo is 2912062. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. If the area of X is smaller than 500000 square kilometers then X is not big.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the number of provinces that are not big?","answer":"2"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition","negation","counting"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is a province in Bievorsk. There are 7 provinces. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. The population of Voronolga is 101. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The population of Abdorostan is 67. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The population of Fordgorod is 72. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The population of Galininograd is 23. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The population of Puotorsk is 41. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The population of Getarovo is 229. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The population of Bripetrsk is 4. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. If the area of X is smaller than 600000 square kilometers then X is not big.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the number of provinces that are not big?","answer":"3"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition","negation","counting"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is a province in Bievorsk. There are 7 provinces. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. The population of Voronolga is 101. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The population of Abdorostan is 67. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The population of Fordgorod is 72. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The population of Galininograd is 23. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The population of Puotorsk is 41. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The population of Getarovo is 22. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The population of Bripetrsk is 4. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. If the area of X is smaller than 1000000 square kilometers then X is not big.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the number of provinces that are not big?","answer":"6"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition","negation","counting"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is a province in Bievorsk. There are 7 provinces. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. The population of Voronolga is 10. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The population of Abdorostan is 67. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The population of Fordgorod is 72. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The population of Galininograd is 23. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The population of Puotorsk is 41. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The population of Getarovo is 22. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The population of Bripetrsk is 4. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. If the area of X is smaller than 500000 square kilometers then X is not big.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the number of provinces that are not big?","answer":"2"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition","negation","counting"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 6712302. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What provinces border the province with the highest population?","answer":"Bripetrsk, Galininograd, Puotorsk, Voronolga"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","superlative"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 6712302. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 2291206. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What provinces border the province with the highest population?","answer":"Abdorostan, Galininograd, Getarovo, Fordgorod, Puotorsk"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","superlative"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 1017829. The population of Abdorostan is 6712302. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 2291206. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What provinces border the province with the highest population?","answer":"Abdorostan, Bripetrsk, Galininograd"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","superlative"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 6712302. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 41290800. There are 7 provinces.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What provinces border the province with the highest population?","answer":"Fordgorod, Galininograd, Getarovo"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","superlative"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What provinces border the province with the highest population?","answer":"Fordgorod, Voronolga"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","superlative"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 6712302. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What provinces border the province with the highest population?","answer":"Bripetrsk, Galininograd, Puotorsk, Voronolga"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","superlative"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 6712302. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 2291206. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What provinces border the province with the highest population?","answer":"Abdorostan, Galininograd, Getarovo, Fordgorod, Puotorsk"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","superlative"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 1017829. The population of Abdorostan is 6712302. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 2291206. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What provinces border the province with the highest population?","answer":"Abdorostan, Bripetrsk, Galininograd"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","superlative"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 6712302. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 41290800. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What provinces border the province with the highest population?","answer":"Fordgorod, Galininograd, Getarovo"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","superlative"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What provinces border the province with the highest population?","answer":"Fordgorod, Voronolga"}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition","superlative"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is a province in Bievorsk. There are 7 provinces. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The population of Abdorostan is 6712302. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the most populous province?","answer":"Getarovo"}},"flags":["superlative"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is a province in Bievorsk. There are 7 provinces. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The population of Abdorostan is 6712302. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The population of Getarovo is 2912062. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the most populous province?","answer":"Voronolga"}},"flags":["superlative"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is a province in Bievorsk. There are 7 provinces. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. The population of Voronolga is 101. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The population of Abdorostan is 67. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The population of Fordgorod is 72. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The population of Galininograd is 23. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The population of Puotorsk is 41. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The population of Getarovo is 229. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The population of Bripetrsk is 4. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the most populous province?","answer":"Getarovo"}},"flags":["superlative"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is a province in Bievorsk. There are 7 provinces. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. The population of Voronolga is 101. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The population of Abdorostan is 67. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The population of Fordgorod is 72. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The population of Galininograd is 23. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The population of Puotorsk is 41. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The population of Getarovo is 22. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The population of Bripetrsk is 4. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the most populous province?","answer":"Voronolga"}},"flags":["superlative"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is a province in Bievorsk. There are 7 provinces. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. The population of Voronolga is 10. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The population of Abdorostan is 67. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The population of Fordgorod is 72. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The population of Galininograd is 23. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The population of Puotorsk is 41. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The population of Getarovo is 22. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The population of Bripetrsk is 4. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the most populous province?","answer":"Fordgorod"}},"flags":["superlative"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is a province in Bievorsk. There are 7 provinces. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The population of Abdorostan is 6712302. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the least populous province?","answer":"Puotorsk"}},"flags":["superlative"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is a province in Bievorsk. There are 7 provinces. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The population of Abdorostan is 6712302. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The population of Getarovo is 2912062. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the least populous province?","answer":"Puotorsk"}},"flags":["superlative"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is a province in Bievorsk. There are 7 provinces. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. The population of Voronolga is 101. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The population of Abdorostan is 67. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The population of Fordgorod is 72. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The population of Galininograd is 23. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The population of Puotorsk is 41. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The population of Getarovo is 229. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The population of Bripetrsk is 4. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the least populous province?","answer":"Bripetrsk"}},"flags":["superlative"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is a province in Bievorsk. There are 7 provinces. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. The population of Voronolga is 101. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The population of Abdorostan is 67. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The population of Fordgorod is 72. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The population of Galininograd is 23. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The population of Puotorsk is 41. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The population of Getarovo is 22. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The population of Bripetrsk is 4. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the least populous province?","answer":"Bripetrsk"}},"flags":["superlative"]}
{"theory":"Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is a province in Bievorsk. There are 7 provinces. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. The population of Voronolga is 10. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The population of Abdorostan is 67. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The population of Fordgorod is 72. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The population of Galininograd is 23. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The population of Puotorsk is 41. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The population of Getarovo is 22. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The population of Bripetrsk is 4. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the least populous province?","answer":"Bripetrsk"}},"flags":["superlative"]}
{"theory":"The Merasardu River is a river in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is a river in Efanangole. The Mbalam is a river in Bolurofi. The Kolufori River is a river in Efanangole. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 432 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 218 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 587 kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the length of the Kolufori River?","answer":"587","answer_templates":["{0} kilometers", "{0} km", "{0} km."]}}}
{"theory":"The Merasardu River is a river in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is a river in Efanangole. The Mbalam is a river in Bolurofi. The Kolufori River is a river in Efanangole. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 61 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 12 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 92 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 58 kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the length of the Merasardu River?","answer":"61","answer_templates":["{0} kilometers", "{0} km", "{0} km."]}}}
{"theory":"The Merasardu River is a river in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is a river in Efanangole. The Mbalam is a river in Bolurofi. The Kolufori River is a river in Efanangole. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 3049 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 6128 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 9587 kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the length of the Kolufori?","answer":"9587","answer_templates":["{0} kilometers", "{0} km", "{0} km."]}}}
{"theory":"The Merasardu River is a river in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is a river in Bolurofi. The Mbalam is a river in Bolurofi. The Kolufori River is a river in Efanangole. There are 2 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 3049 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 6128 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 913 kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the length of the Merasardu River?","answer":"3049","answer_templates":["{0} kilometers", "{0} km", "{0} km."]}}}
{"theory":"The Merasardu River is a river in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is a river in Bolurofi. The Mbalam is a river in Bolurofi. The Kolufori River is a river in Efanangole. There are 2 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 13 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 21 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 7 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 91 kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the length of the Kolufori River?","answer":"91","answer_templates":["{0} kilometers", "{0} km", "{0} km."]}}}
{"theory":"If X is in Y and Y is in Z, then X is in Z. The Merasardu River is a river in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is a river in the state of Merafagole. Merafagole is a state in Efanangole. The Mbalam is a river in Bolurofi. The Kolufori River is a river in Efanangole. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 432 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 218 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 587 kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the length of the Kolufori River?","answer":"587","answer_templates":["{0} kilometers", "{0} km", "{0} km."]}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"If X is in Y and Y is in Z, then X is in Z. The Merasardu River is a river in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is a river in the state of Merafagole. Merafagole is a state in Efanangole. The Mbalam is a river in Bolurofi. The Kolufori River is a river in Efanangole. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 61 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 12 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 92 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 58 kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the length of the Merasardu River?","answer":"61","answer_templates":["{0} kilometers", "{0} km", "{0} km."]}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"If X is in Y and Y is in Z, then X is in Z. The Merasardu River is a river in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is a river in the state of Merafagole. Merafagole is a state in Efanangole. The Mbalam is a river in Bolurofi. The Kolufori River is a river in Efanangole. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 3049 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 6128 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 9587 kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the length of the Kolufori River?","answer":"9587","answer_templates":["{0} kilometers", "{0} km", "{0} km."]}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"If X is in Y and Y is in Z, then X is in Z. The Merasardu River is a river in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is a river in the state of Merafagole. Merafagole is a state in Bolurofi. The Mbalam is a river in Bolurofi. The Kolufori River is a river in Efanangole. There are 2 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 3049 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 6128 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 913 kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the length of the Merasardu River?","answer":"3049","answer_templates":["{0} kilometers", "{0} km", "{0} km."]}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"If X is in Y and Y is in Z, then X is in Z. The Merasardu River is a river in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is a river in the state of Merafagole. Merafagole is a state in Bolurofi. The Mbalam is a river in Bolurofi. The Kolufori River is a river in Efanangole. There are 2 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 13 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 21 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 7 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 91 kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the length of the Kolufori River?","answer":"91","answer_templates":["{0} kilometers", "{0} km", "{0} km."]}},"flags":["objective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"Kangoyaken is a state in Gyoshoru. Gunmaishyu is one of the 4 states in Gyoshoru. Ibarakishyo is a state in Gyoshoru. Toyusuma is a state in Dogoreoku. Senkuoka is a state in Gyoshoru. The area of Kangoyaken is 3507 square kilometers. The area of Senkuoka is 4216 square kilometers. The area of Toyusuma is 4198 square kilometers. The area of Ibarakishyo is 9108 square kilometers. The area of Gunmaishyu is 82987 square kilometers. The population of Gunmaishyu is 5218607. The population of Senkuoka is 1027862. The population of Ibarakishyo is 419272. The population of Kangoyaken is 89703. The population of Toyusuma is 19272. The population density of X is the population of X divided by the area of X. If the population density of X is greater than 200, X is dense.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the dense states in Gyoshoru?","answer":"Senkuoka"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition","objective_concept_definition","arithmetic"]}
{"theory":"Kangoyaken is a state in Gyoshoru. Gunmaishyu is one of the 4 states in Gyoshoru. Ibarakishyo is a state in Gyoshoru. Toyusuma is a state in Dogoreoku. Senkuoka is a state in Gyoshoru. The area of Kangoyaken is 3507 square kilometers. The area of Senkuoka is 4216 square kilometers. The area of Toyusuma is 4198 square kilometers. The area of Ibarakishyo is 9108 square kilometers. The area of Gunmaishyu is 82987 square kilometers. The population of Gunmaishyu is 5218607. The population of Senkuoka is 1027862. The population of Ibarakishyo is 419272. The population of Kangoyaken is 89703. The population of Toyusuma is 19272. The population density of X is the population of X divided by the area of X. If the population density of X is greater than 60, X is dense.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the dense states in Gyoshoru?","answer":"Gunmaishyu, Senkuoka"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition","objective_concept_definition","arithmetic"]}
{"theory":"Kangoyaken is a state in Gyoshoru. Gunmaishyu is one of the 4 states in Gyoshoru. Ibarakishyo is a state in Gyoshoru. Toyusuma is a state in Dogoreoku. Senkuoka is a state in Gyoshoru. The area of Kangoyaken is 3507 square kilometers. The area of Senkuoka is 4216 square kilometers. The area of Toyusuma is 4198 square kilometers. The area of Ibarakishyo is 9108 square kilometers. The area of Gunmaishyu is 82987 square kilometers. The population of Gunmaishyu is 5218607. The population of Senkuoka is 1027862. The population of Ibarakishyo is 419272. The population of Kangoyaken is 89703. The population of Toyusuma is 19272. The population density of X is the population of X divided by the area of X. If the population density of X is greater than 40, X is dense.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the dense states in Gyoshoru?","answer":"Gunmaishyu, Ibarakishyo, Senkuoka"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition","objective_concept_definition","arithmetic"]}
{"theory":"Kangoyaken is a state in Gyoshoru. Gunmaishyu is one of the 4 states in Gyoshoru. Ibarakishyo is a state in Gyoshoru. Toyusuma is a state in Dogoreoku. Senkuoka is a state in Gyoshoru. The area of Kangoyaken is 3507 square kilometers. The area of Senkuoka is 4216 square kilometers. The area of Toyusuma is 4198 square kilometers. The area of Ibarakishyo is 9108 square kilometers. The area of Gunmaishyu is 82987 square kilometers. The population of Gunmaishyu is 5218607. The population of Senkuoka is 1027862. The population of Ibarakishyo is 419272. The population of Kangoyaken is 89703. The population of Toyusuma is 19272. The population density of X is the population of X divided by the area of X. If the population density of X is greater than 20, X is dense.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the dense states in Gyoshoru?","answer":"Gunmaishyu, Ibarakishyo, Kangoyaken, Senkuoka"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition","objective_concept_definition","arithmetic"]}
{"theory":"Kangoyaken is a state in Gyoshoru. Gunmaishyu is one of the 4 states in Gyoshoru. Ibarakishyo is a state in Gyoshoru. Toyusuma is a state in Dogoreoku. Senkuoka is a state in Gyoshoru. The area of Kangoyaken is 3507 square kilometers. The area of Senkuoka is 4216 square kilometers. The area of Toyusuma is 4198 square kilometers. The area of Ibarakishyo is 9108 square kilometers. The area of Gunmaishyu is 82987 square kilometers. The population of Gunmaishyu is 5218607. The population of Senkuoka is 1027862. The population of Ibarakishyo is 419272. The population of Kangoyaken is 89703. The population of Toyusuma is 19272. The population density of X is the population of X divided by the area of X. If the population density of X is greater than 300, X is dense.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the dense states in Gyoshoru?","answer":""}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition","objective_concept_definition","arithmetic"]}
{"theory":"Kangoyaken is a state in Gyoshoru. Gunmaishyu is one of the 4 states in Gyoshoru. Ibarakishyo is a state in Gyoshoru. Toyusuma is a state in Dogoreoku. Senkuoka is a state in Gyoshoru. The area of Kangoyaken is 3507 square kilometers. The area of Senkuoka is 4216 square kilometers. The area of Toyusuma is 4198 square kilometers. The area of Ibarakishyo is 9108 square kilometers. The area of Gunmaishyu is 82987 square kilometers. The population of Gunmaishyu is 5218607. The population of Senkuoka is 1027862. The population of Ibarakishyo is 419272. The population of Kangoyaken is 89703. The population of Toyusuma is 19272. The population density of X is the population of X divided by the area of X. If the population density of X is less than 200, X is sparse.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the sparse states in Gyoshoru?","answer":"Gunmaishyu, Ibarakishyo, Kangoyaken"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition","objective_concept_definition","arithmetic"]}
{"theory":"Kangoyaken is a state in Gyoshoru. Gunmaishyu is one of the 4 states in Gyoshoru. Ibarakishyo is a state in Gyoshoru. Toyusuma is a state in Dogoreoku. Senkuoka is a state in Gyoshoru. The area of Kangoyaken is 3507 square kilometers. The area of Senkuoka is 4216 square kilometers. The area of Toyusuma is 4198 square kilometers. The area of Ibarakishyo is 9108 square kilometers. The area of Gunmaishyu is 82987 square kilometers. The population of Gunmaishyu is 5218607. The population of Senkuoka is 1027862. The population of Ibarakishyo is 419272. The population of Kangoyaken is 89703. The population of Toyusuma is 19272. The population density of X is the population of X divided by the area of X. If the population density of X is less than 60, X is sparse.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the sparse states in Gyoshoru?","answer":"Ibarakishyo, Kangoyaken"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition","objective_concept_definition","arithmetic"]}
{"theory":"Kangoyaken is a state in Gyoshoru. Gunmaishyu is one of the 4 states in Gyoshoru. Ibarakishyo is a state in Gyoshoru. Toyusuma is a state in Dogoreoku. Senkuoka is a state in Gyoshoru. The area of Kangoyaken is 3507 square kilometers. The area of Senkuoka is 4216 square kilometers. The area of Toyusuma is 4198 square kilometers. The area of Ibarakishyo is 9108 square kilometers. The area of Gunmaishyu is 82987 square kilometers. The population of Gunmaishyu is 5218607. The population of Senkuoka is 1027862. The population of Ibarakishyo is 419272. The population of Kangoyaken is 89703. The population of Toyusuma is 19272. The population density of X is the population of X divided by the area of X. If the population density of X is less than 40, X is sparse.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the sparse states in Gyoshoru?","answer":"Kangoyaken"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition","objective_concept_definition","arithmetic"]}
{"theory":"Kangoyaken is a state in Gyoshoru. Gunmaishyu is one of the 4 states in Gyoshoru. Ibarakishyo is a state in Gyoshoru. Toyusuma is a state in Dogoreoku. Senkuoka is a state in Gyoshoru. The area of Kangoyaken is 3507 square kilometers. The area of Senkuoka is 4216 square kilometers. The area of Toyusuma is 4198 square kilometers. The area of Ibarakishyo is 9108 square kilometers. The area of Gunmaishyu is 82987 square kilometers. The population of Gunmaishyu is 5218607. The population of Senkuoka is 1027862. The population of Ibarakishyo is 419272. The population of Kangoyaken is 89703. The population of Toyusuma is 19272. The population density of X is the population of X divided by the area of X. If the population density of X is less than 20, X is sparse.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the sparse states in Gyoshoru?","answer":""}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition","objective_concept_definition","arithmetic"]}
{"theory":"Kangoyaken is a state in Gyoshoru. Gunmaishyu is one of the 4 states in Gyoshoru. Ibarakishyo is a state in Gyoshoru. Toyusuma is a state in Dogoreoku. Senkuoka is a state in Gyoshoru. The area of Kangoyaken is 3507 square kilometers. The area of Senkuoka is 4216 square kilometers. The area of Toyusuma is 4198 square kilometers. The area of Ibarakishyo is 9108 square kilometers. The area of Gunmaishyu is 82987 square kilometers. The population of Gunmaishyu is 5218607. The population of Senkuoka is 1027862. The population of Ibarakishyo is 419272. The population of Kangoyaken is 89703. The population of Toyusuma is 19272. The population density of X is the population of X divided by the area of X. If the population density of X is less than 300, X is sparse.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the sparse states in Gyoshoru?","answer":"Gunmaishyu, Ibarakishyo, Kangoyaken, Senkuoka"}},"flags":["subjective_concept_definition","objective_concept_definition","arithmetic"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam is in Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River is in Kolufori. The Merasardu River is in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 432 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 218 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 587 kilometers. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which is the longest river in Efanangole?","answer":"Kolufori River"}},"flags":["large_context","superlative"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam is in Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River is in Kolufori. The Merasardu River is in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 61 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 12 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 92 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 58 kilometers. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which is the longest river in Efanangole?","answer":"Merasardu River"}},"flags":["large_context","superlative"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam is in Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River is in Kolufori. The Merasardu River is in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 3049 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 6128 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 9587 kilometers. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which is the longest river in Efanangole?","answer":"Kolufori River"}},"flags":["large_context","superlative"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam is in Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River is in Kolufori. The Merasardu River is in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is in Bolurofi. The Kolufori River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 2 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 3049 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 6128 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 913 kilometers. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which is the longest river in Efanangole?","answer":"Merasardu River"}},"flags":["large_context","superlative"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam is in Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River is in Kolufori. The Merasardu River is in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is in Bolurofi. The Kolufori River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 2 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 13 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 21 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 7 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 91 kilometers. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which is the longest river in Efanangole?","answer":"Kolufori River"}},"flags":["large_context","superlative"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam is in Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River is in Kolufori. The Merasardu River is in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 432 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 218 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 587 kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which is the longest river in Efanangole?","answer":"Kolufori River"}},"flags":["large_context","superlative"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam is in Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River is in Kolufori. The Merasardu River is in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 61 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 12 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 92 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 58 kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which is the longest river in Efanangole?","answer":"Merasardu River"}},"flags":["large_context","superlative"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam is in Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River is in Kolufori. The Merasardu River is in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 3049 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 6128 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 9587 kilometers. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which is the longest river in Efanangole?","answer":"Kolufori River"}},"flags":["large_context","superlative"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam is in Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River is in Kolufori. The Merasardu River is in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is in Bolurofi. The Kolufori River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 2 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 3049 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 6128 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 913 kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which is the longest river in Efanangole?","answer":"Merasardu River"}},"flags":["large_context","superlative"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam is in Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River is in Kolufori. The Merasardu River is in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is in Bolurofi. The Kolufori River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 2 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 13 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 21 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 7 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 91 kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"Which is the longest river in Efanangole?","answer":"Kolufori River"}},"flags":["large_context","superlative"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam runs through Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River runs through Kolufori. The Merasardu River runs through Efanangole. The Merafagole River runs through Efanangole. The Kolufori River runs through Efanangole. The Kolufori River runs through Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers that run through Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 432 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 218 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 587 kilometers. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"The Kolufori River runs through which states?","answer":"Bolurofi, Efanangole, Kolufori"}},"flags":["large_context"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam runs through Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River runs through Kolufori. The Merasardu River runs through Efanangole. The Merafagole River runs through Efanangole. The Kolufori River runs through Efanangole. The Kolufori River runs through Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers that run through Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 432 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 218 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 587 kilometers. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"The Merafagole River runs through which states?","answer":"Efanangole"}},"flags":["large_context"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam runs through Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River runs through Kolufori. The Merasardu River runs through Efanangole. The Merafagole River runs through Efanangole. The Kolufori River runs through Efanangole. The Kolufori River runs through Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers that run through Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 432 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 218 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 587 kilometers. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"The Mbalam runs through which states?","answer":"Bolurofi"}},"flags":["large_context"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam runs through Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River runs through Kolufori. The Merasardu River runs through Efanangole. The Merafagole River runs through Efanangole. The Kolufori River runs through Efanangole. The Kolufori River runs through Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers that run through Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 432 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 218 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 587 kilometers. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"The Merasardu River runs through which states?","answer":"Efanangole"}},"flags":["large_context"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam runs through Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River runs through Kolufori. The Merasardu River runs through Efanangole. The Merafagole River runs through Efanangole. The Kolufori River runs through Efanangole. The Kolufori River runs through Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers that run through Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 432 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 218 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 587 kilometers. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"The Mbalam does not run through which states?","answer":"Efanangole"}},"flags":["large_context","negation"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam runs through Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River runs through Kolufori. The Merasardu River runs through Efanangole. The Merafagole River runs through Efanangole. The Kolufori River runs through Efanangole. The Kolufori River runs through Bolurofi. If X runs through Y, then X is in Y. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers that run through Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 432 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 218 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 587 kilometers. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"The Kolufori River runs through which states?","answer":"Bolurofi, Efanangole, Kolufori"}},"flags":["large_context"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam runs through Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River runs through Kolufori. The Merasardu River runs through Efanangole. The Merafagole River runs through Efanangole. The Kolufori River runs through Efanangole. The Kolufori River runs through Bolurofi. If X runs through Y, then X is in Y. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers that run through Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 432 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 218 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 587 kilometers. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"The Merafagole River runs through which states?","answer":"Efanangole"}},"flags":["large_context"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam runs through Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River runs through Kolufori. The Merasardu River runs through Efanangole. The Merafagole River runs through Efanangole. The Kolufori River runs through Efanangole. The Kolufori River runs through Bolurofi. If X runs through Y, then X is in Y. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers that run through Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 432 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 218 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 587 kilometers. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"The Mbalam runs through which states?","answer":"Bolurofi"}},"flags":["large_context"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam runs through Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River runs through Kolufori. The Merasardu River runs through Efanangole. The Merafagole River runs through Efanangole. The Kolufori River runs through Efanangole. The Kolufori River runs through Bolurofi. If X runs through Y, then X is in Y. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers that run through Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 432 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 218 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 587 kilometers. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"The Merasardu River runs through which states?","answer":"Efanangole"}},"flags":["large_context"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam runs through Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River runs through Kolufori. The Merasardu River runs through Efanangole. The Merafagole River runs through Efanangole. The Kolufori River runs through Efanangole. The Kolufori River runs through Bolurofi. If X does not run through Y, then X is not in Y. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers that run through Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 432 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 218 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 587 kilometers. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"The Mbalam does not run through which states?","answer":"Efanangole"}},"flags":["large_context","negation"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam is in Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River is in Kolufori. The Merasardu River is in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 432 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 218 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 587 kilometers. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"The Voronolga runs through what provinces?","answer":"Bripetrsk, Galininograd, Puotorsk, Voronolga"}},"flags":["large_context"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam is in Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River is in Kolufori. The Merasardu River is in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 432 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 218 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 587 kilometers. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"The Kolonolga runs through what provinces?","answer":"Bripetrsk, Getarovo, Puotorsk"}},"flags":["large_context"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam is in Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River is in Kolufori. The Merasardu River is in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 432 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 218 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 587 kilometers. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"The Karbankaya runs through what provinces?","answer":"Abdorostan, Voronolga"}},"flags":["large_context"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam is in Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River is in Kolufori. The Merasardu River is in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 432 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 218 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 587 kilometers. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"The Chetershka runs through what provinces?","answer":"Fordgorod"}},"flags":["large_context"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam is in Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River is in Kolufori. The Merasardu River is in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 432 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 218 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 587 kilometers. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"The Brasyugan runs through what provinces?","answer":"Puotorsk"}},"flags":["large_context"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam is in Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River is in Kolufori. The Merasardu River is in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 432 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 218 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 587 kilometers. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"The Voronolga runs through what provinces?","answer":"Bripetrsk, Galininograd, Puotorsk, Voronolga"}},"flags":["large_context"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam is in Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River is in Kolufori. The Merasardu River is in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 432 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 218 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 587 kilometers. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"The Kolonolga runs through what provinces?","answer":"Bripetrsk, Getarovo, Puotorsk"}},"flags":["large_context"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam is in Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River is in Kolufori. The Merasardu River is in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 432 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 218 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 587 kilometers. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"The Karbankaya runs through what provinces?","answer":"Abdorostan, Voronolga"}},"flags":["large_context"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam is in Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River is in Kolufori. The Merasardu River is in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 432 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 218 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 587 kilometers. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"The Chetershka runs through what provinces?","answer":"Fordgorod"}},"flags":["large_context"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam is in Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River is in Kolufori. The Merasardu River is in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 432 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 218 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 587 kilometers. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"The Brasyugan runs through what provinces?","answer":"Puotorsk"}},"flags":["large_context"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam is in Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River is in Kolufori. The Merasardu River is in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 432 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 218 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 587 kilometers. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the capital of states that have cities named Baritolloti?","answer":"Baritolloti","answer_templates":["{0} is the capital city of Grappulia.", "{0} is the capital of Grappulia."]}},"flags":["large_context","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam is in Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River is in Kolufori. The Merasardu River is in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 432 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 218 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 587 kilometers. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the capital of states that have cities named Lomberona?","answer":"Messinitina","answer_templates":["{0} is a city in Regnobenoa.", "The capital city of Regnobenoa is {0}.", "The capital of Regnobenoa is {0}."]}},"flags":["large_context","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam is in Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River is in Kolufori. The Merasardu River is in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 432 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 218 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 587 kilometers. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the capital of states that have cities named Lomtrieste?","answer":"Albucapua","answer_templates":["{0} is the capital city of Bascilitina.", "{0} is the capital of Bascilitina."]}},"flags":["large_context","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam is in Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River is in Kolufori. The Merasardu River is in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 432 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 218 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 587 kilometers. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the capital of states that have cities named Albucapua?","answer":"Albucapua","answer_templates":["{0} is the capital city of Bascilitina.", "{0} is the capital of Bascilitina."]}},"flags":["large_context","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam is in Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River is in Kolufori. The Merasardu River is in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 432 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 218 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 587 kilometers. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the capital of states that have cities named Brescitabia?","answer":"Geoturin","answer_templates":["{0} is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan.", "{0} is the capital of the state of Cartabitan."]}},"flags":["large_context","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam is in Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River is in Kolufori. The Merasardu River is in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 432 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 218 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 587 kilometers. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. Lomberona is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the capital of states that have cities named Lomberona?","answer":"Geoturin, Messinitina"}},"flags":["large_context","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam is in Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River is in Kolufori. The Merasardu River is in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 432 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 218 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 587 kilometers. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. Lomberona is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the capital of states that have cities named Veronizzia?","answer":"Geoturin","answer_templates":["{0} is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan.", "{0} is the capital of the state of Cartabitan."]}},"flags":["large_context","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam is in Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River is in Kolufori. The Merasardu River is in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 432 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 218 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 587 kilometers. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. Lomberona is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the capital of states that have cities named Baritolloti?","answer":"Baritolloti","answer_templates":["{0} is the capital city of Grappulia.", "{0} is the capital of Grappulia."]}},"flags":["large_context","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam is in Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River is in Kolufori. The Merasardu River is in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 432 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 218 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 587 kilometers. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. Lomberona is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the capital of states that have cities named Lomtrieste?","answer":"Albucapua","answer_templates":["{0} is the capital city of Bascilitina.", "{0} is the capital of Bascilitina."]}},"flags":["large_context","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam is in Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River is in Kolufori. The Merasardu River is in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 432 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 218 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 587 kilometers. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. Lomberona is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the capital of states that have cities named Geoturin?","answer":"Geoturin","answer_templates":["{0} is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan.", "{0} is the capital of the state of Cartabitan."]}},"flags":["large_context","lexical_ambiguity"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam is in Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River is in Kolufori. The Merasardu River is in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 432 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 218 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 587 kilometers. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"How long is the longest river in Efanangole?","answer":"587","answer_templates":["{0} kilometers", "{0} km", "{0} km.", "The length of the Kolufori River is {0} kilometers."]}},"flags":["large_context","superlative"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam is in Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River is in Kolufori. The Merasardu River is in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 61 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 12 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 92 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 58 kilometers. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"How long is the longest river in Efanangole?","answer":"61","answer_templates":["{0} kilometers", "{0} km", "{0} km.", "The length of the Merasardu River is {0} kilometers."]}},"flags":["large_context","superlative"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam is in Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River is in Kolufori. The Merasardu River is in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 3049 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 6128 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 9587 kilometers. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"How long is the longest river in Efanangole?","answer":"9587","answer_templates":["{0} kilometers", "{0} km", "{0} km.", "The length of the Kolufori River is {0} kilometers."]}},"flags":["large_context","superlative"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam is in Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River is in Kolufori. The Merasardu River is in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is in Bolurofi. The Kolufori River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 2 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 3049 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 6128 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 913 kilometers. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"How long is the longest river in Efanangole?","answer":"3049","answer_templates":["{0} kilometers", "{0} km", "{0} km.", "The length of the Merasardu River is {0} kilometers."]}},"flags":["large_context","superlative"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam is in Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River is in Kolufori. The Merasardu River is in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is in Bolurofi. The Kolufori River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 2 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 13 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 21 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 7 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 91 kilometers. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"How long is the longest river in Efanangole?","answer":"91","answer_templates":["{0} kilometers", "{0} km", "{0} km.", "The length of the Kolufori River is {0} kilometers."]}},"flags":["large_context","superlative"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam is in Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River is in Kolufori. The Merasardu River is in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 432 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 218 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 587 kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"How long is the longest river in Efanangole?","answer":"587","answer_templates":["{0} kilometers", "{0} km", "{0} km.", "The length of the Kolufori River is {0} kilometers."]}},"flags":["large_context","superlative"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam is in Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River is in Kolufori. The Merasardu River is in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 61 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 12 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 92 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 58 kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"How long is the longest river in Efanangole?","answer":"61","answer_templates":["{0} kilometers", "{0} km", "{0} km.", "The length of the Merasardu River is {0} kilometers."]}},"flags":["large_context","superlative"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam is in Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River is in Kolufori. The Merasardu River is in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 3049 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 6128 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 9587 kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"How long is the longest river in Efanangole?","answer":"9587","answer_templates":["{0} kilometers", "{0} km", "{0} km.", "The length of the Kolufori River is {0} kilometers."]}},"flags":["large_context","superlative"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam is in Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River is in Kolufori. The Merasardu River is in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is in Bolurofi. The Kolufori River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 2 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 3049 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 6128 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 913 kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"How long is the longest river in Efanangole?","answer":"3049","answer_templates":["{0} kilometers", "{0} km", "{0} km.", "The length of the Merasardu River is {0} kilometers."]}},"flags":["large_context","superlative"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam is in Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River is in Kolufori. The Merasardu River is in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is in Bolurofi. The Kolufori River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 2 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 13 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 21 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 7 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 91 kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"How long is the longest river in Efanangole?","answer":"91","answer_templates":["{0} kilometers", "{0} km", "{0} km.", "The length of the Kolufori River is {0} kilometers."]}},"flags":["large_context","superlative"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam is in Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River is in Kolufori. The Merasardu River is in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 432 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 218 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 587 kilometers. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the minor provinces?","answer":""}},"flags":["large_context","subjective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam is in Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River is in Kolufori. The Merasardu River is in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 432 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 218 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 587 kilometers. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 500000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the minor provinces?","answer":"Bripetrsk, Puotorsk"}},"flags":["large_context","subjective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam is in Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River is in Kolufori. The Merasardu River is in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 432 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 218 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 587 kilometers. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 3000000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the minor provinces?","answer":"Bripetrsk, Galininograd, Puotorsk"}},"flags":["large_context","subjective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam is in Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River is in Kolufori. The Merasardu River is in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 432 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 218 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 587 kilometers. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 10000000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the minor provinces?","answer":"Bripetrsk, Fordgorod, Galininograd, Puotorsk"}},"flags":["large_context","subjective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam is in Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River is in Kolufori. The Merasardu River is in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 432 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 218 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 587 kilometers. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 15000000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the minor provinces?","answer":"Bripetrsk, Fordgorod, Galininograd, Puotorsk, Voronolga"}},"flags":["large_context","subjective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam is in Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River is in Kolufori. The Merasardu River is in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 432 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 218 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 587 kilometers. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is not big. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the provinces that are not big?","answer":""}},"flags":["large_context","subjective_concept_definition","negation"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam is in Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River is in Kolufori. The Merasardu River is in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 432 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 218 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 587 kilometers. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 500000 then X is not big. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the provinces that are not big?","answer":"Bripetrsk, Puotorsk"}},"flags":["large_context","subjective_concept_definition","negation"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam is in Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River is in Kolufori. The Merasardu River is in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 432 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 218 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 587 kilometers. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 3000000 then X is not big. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the provinces that are not big?","answer":"Bripetrsk, Galininograd, Puotorsk"}},"flags":["large_context","subjective_concept_definition","negation"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam is in Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River is in Kolufori. The Merasardu River is in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 432 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 218 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 587 kilometers. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 10000000 then X is not big. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the provinces that are not big?","answer":"Bripetrsk, Fordgorod, Galininograd, Puotorsk"}},"flags":["large_context","subjective_concept_definition","negation"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam is in Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River is in Kolufori. The Merasardu River is in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 432 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 218 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 587 kilometers. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 15000000 then X is not big. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the provinces that are not big?","answer":"Bripetrsk, Fordgorod, Galininograd, Puotorsk, Voronolga"}},"flags":["large_context","subjective_concept_definition","negation"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam is in Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River is in Kolufori. The Merasardu River is in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 432 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 218 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 587 kilometers. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the minor provinces?","answer":""}},"flags":["large_context","subjective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam is in Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River is in Kolufori. The Merasardu River is in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 432 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 218 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 587 kilometers. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 500000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the minor provinces?","answer":"Bripetrsk, Puotorsk"}},"flags":["large_context","subjective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam is in Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River is in Kolufori. The Merasardu River is in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 432 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 218 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 587 kilometers. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 3000000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the minor provinces?","answer":"Bripetrsk, Galininograd, Puotorsk"}},"flags":["large_context","subjective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam is in Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River is in Kolufori. The Merasardu River is in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 432 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 218 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 587 kilometers. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 10000000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the minor provinces?","answer":"Bripetrsk, Fordgorod, Galininograd, Puotorsk"}},"flags":["large_context","subjective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam is in Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River is in Kolufori. The Merasardu River is in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 432 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 218 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 587 kilometers. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 15000000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the minor provinces?","answer":"Bripetrsk, Fordgorod, Galininograd, Puotorsk, Voronolga"}},"flags":["large_context","subjective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam is in Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River is in Kolufori. The Merasardu River is in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 432 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 218 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 587 kilometers. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is not big. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the provinces that are not big?","answer":""}},"flags":["large_context","subjective_concept_definition","negation"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam is in Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River is in Kolufori. The Merasardu River is in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 432 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 218 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 587 kilometers. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 500000 then X is not big. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the provinces that are not big?","answer":"Bripetrsk, Puotorsk"}},"flags":["large_context","subjective_concept_definition","negation"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam is in Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River is in Kolufori. The Merasardu River is in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 432 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 218 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 587 kilometers. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 3000000 then X is not big. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the provinces that are not big?","answer":"Bripetrsk, Galininograd, Puotorsk"}},"flags":["large_context","subjective_concept_definition","negation"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam is in Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River is in Kolufori. The Merasardu River is in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 432 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 218 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 587 kilometers. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 10000000 then X is not big. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the provinces that are not big?","answer":"Bripetrsk, Fordgorod, Galininograd, Puotorsk"}},"flags":["large_context","subjective_concept_definition","negation"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam is in Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River is in Kolufori. The Merasardu River is in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 432 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 218 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 587 kilometers. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 15000000 then X is not big. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the provinces that are not big?","answer":"Bripetrsk, Fordgorod, Galininograd, Puotorsk, Voronolga"}},"flags":["large_context","subjective_concept_definition","negation"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam is in Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River is in Kolufori. The Merasardu River is in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 432 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 218 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 587 kilometers. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the length of the Kolufori River?","answer":"587","answer_templates":["{0} kilometers", "{0} km", "{0} km."]}},"flags":["large_context"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam is in Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River is in Kolufori. The Merasardu River is in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 61 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 12 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 92 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 58 kilometers. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the length of the Merasardu River?","answer":"61","answer_templates":["{0} kilometers", "{0} km", "{0} km."]}},"flags":["large_context"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam is in Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River is in Kolufori. The Merasardu River is in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 3049 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 6128 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 9587 kilometers. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the length of the Kolufori River?","answer":"9587","answer_templates":["{0} kilometers", "{0} km", "{0} km."]}},"flags":["large_context"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam runs through Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River runs through Kolufori. The Merasardu River runs through Bolurofi. The Merafagole River runs through Efanangole. The Kolufori River runs through Efanangole. The Kolufori River runs through Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers that run through Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 3049 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 6128 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 913 kilometers. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the length of the Merasardu River?","answer":"3049","answer_templates":["{0} kilometers", "{0} km", "{0} km."]}},"flags":["large_context"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam runs through Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River runs through Kolufori. The Merasardu River runs through Bolurofi. The Merafagole River runs through Efanangole. The Kolufori River runs through Efanangole. The Kolufori River runs through Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers that run through Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 13 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 21 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 7 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 91 kilometers. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the length of the Kolufori River?","answer":"91","answer_templates":["{0} kilometers", "{0} km", "{0} km."]}},"flags":["large_context"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam is in Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River is in Kolufori. The Merasardu River is in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 432 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 218 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 587 kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the length of the Kolufori River?","answer":"587","answer_templates":["{0} kilometers", "{0} km", "{0} km."]}},"flags":["large_context"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam is in Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River is in Kolufori. The Merasardu River is in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 61 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 12 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 92 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 58 kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the length of the Merasardu River?","answer":"61","answer_templates":["{0} kilometers", "{0} km", "{0} km."]}},"flags":["large_context"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam is in Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River is in Kolufori. The Merasardu River is in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 3049 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 6128 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 9587 kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the length of the Kolufori River?","answer":"9587","answer_templates":["{0} kilometers", "{0} km", "{0} km."]}},"flags":["large_context"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam runs through Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River runs through Kolufori. The Merasardu River runs through Bolurofi. The Merafagole River runs through Efanangole. The Kolufori River runs through Efanangole. The Kolufori River runs through Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers that run through Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 3049 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 6128 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 913 kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the length of the Merasardu River?","answer":"3049","answer_templates":["{0} kilometers", "{0} km", "{0} km."]}},"flags":["large_context"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam runs through Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River runs through Kolufori. The Merasardu River runs through Bolurofi. The Merafagole River runs through Efanangole. The Kolufori River runs through Efanangole. The Kolufori River runs through Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers that run through Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 13 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 21 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 7 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 91 kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What is the length of the Kolufori River?","answer":"91","answer_templates":["{0} kilometers", "{0} km", "{0} km."]}},"flags":["large_context"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam is in Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River is in Kolufori. The Merasardu River is in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 432 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 218 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 587 kilometers. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"How long is the Kolufori River?","answer":"587","answer_templates":["{0} kilometers", "{0} km", "{0} km."]}},"flags":["large_context"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam is in Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River is in Kolufori. The Merasardu River is in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 61 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 12 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 92 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 58 kilometers. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"How long is the Merasardu River?","answer":"61","answer_templates":["{0} kilometers", "{0} km", "{0} km."]}},"flags":["large_context"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam is in Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River is in Kolufori. The Merasardu River is in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 3049 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 6128 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 9587 kilometers. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"How long is the Kolufori River?","answer":"9587","answer_templates":["{0} kilometers", "{0} km", "{0} km."]}},"flags":["large_context"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam runs through Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River runs through Kolufori. The Merasardu River runs through Bolurofi. The Merafagole River runs through Efanangole. The Kolufori River runs through Efanangole. The Kolufori River runs through Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers that run through Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 3049 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 6128 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 913 kilometers. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"How long is the Merasardu River?","answer":"3049","answer_templates":["{0} kilometers", "{0} km", "{0} km."]}},"flags":["large_context"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam runs through Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River runs through Kolufori. The Merasardu River runs through Bolurofi. The Merafagole River runs through Efanangole. The Kolufori River runs through Efanangole. The Kolufori River runs through Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers that run through Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 13 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 21 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 7 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 91 kilometers. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"How long is the Kolufori River?","answer":"91","answer_templates":["{0} kilometers", "{0} km", "{0} km."]}},"flags":["large_context"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam is in Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River is in Kolufori. The Merasardu River is in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 432 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 218 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 587 kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"How long is the Kolufori River?","answer":"587","answer_templates":["{0} kilometers", "{0} km", "{0} km."]}},"flags":["large_context"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam is in Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River is in Kolufori. The Merasardu River is in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 61 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 12 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 92 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 58 kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"How long is the Merasardu River?","answer":"61","answer_templates":["{0} kilometers", "{0} km", "{0} km."]}},"flags":["large_context"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam is in Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River is in Kolufori. The Merasardu River is in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 3049 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 6128 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 9587 kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"How long is the Kolufori River?","answer":"9587","answer_templates":["{0} kilometers", "{0} km", "{0} km."]}},"flags":["large_context"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam runs through Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River runs through Kolufori. The Merasardu River runs through Bolurofi. The Merafagole River runs through Efanangole. The Kolufori River runs through Efanangole. The Kolufori River runs through Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers that run through Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 3049 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 6128 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 913 kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"How long is the Merasardu River?","answer":"3049","answer_templates":["{0} kilometers", "{0} km", "{0} km."]}},"flags":["large_context"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam runs through Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River runs through Kolufori. The Merasardu River runs through Bolurofi. The Merafagole River runs through Efanangole. The Kolufori River runs through Efanangole. The Kolufori River runs through Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers that run through Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 13 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 21 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 7 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 91 kilometers.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"How long is the Kolufori River?","answer":"91","answer_templates":["{0} kilometers", "{0} km", "{0} km."]}},"flags":["large_context"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam is in Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River is in Kolufori. The Merasardu River is in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 432 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 218 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 587 kilometers. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka. If the population of X is greater than 150000, X is major.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the major cities in Kangoyaken?","answer":"Dogayashi, Kagenegawa, Kyoukashino"}},"flags":["large_context","subjective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam is in Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River is in Kolufori. The Merasardu River is in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 432 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 218 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 587 kilometers. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka. If the population of X is greater than 250000, X is major.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the major cities in Kangoyaken?","answer":"Dogayashi, Kagenegawa"}},"flags":["large_context","subjective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam is in Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River is in Kolufori. The Merasardu River is in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 432 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 218 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 587 kilometers. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka. If the population of X is greater than 1000000, X is major.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the major cities in Kangoyaken?","answer":"Dogayashi"}},"flags":["large_context","subjective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam is in Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River is in Kolufori. The Merasardu River is in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 432 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 218 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 587 kilometers. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka. If the population of X is greater than 100000, X is major.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the major cities in Kangoyaken?","answer":"Dogayashi, Kagenegawa, Koruhashi, Kyoukashino"}},"flags":["large_context","subjective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam is in Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River is in Kolufori. The Merasardu River is in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 432 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 218 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 587 kilometers. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka. If the population of X is greater than 20000, X is major.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What are the major cities in Kangoyaken?","answer":"Agarikoshi, Dogayashi, Kagenegawa, Koruhashi, Kyoukashino"}},"flags":["large_context","subjective_concept_definition"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam is in Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River is in Kolufori. The Merasardu River is in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 432 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 218 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 587 kilometers. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka. If the population of X is less than 150000, X is not major.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What cities in Kangoyaken are not major?","answer":"Dogayashi, Kagenegawa, Kyoukashino"}},"flags":["large_context","subjective_concept_definition","negation"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam is in Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River is in Kolufori. The Merasardu River is in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 432 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 218 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 587 kilometers. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka. If the population of X is less than 250000, X is not major.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What cities in Kangoyaken are not major?","answer":"Dogayashi, Kagenegawa"}},"flags":["large_context","subjective_concept_definition","negation"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam is in Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River is in Kolufori. The Merasardu River is in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 432 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 218 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 587 kilometers. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka. If the population of X is less than 1000000, X is not major.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What cities in Kangoyaken are not major?","answer":"Dogayashi"}},"flags":["large_context","subjective_concept_definition","negation"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam is in Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River is in Kolufori. The Merasardu River is in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 432 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 218 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 587 kilometers. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka. If the population of X is less than 100000, X is not major.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What cities in Kangoyaken are not major?","answer":"Dogayashi, Kagenegawa, Koruhashi, Kyoukashino"}},"flags":["large_context","subjective_concept_definition","negation"]}
{"theory":"Mofubali is a country. Catardinia is a country. Bievorsk is a country. The Merasardu River is a river in Mofubali. Efanangole is a state in Mofubali. The Merafagole River is a river in Mofubali. Bolurofi is a state in Mofubali. The Mbalam is a river in Mofubali. The Mbalam is in Bolurofi. The Mbalam does not run through Efanangole. The Kolufori River is a river in Mofubali. Kolufori is a state in Mofubali. The Kolufori River is in Kolufori. The Merasardu River is in Efanangole. The Merafagole River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Efanangole. The Kolufori River is in Bolurofi. The population of Efanangole is 1420892. The population of Bolurofi is 9021832. The population of Kolufori is 812390. There are 3 rivers in Efanangole. The length of the Merasardu River is 432 kilometers. The length of the Merafagole River is 218 kilometers. The length of the Mbalam River is 1297 kilometers. The length of the Kolufori River is 587 kilometers. Voronolga is a province in Bievorsk. Abdorostan is a province in Bievorsk. Fordgorod is one of the 7 provinces in Bievorsk. Galininograd is a province in Bievorsk. Puotorsk is a province in Bievorsk. Getarovo is a province in Bievorsk. Bripetrsk is a province in Bievorsk. Voronolga borders Puotorsk. Galininograd borders Voronolga. Fordgorod borders Galininograd. Voronolga borders Galininograd. Abdorostan borders Fordgorod. Abdorostan borders Voronolga. Voronolga borders Getarovo. Getarovo borders Puotorsk. Getarovo borders Galininograd. Galininograd borders Bripetrsk. Bripetrsk borders Getarovo. Bripetrsk borders Fordgorod. If X borders Y, then Y borders X. The population of Voronolga is 10178291. The population of Abdorostan is 67123020. The population of Fordgorod is 7290132. The population of Galininograd is 2392010. The population of Puotorsk is 410293. The population of Getarovo is 22912062. The population of Bripetrsk is 412908. There are 7 provinces. The area of Voronolga is 671200 square kilometers. The area of Abdorostan is 912300 square kilometers. The area of Fordgorod is 671300 square kilometers. The area of Galininograd is 314900 square kilometers. The area of Puotorsk is 1023900 square kilometers. The area of Getarovo is 519200 square kilometers. The area of Bripetrsk is 428100 square kilometers. Baritolloti is the capital city of Grappulia. Grappulia is a state in Catardinia. Regnobenoa is a state in Catardinia. The capital of Regnobenoa is Messinitina. Messinitina is a city in Regnobenoa. Lomberona is a city in Regnobenoa. Bascilitina is a state in Catardinia. Lomtrieste is a city in Bascilitina. Albucapua is the capital city of Bascilitina. Geoturin is the capital city of the state of Cartabitan. Veronizzia is a city in Cartabitan. Brescitabia is a city in Cartabitan. If the population of X is smaller than 100000 then X is minor. Every city has one name. The Voronolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Voronolga runs through Voronolga. The Voronolga runs through Galininograd. The Voronolga runs through Puotorsk. The Voronolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Kolonolga is a river in Bievorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Puotorsk. The Kolonolga runs through Getarovo. The Kolonolga runs through Bripetrsk. The Karbankaya is a river in Bievorsk. The Karbankaya runs through Voronolga. The Karbankaya runs through Abdorostan. The Chetershka is a river in Bievorsk. The Chetershka runs through Fordgorod. The Brasyugan is a river in Bievorsk. The Brasyugan runs through Puotorsk. Koruhashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Koruhashi is 132902. Dogayashi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Dogayashi is 1923012. Kyoukashino is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kyoukashino, Kangoyaken is 210392. Agarikoshi is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Agarikoshi is 42910. Kagenegawa is a city in Kangoyaken. The population of Kagenegawa is 813729. Yotsuyamashi is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Yotsuyamashi is 21390162. There are 5 cities in Kangoyaken. Sennouhama is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Sennouhama is 29104. Kyoukashino is a city in Senkuoka. The population of Kyoukashino, Senkuoka is 210390. There are 3 cities in Senkuoka. If the population of X is less than 20000, X is not major.","questions":{"Q1":{"question":"What cities in Kangoyaken are not major?","answer":"Agarikoshi, Dogayashi, Kagenegawa, Koruhashi, Kyoukashino"}},"flags":["large_context","subjective_concept_definition","negation"]}
